<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Controllib" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="zeroVarOrder">Zero value cannot be used when using a row vector for subspace orders.</entry>
    <entry key="nonPersistentData">Model estimation failed. Check that the estimation data is sufficiently exciting. Try lower orders.</entry>
    <entry key="subspaceHighMaxOrderSelect">Specified orders are too high for search of optimal state-space model orders. Reduce the order values or use data with more samples. </entry>
    <entry key="tooFewSamples">There are too many parameters to estimate for chosen estimation data size. Reduce model order or use a larger data set. </entry>
    <entry key="KestFailed">Estimation of the model disturbance component failed. It has been set to zero in the estimated model. </entry>
    <entry key="changedPRBSLength">The period of the PRBS signal was changed to {0,number,integer}. Accordingly, the length of the generated signal will be {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="initialPRBSSequence">The PRBS signal delivered is the {0,number,integer} first values of a full sequence of length {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPRBSSequence">The period of the PRBS sequence must be between {0} and 2^{1}-1.</entry>
    <!-- fitRational messages -->
    <entry key="fitRationalUnspecifiedTs">Unspecified sample time (Ts=-1). It will be treated as Ts=1.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalRelDegFitDeterioration">Quality of fit deterioration is detected. Consider a relative degree closer to 0.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalInvalidSysDecriptionObj">Expected a [{0} {1}] param.Continuous object.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalInvalidSysDescription">Invalid system description in S, the first argument. See function help for valid values.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalInvalidSysDescriptionNotRowVector">Expected parameters in param.Continuous objects to be row vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalRelativeDegreeTooLarge">Relative degree cannot be larger than the denominator order. Assuming they are equal.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalDataConstraintConflictAtDC">Denominator parameter constraints imply Inf response at DC frequency. Remove the data at 0 rad/s.</entry>
    <entry key="fitRationalDataConstraintConflictAtNyquistFreq">Denominator parameter constraints imply Inf response at Nyquist frequency (pi/SampleTime). Remove the data at or very near the Nyquist frequency.</entry>
</message>
</rsccat>