<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="WrongHeight">이 연산을 하려면 두 테이블의 높이가 동일해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="FunWrongHeight">함수 ''{0}''을(를) 변수 ''{1}''에 적용하면 높이가 동일한 출력값을 반환해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidObjectArray">이 연산은 ''{0}''과(와) ''{1}'' 간에 정의되지 않았습니다. table형 또는 timetable형이 아닌 입력값은 숫자형 배열 또는 논리형 배열이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ArrayWrongHeight">배열 입력값의 높이는 테이블의 높이와 같거나 1이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ArrayWrongWidth">배열 입력값의 너비는 테이블의 너비와 같거나 1이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="NDArray">N-dimensional arrays are not supported for this operation when one of the inputs is a table.</entry>
    <entry key="DifferentVars">두 테이블은 동일한 변수를 가져야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="DifferentRowLabels">두 입력값은 행 레이블이 동일해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="MixedRowLabels">두 입력값은 동일한 유형의 행 레이블을 가져야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ImplicitExpansionRowLabels">두 입력값은 높이가 동일해야 합니다. 하나의 행 입력이 행 레이블을 가질 경우 묵시적 확장이 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleUnits">입력 테이블이 이 연산에서 호환되지 않는 VariableUnits를 가집니다.</entry>
    <entry key="AssumeSameUnits">한 입력값에 대해서는 정의되고 다른 입력값에 대해서는 정의되지 않은 VariableUnits가 하나 이상의 테이블 변수에 있습니다. 연산자 ''{0}''은(는) 정의되지 않은 단위를 다른 단위와 일치하는 것으로 간주합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="AssumeUnitless">한 입력값에 대해서는 정의되고 다른 입력값에 대해서는 정의되지 않은 VariableUnits가 하나 이상의 테이블 변수에 있습니다. 연산자 ''{0}''은(는) 정의되지 않은 단위를 단위 없음을 뜻하는 것으로 간주합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="CustomPropsClash">동일한 사용자 지정 속성 이름이 한 테이블에서는 테이블에 해당하는 속성이고 다른 테이블에서는 변수에 해당하는 속성인 경우에는 산술 연산이 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="MinMaxLinearIndices">Linear indices output I is not supported for tabular inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="MinMaxAllLinearIndices">Indices output I is not supported for tabular inputs when applying ''{0}'' over all elements.</entry>
    <entry key="MultiColumnVarAmbiguous">All variables must be column vectors when the dimension input is greater than 1.</entry>
    <entry key="TabularVarAmbiguous">Variables cannot be tabular when the dimension input is greater than 1.</entry>
    <entry key="RowOperationUnitsMismatch">Row operation requires all variables to have the same unit.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsortedRowtimes">Row times must be sorted (ascending) to use ''{0}'' on a timetable input.</entry>
    <entry key="FunWrongSize">The output of this function must match the size of the input.</entry>
    <entry key="VarFunFailed">함수 ''{0}''을(를) 변수 ''{1}''에 적용하면 오류가 발생합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="RowFunFailed">함수 ''{0}''을(를) 입력 테이블의 행에 적용하는 동안 오류가 발생했습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="FunFailed">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the input table generated an error.</entry>
    <entry key="VarReductionWrongHeight">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one row when applied to variable ''{1}'' in the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="RowReductionWrongHeight">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the rows of the input table must return an output with the same height.</entry>
    <entry key="NoopReductionWrongHeight">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the input table with an empty vector of dimensions or a dimension argument greater than 2 must return an output with the same height.</entry>
    <entry key="ReductionWrongHeight">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one row when applied to the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="ReductionWrongWidth">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one column when applied to the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="DiffND">Dimension input cannot be greater than 2 to use ''diff'' on a tabular input.</entry>
    <entry key="TabularOption">위치 {0}의 인수는 ''{1}'' 유형일 수 없습니다.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
