<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011, 2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="WrongNumberOfComponentsException">CData should have 1, 3, or 4 components.</entry>
    <entry key="NumColorsNotEqualNumVertsException">Number of colors must equal number of vertices.</entry>
    <entry key="NumColorsNotEqualNumVertsOrNumFacesException">Number of colors must equal number of vertices or faces.</entry>
    <entry key="NumAlphaNotEqualNumVertsException">Number of alpha values must equal number of vertices.</entry>
    <entry key="NumAlphaNotEqualNumVertsOrNumFacesException">Number of alpha values must equal number of vertices or faces.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedColorStyleException">Unsupported color style.</entry>
    <entry key="mxArrayBadType">Unsupported type for Faces array.</entry>
    <entry key="MarkerFaceColorNotEqualToNumColors">The number of colors must be equal to number of vertices when MarkerFaceColor or MarkerEdgeColor is 'flat'.</entry>
    <entry key="MarkerFaceColorNotEqualToNumColorsEmpty">The number of colors must be equal to number of vertices when MarkerFaceColor or MarkerEdgeColor is 'flat'.</entry>
    <entry key="FacesToVerticesDataInconsistency">Values in Faces must be between 1 and the number of vertices.</entry>
    <entry key="FaceVertexAlphaDataNull">FaceVertexAlphaData must be specified when FaceAlpha is 'flat' or 'interp'.</entry>
    <entry key="FaceColorToAlphaInconsistency">Flat or interp true alpha is not supported when the FaceColor is interp indexed.</entry>
    <entry key="VertexNormalsToVerticesInconsistency">Size of VertexNormals must be equal to the size of Vertices when FaceLighting or EdgeLighting is 'gouraud'.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidVertexNormals">VertexNormals cannot be an empty array when FaceLighting or EdgeLighting is 'gouraud'.</entry>
    <entry key="FaceNormalsToFacesInconsistency">Size of FaceNormals must be equal to the size of Faces when FaceLighting or EdgeLighting is 'flat'.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFaceNormals">FaceNormals cannot be an empty array when FaceLighting or EdgeLighting is 'flat'.</entry>
    <entry key="VertexDataDimensionMismatch">Specify the coordinates as matrices of the same size or as vectors with the same number of elements.</entry>
    <entry key="DatatypeSyntaxMismatch">{0} value must match the data type of the corresponding ruler. To specify categorical, datetime, or duration data, use the positional argument syntax.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
