<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="OperatorNotSupported">演算子はサポートされていません。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTraverseFcn">Not enough arguments. The "traverse" method must have one or more input arguments and one or more output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidVariableName">Variable name "{0}" is not a selected variable. Filter constraints can only be applied on selected variables:\n\n    {1}\n\n</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterInput">Input argument must be a table or timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterOperand">Data type of operand not supported for filtering. Supported operand data types are: numeric, string, logical, datetime, duration scalars, or character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperationOperand">Relational operators (&gt;, &lt;, &gt;=, &lt;=, ==, ~=) with multiple rowfilter or eventfilter inputs are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperatorInputs">Relational operator must have a rowfilter or eventfilter object as input.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">Invalid binary operator input. Both operands must be rowfilter or eventfilter objects.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForRelationalOperator">Unsupported relational operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForBinaryOperator">Unsupported binary operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="MissingNotSupported">Missing values are not supported as operands to RowFilter.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterInput">関数 "rowfilter" への入力が無効です。入力は次のいずれかでなければなりません。\n - string ベクトル、文字ベクトル、または文字ベクトルの cell 配列\n - ParquetInfo オブジェクト\n - ParquetDatastore オブジェクト\n - DatabaseDatastore オブジェクト\n - table または timetable。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidIndexingOperation">Unsupported filtering operation. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingInput">Unsupported dot indexing input for filtering. Use a string scalar or a character vector to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingVariableNames">Unrecognized variable name for filtering. Select a variable for filtering using one of the following variable names: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedDotAssignment">Unsupported filtering operation. rowfilter and eventfilter variables cannot be set using dot assignment.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedClassVersion">バージョンに互換性がないため、matlab.io.RowFilter を読み込めません。\nRowFilter を再構成することを検討してください。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterClass">RowFilter ディスパッチャーのクラス "{0}" が無効です。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">Unable to use a row filter to subscript into the variables of a table, timetable, or event table. Specify rows using the syntax T(rf,vars), where rf specifies a row filter and vars specifies variables of T.</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperationFailed">制約を適用できません: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedType">Unexpected type returned from relational operator in the "{0}" expression. A logical vector was expected but the expression returned a value of "{1}" type.</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedDimensions">式 "{0}" の関係演算子から予期せぬ次元の logical 行列が返されました。結果は空の logical 配列または logical の列ベクトルでなければなりません。しかし、式は {1} の logical 行列を返しました。</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedHeight">式 "{0}" の関係演算子から予期せぬ行数が返されました。{1} 行が必要ですが、式は {2} 行の logical ベクトルを返しました。</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
