<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2022 The MathWorks, Inc.
-->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ioserver" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="TransportLayerObjectCorrupted">Transport layer object is corrupted. Clear and recreate the hardware object.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTransportLayer">Invalid transport layer object. Supported transport layer are {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableToReceiveData">Unable to receive data from the target hardware. \n For MATLAB, reconnect the target hardware, clear the hardware objects and try again. \n For Simulink, reconnect the target hardware and start simulation again.</entry>
        <entry key="StreamingPacketSizeInconsistent">Packet size is changing at runtime.</entry>
        <entry key="OnDemandBufferFull">On demand storage buffer for received data is full. The buffer size will increase dynamically which might affect performance. To avoid performance issues, increase the on demand storage using Name-Value pair 'DataStorageOnDemandLength' during IOProtocol object creation.</entry>
        <entry key="PeripheralResponseSizeMismatch">Response size for request ID 0x{0} is expected as {1} but received as {2}.</entry>
        <entry key="TransmissionOverrun">Not enough memory on the target to buffer the data. Data dropped may be seen in the logged data.</entry>
        <entry key="DebugObjectNotFound">No debug object is present on host to decode the trace messages from hardware. Either disable traceOn or create a new hardware object.</entry>
        <entry key="DebugMessageCorrupted">Error occurred while decoding the trace message corresponding to message Id {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDebugMessageID">No debug message is defined for message id {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="I2CDeviceDisconnect">Unable to read the data from the I2C device. Check the connections between the hardware and device, For MATLAB clear the device object and try again. For Simulink, stop the simulation and start again.</entry>
        <entry key="I2CDeviceTimeOut">Reading data from I2C device timed out. This issue occurs when the connection between the hardware and I2C device is not intact. Check the connections between the hardware and device, For MATLAB clear the device object and try again. For Simulink, stop the simulation and start again.</entry>
        <entry key="LowSamplesPerRead">Time required to fetch one frame is too high. Consider reducing the SamplesPerRead or increasing the SampleRate.</entry>
        <entry key="IOProtocolStreamingBufferFull">The internal buffers to store data is full. Read data to clear the buffers so that you can continue reading data from the hardware.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTime">The target hardware cannot read data as the Sample time/Sample rate is not a positive number.</entry>
        <entry key="CFunctionNotFound">No C function found on server for request ID "0x{0}".</entry>
        <entry key="MaximumTxPacketSize">Current Data size is {0} bytes. Data size must be less than or equal to {1} bytes.</entry>
        <entry key="MaximumRxPacketSize">Current response Data size is {0} bytes. Response Data size must be less than or equal to {1} bytes.</entry>
        <entry key="NotEnoughMemoryForBuffers">Not enough memory to create buffers on target. Increase the heap size or Sample time (decrease Sample rate) of the Source/Sensor.</entry>
        <entry key="ServerSchedulerInOverrun">The target hardware is in an overrun condition. Increase the Sample time (decrease Sample rate) of the Source/Sensor.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidHeapUtilizationFactor">Utilization should be greater than zero and less than or equal to 1.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidStopBit">Invalid Stop bit type value, expected value to be one of these values: 0.5, 1, 1.5 or 2</entry>
        <entry key="StreamingNotConfigured">Streaming configuration is not done. Configure streaming before starting to stream.</entry>
        <entry key="SampleRateNotConfigured">Sample rates not set for all sources. Set sample rate for all streaming sources.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDebugObject">Invalid debug object provided.</entry>
        <entry key="ExternalSerialDeprecated">'external' serial object creation is not supported. Instead, use 'internal' while creating the serial object.</entry>
        <entry key="ExternalTcpClientDeprecated">'external' tcpclient object creation is not supported. Instead, use 'internal' while creating the tcpclient object.</entry>
        <entry key="CommandQueueFull">Command queue is full.</entry>
        <entry key="EmptyCommandQueue">No command available in command queue.</entry> 
        <entry key="MemoryAddressLengthError">Memory address length and addressbuswidth are not equal.</entry>
        <entry key="MemoryAddressError">Expecting an array in the range 0-255 for memoryAddress.</entry>
        <entry key="ResponseSizeError">Expecting a value in the range 0-65535 for responseSize or Data.</entry>
        <entry key="PeripheralDataError">Expecting an array in the range 0-65535 for data.</entry>
        <entry key="NonNumericError">The value is not of numeric type.</entry>
        <entry key="NotLogicalError">The value is not of logical type.</entry>
        <entry key="NotCellArrayError">The passed parameter is not a cell array.</entry>
        <entry key="DataLengthError">Length of responseSize or Data is not a multiple of charsize.</entry>
        <entry key="BitPositionValueError">Mismatch between dataType, bitPosition and bitValue</entry>
        <entry key="PortInUse"> Specified Serial port is in use. </entry>
        <entry key="PortNotAvailable"> Specified Serial port is not available in the serial list. </entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedCommunicationInterface">Connected I/O: Unsupported Communication Interface.</entry>
        <entry key="RegenerationDueToConfigurationParameterChanges">IO Server will be regenerated due to Configuration Parameter changes.</entry>
        <entry key="RegenerationDueToUSARTConfigurationParameterChanges">IO Server will be regenerated due to USART Configuration Parameter changes.</entry>
        <entry key="RegenerationDueToADCConfigurationParameterChanges">IO Server will be regenerated due to ADC Parameter changes.</entry>
        <entry key="RegenerationDueToIOCChanges">IO Server will be regenerated due to STM32CubeMX project file updates.</entry>
        <entry key="ServerNotFlashedProperly">Simulink Connected IO: Error: IO server is not flashed properly. Reconnect the board and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableToGetVersionNumber">Simulink Connected IO: Unable to get the latest server version number.</entry>
        <entry key="WrongDataTypeSpecified">Wrong data type specified</entry>
        <entry key="SizeOfInputDoesntMatchSizeOfOutput">Size of input does not match the size of output.</entry>
        <entry key="NumberOfInputsDoesNotMatchTheNumberOfDatatypes">Number of inputs does not match the number of datatypes.</entry>
        <entry key="NumberOfElementInSizeDoesNotMatchDatatypes">The number of elements in Size must be the same as Datatype.</entry>
        <entry key="InputHasIncorrectDatatype">Input {0}  has incorrect datatype. Expected: {1}, Actual: {2} </entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedDatatype">Unsupported datatype: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="BytePackMaskText">Pack input data into a single output vector of required type.</entry>
        <entry key="ByteUnPackMaskText">Unpack input data packet into its constituent data vectors of required type.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputDatatypes">Output datatypes.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputSize">Output size.</entry>
        <entry key="DatatypeMustBeACell">Datatype must be a cell array.</entry>
        <entry key="SizeMustBeACell">Size must be a cell array.</entry>
        <entry key="SizeMustContainPositiveNumericVectors">Size must contain positive numeric vectors.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
<!-- LocalWords:  serial tcpclient
-->
