<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="BackgroundRemedyForDisallowed" context="error"
           note="This message is a remedy to be appended to our unsupported error messages. The full error message will be:
                 'Use of {0} is not supported on a thread-based worker. Use alternatives supported on the background pool.'"
           >{0} Use alternatives supported on the background pool.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotPreallocatePoolArray" context="error">Creating arrays of parallel pools is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="DisallowedPathAlteration" context="error">Changing the MATLAB path is not supported on a thread-based worker.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAttachFilesArgument" context="error">Files must be specified as a character vector or a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidParallelPoolFallBack" context="warning">Failed to create parallel pool, your code will run in serial instead. To use a parallel pool, change your default cluster profile or validate it in the Cluster Profile Manager.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionMethod" context="error">Invalid partition method argument. Partition method argument must be one of {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionNumWorkersPerGPU" context="error">Invalid value for "MaxNumWorkersPerGPU" partition method argument. Value must be a numeric scalar integer equal to the maximum number of workers per unique GPU to use.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionNumWorkersPerHost" context="error">Invalid value for "MaxNumWorkersPerHost" partition method argument. Value must be a numeric scalar integer equal to the maximum number of workers per unique host to use.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionWorkersArgument" context="error">Invalid value for "Workers" partition method argument. Value must be an array of parallel.Worker instances, all of which must be members of the input parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPool" context="error">The parallel pool has shut down. Use parpool to start a new pool.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidUseParallel" context="error">Invalid value. UseParallel must be "on", "off", "auto", true, or false.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidUseParallelForApp" context="error">Invalid value. UseParallel must be "on", "off", true, or false.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSerializedPool" context="error">Use of a loaded parallel pool object is not supported. Avoid storing parallel pool objects in MAT files or sending them between MATLAB Sessions.</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoAttachedFiles" context="uistring">No files automatically added to the parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoCreate" context="error">No parallel pool is available for parallel execution and AutoCreate is disabled. Either create a parallel pool using parpool, set UseParallel to "auto", or modify your Parallel Settings to enable AutoCreate.</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoCreateOnWorker" context="error">No parallel pool is available for parallel execution. Either create a parallel pool using parpool, or set UseParallel to "auto".</entry>
    <entry key="NoParallelPoolAvailableInApp" context="error">No parallel pool is available for parallel execution and AutoCreate is disabled. Either create a parallel pool using parpool or modify your Parallel Settings to enable AutoCreate.</entry>
    <entry key="PCTNotLicensed" context="error">Parallel functionality with parallel pools requires Parallel Computing Toolbox.</entry>
    <entry key="PCTNotInstalled" context="error">Parallel functionality with parallel pools requires a Parallel Computing Toolbox license.</entry>
    <entry key="ParpoolRemedyForDisallowed" context="error"
           note="This message is a remedy to be appended to our unsupported error messages. The full error message will be:
                 'Use of {0} is not supported on a thread-based worker. Use a PARPOOL('Processes') process-based pool or a different process-based pool instead.'"
           >{0} Use a PARPOOL('Processes') process-based pool or a different process-based pool instead.</entry>
    <entry key="PartitionErrorNumWorkersPerGPU" context="error">Failed to partition pool using "NumWorkersPerGPU" method. Caused by:\n{0}.</entry>
    <entry key="ScalarPoolRequired" context="error">A scalar parallel pool is required as the first argument to ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SerialFallbackOnAutoCreateFailure" context="warning">Failed to automatically create a parallel pool with the default parallel environment. Running serially on the client instead. Fallback to serial execution will be removed in a future release. Error details:\n\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="SerializedPool" context="uistring">Parallel pool is unavailable because it was created in a different MATLAB session or it has been loaded from a file.</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownPool" context="uistring">Shutdown parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="SlowToGatherGPUDevice" context="warning">Waiting to gather gpuDevice information for each parallel pool worker. One or more required parallel pool workers are busy executing PARFEVALs. If this is expected, disable this warning using {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesDifferentPool" context="error">tocBytes must be called with the same connected pool object that was used for ticBytes.</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesNotCalled" context="error">ticBytes must be called without an output argument before calling tocBytes with only a single input argument.</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesResultRequired" context="error">Argument to tocBytes must be the argument returned from ticBytes.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeature" context="error">Syntax not supported on a thread-based pool.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureBackground" context="error">Syntax not supported on a thread-based pool. Use alternatives supported on the background pool.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureParpool" context="error">Syntax not supported on a thread-based pool. Use a process-based parallel pool instead.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureInternalPool" context="error">Syntax not supported on internal pool.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureNonParpool" context="error">Syntax not supported on the background pool. Use a Parallel Computing Toolbox pool created via parpool instead.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedTicBytesTocBytes" context="warning">Thread-based pools do not support measuring bytes sent to or received from workers.</entry>
    <entry key="UseDelete" context="error">"close" not supported for parallel pool objects. Use "delete" instead. </entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
