<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="vision" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidLabelNames">레이블 정의 테이블의 각 이름은 유효한 MATLAB 변수 이름이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidName">{0} is an invalid label name. Please update the label definitions table.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidLabelType">Expected each Type in the label definitions table to be a labelType enumeration.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidPixelLabelID">Expected each PixelLabelID in the label definitions table to be a column vector or M-by-3 matrix with values between 0 and 255. Other label types must specify an empty PixelLabelID.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidLabelDesc">Expected each Description in the label definitions table to be a character vector or a string.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidLabelGroup">Expected each Group in the label definitions table to be a character vector or a string.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsInvalidLabelColor">Expected each Color in the label definitions table to be a 3 element row vector and not yellow [1 1 0] in color</entry>
    <entry key="labelHierarchyInvalidPixelLabelID">Invalid label definitions defined with  PixelLabel label type, sublabels and/or attributes.</entry>
    <entry key="labelHierarchyInvalidLabelDesc">Invalid label description for labels defined with sublabel and/or attributes.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidHierarchynotStruct">하위레이블 및/또는 특성으로 정의된 레이블 정의가 유효하지 않습니다. 구조체여야 합니다</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelDefinitionColumns">레이블 정의는 2~5개의 열을 가진 테이블이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelDefinitionColumnsPixelLabel">Expected label definitions to be a table with 2 - 4 columns when PixelLabel is not one of the label types.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataSourceFooter">유효하지 않은 DataSource입니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt;를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsNotUnique">Expected each Name in the label definitions table to be unique.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRootDir">rootDirectory는 유효한 디렉터리 이름이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelSpecification">레이블은 레이블 이름으로 구성된 셀형 배열/string형 또는 labelType 열거형으로 지정되어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="typeNotPresent">labelType ''{0}''의 레이블을 찾을 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="nonEmptyLabels">레이블은 비어 있어서는 안 됩니다.</entry>
    <entry key="labelNotFound">레이블 ''{0}''을(를) 찾을 수 없음</entry>
    <entry key="groupNotFound">그룹 ''{0}''을(를) 찾을 수 없음</entry>
    <entry key="inconsistentLabelDefNames">레이블 데이터의 열 이름이 레이블 정의와 일치하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="inconsistentTimeStamps">레이블 데이터의 타임스탬프 개수가 데이터 소스와 일치하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="badPolygonData">Invalid entry in label data table for Polygon labelType. Table entries for column ''{0}'' must be  M-by-1 cell arrays, each containing N-by-2 matrices of [x, y] locations. Please refer to &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; object.</entry>
    <entry key="badPointData">Point labelType에 대한 레이블 데이터 테이블의 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''에 대한 테이블 요소는 [x, y] 위치의 M×2 행렬이어야 합니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; 객체를 참조하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badRectData">레이블 데이터 테이블에서 Rectangle labelType에 대한 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''에 대한 테이블 요소는 [x, y, width, height]의 M×4 행렬이어야 합니다. 너비와 높이는 음수가 아니어야 합니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('groundTruth')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; 객체를 참조하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badRotatedRectData">레이블 데이터 테이블에서 Rotated Rectangle labelType에 대한 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''에 대한 테이블 요소는 [xctr, yctr, width, height, yaw]의 M×5 행렬이어야 합니다. 너비와 높이는 음수가 아니어야 합니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('groundTruth')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; 객체를 참조하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badProjCuboidData">Invalid entry in label data table for Projected Cuboid labelType. Table entries for column ''{0}'' must be M-by-8 matrices of [x1, y1, width1, height1, x2, y2, width2, height2]. The values of width1, height1, width2 and height2 must be non-negative. Please refer to &lt;a href="matlab:doc('groundTruth')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; object.</entry>
    <entry key="badCuboidData">Invalid entry in label data table for Cuboid labelType. Table entries for column ''{0}'' must be M-by-9 matrices of [xctr, yctr, zctr, xlen, ylen, zlen, xrot, yrot, zrot]. The xlen, ylen and zlen must be non-negative. Please refer to &lt;a href="matlab:doc('groundTruthMultisignal')"&gt;groundTruthMultisignal&lt;/a&gt; object.</entry>
    <entry key="badLineData">레이블 데이터 테이블에서 Line labelType에 대한 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''의 테이블 요소는 M×1 셀형 배열이어야 합니다. 각 요소는 [x, y] 위치값의 N×2 행렬 또는 [x, y, z] 위치값의 N×3 행렬이어야 합니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;groundTruth&lt;/a&gt; 객체를 참조하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidEntryLabelDataStruct">레이블 데이터 테이블의 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''에 대한 테이블 요소는 구조체형이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="badSceneData">Invalid entry in label data table for Scene labelType. Table entries for column ''{0}'' must be logical scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="badImageDirSource">데이터 소스가 찾을 수 없는 디렉터리를 가리킵니다.\n''{0}''\n&lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt; 메서드를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badImageNameSource">데이터 소스가 다음 디렉터리에 있는 한 개 이상의 영상 파일을 가리킵니다. \n ''{0}''\n 하지만 이러한 영상 파일을 찾을 수 없습니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt; 메서드를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badSource">데이터 소스를 찾을 수 없습니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt; 메서드를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badVideoSource">데이터 소스가 찾을 수 없는 비디오 파일을 가리킵니다.\n ''{0}''\n &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt; 메서드를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="badPixelLabelData">레이블 데이터 테이블에서 PixelLabel labelType에 대한 요소가 유효하지 않습니다. 열 ''{0}''에 대한 테이블 요소는 문자형 벡터로 지정된 영상 파일 이름이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDataMissingPixelLabelData">레이블 데이터는 PixelLabelData라는 하나의 열을 포함해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsMissingType">레이블 정의의 두 번째 열은 labelType 열거형을 포함해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="badImageFiles">데이터 소스가 가리키는 영상 파일 중에서 찾을 수 없는 파일이 한 개 이상 있습니다. &lt;a href="matlab:doc('changeFilePaths')"&gt;changeFilePaths&lt;/a&gt; 메서드를 사용하여 DataSource 파일 이름을 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="nonCellstrDataSource">dataSource는 문자형 벡터로 지정된 영상 파일 이름의 셀형 배열이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsAllColumnsNotSameFormat"> Expected all PixelLabelID values to be either column vectors or M-by-3 matrices.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsDuplicateIDs">The same PixelLabelID value in the label definitions table must not be used for multiple label categories.</entry>
    <entry key="pixelLabelsNotSupportWithTimeStamps">labelType.PixelLabel 유형의 레이블 정의에서는 타임스탬프가 있는 데이터 소스가 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="labelDefsMissingPixelLabelID">Expected label definitions table to have PixelLabelID columns when any label type is labelType.PixelLabel.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPixelLabelNotCell">Expected PixelLabelID values in the label definitions table to be cell arrays of numeric values.</entry>
    <entry key="pixelLabelSelectByNameNotSupported">labelType.PixelLabel 레이블에서는 이름을 기준으로 레이블을 선택할 수 없습니다. selectLabels(gTruth, labelType.PixelLabel)를 사용하여 labelType.PixelLabel 레이블을 선택하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="PixelLabelDataNotFoundOnLoad">groundTruth 객체의 LabelData가 가리키는 PixelLabelData 파일 중에서 찾을 수 없는 파일이 한 개 이상 있습니다. changeFilePaths 메서드를 사용하여 PixelLabelData 항목을 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidAlternatePathsType">The alternateFilePaths must be a string vector, a cell array of string vectors or a cell array of character vectors. Each string vector must be of size 1-by-2 and of the form [current alternative].</entry>
    <entry key="NumFilesNotResolved">\n이 groundTruth 객체에서 {0}개 파일이 아직 확인되지 않았습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="AllFilePathsResolved">\n이 groundTruth 객체에서 모든 파일 경로가 확인되었습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="CustomSourceOnlyPixel">사용자 지정 소스의 경우 PixelLabelData만 업데이트됩니다. 유효한 &lt;a href="matlab:doc('groundTruthDataSource')"&gt;groundTruthDataSource&lt;/a&gt; 객체를 사용하여 DataSource를 업데이트하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="labelNameExists">newName ''{0}'' already exists in this groundTruth object. Provide a new label name that is not part of the groundTruth object.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNewLabelName">''{0}''은(는) 유효한 변수 이름이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="badROILabelData">ROILabelData column must contain a valid structure.</entry>
    <entry key="badROILabelDataField">ROILabelData structure contains invalid field name.</entry>
    <entry key="badROILabelDataLabelName">ROILabelData structure contains label names which are not present in the labelDefinitions input.</entry>
    <entry key="ValidateStringsMustBeNonEmpty">{0} 값은 비어 있지 않아야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ValidateInputNotStringOrCellstr">{0}은(는) string형이거나 문자형 벡터로 구성된 셀형 배열이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="SceneTimeRangesNoSceneLabels">The input ground truth at index {0} does not have any scene label data.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesVerboseStart">{1}개의 ground truth 데이터 소스에서 {0}개의 비디오를 작성하는 중입니다.\n</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCreateFolder">Unable to create the folder: {0}\n\n{1}\n</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesTimeRangesSizeMismatch">시간 범위 입력값은 Mx1 크기의 셀형 배열이어야 합니다. 여기서 M은 gTruth 입력값의 요소 개수입니다.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesFolderNamesSizeMismatch">폴더 이름 입력값은 Mx1 크기의 셀형 배열이어야 합니다. 여기서 M은 시간 범위 입력값의 요소 개수입니다.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesInvalidTimeRange">인덱스 {0}의 시간 범위 셀형 배열 입력값은 2열 duration형 행렬이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesInvalidFolderNameSize">The folder names cell array input at index {0} must be a categorical or a string column vector with number of rows equal to the duration matrix at index {0} of the time ranges cell array input.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesInvalidRootFolder">The root folder input must be a non-empty scalar string or a character vector specifying the root folder to prepend to the folder names.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesReadError">시간 {0}에 ground truth {1}에서 프레임을 읽어 들이는 중 오류가 발생했습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteVideoScenesWriteError">An error occurred while writing a frame at time {0} in ground truth {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedMPEG4InPlatform">The specified VideoProfile, "{0}", is not supported on this platform.\nSee &lt;a href="matlab:doc('VideoWriter')"&gt;VideoWriter&lt;/a&gt; documentation for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="IndexedAVIUnsupportedReader">The input ground truth at index {0} does not have a video file with "Indexed AVI" video format.\nThe "Indexed AVI" VideoProfile is only supported when the ground truth datasource is backed by an "Indexed AVI" video file.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelTypeForGrouping">gatherLabelData does not support Scene Label type when the value of 'GroupLabelData' is 'LabelType'.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeRequiresAtLeastTwoInputGTruth">병합하려면 2개의 이상의 groundTruth 객체가 필요합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeUnsupportedSource">비디오 또는 영상 시퀀스 소스가 있는 groundTruth 객체는 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeOutputFolderMustExist">지정한 출력 폴더가 존재하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeUnableToCreateFolder">출력 폴더 {0}을(를) 생성할 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeUnsupportedLabelType">사용자 지정 레이블 유형은 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeUnableToReadPixelLabelData">픽셀 레이블 데이터를 읽을 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeUnableToWritePixelLabelData">병합된 픽셀 레이블 데이터를 쓸 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeImageCollectionAndDatastoreUsingNonDefaultReadFcn">모든 입력 groundTruth 객체에는 디폴트 읽기 함수를 사용하는 imageDatastore 데이터 소스가 있어야 합니다. 이 데이터 소스는 imageDatastore 소스와 영상 파일 목록으로 정의된 소스의 혼합을 groundTruth 객체와 병합할 때 필요합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeDifferentReadFcn">모든 입력 groundTruth 객체에는 동일한 읽기 함수를 갖는 imageDatastore 소스가 있어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeInvalidDataSource">하나 이상의 입력 groundTruth 객체에 유효하지 않은 데이터 소스가 있습니다. 각 입력 groundTruth를 검사하고 필요에 따라 changeFilePaths를 사용하여 파일 경로를 확인하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="mergePixelLabelUnequalSizes">병합되는 픽셀 레이블 데이터의 크기는 같아야 합니다. 다음 파일에 저장된 픽셀 레이블 데이터의 크기는 {0}이지만 ground truth 데이터 소스와 연결된 다른 픽셀 레이블 데이터의 크기는 {1}입니다:\n\nPixelLabelData: {2}\n\n데이터 소스: {3}\n</entry>
    <entry key="mergeLabelNameHasMultipleTypes">The label, {0}, must have the same label type in all input groundTruth objects.</entry>
    <entry key="mergeLabelNameHasMultipleHierarchies">The label, {0}, must have the same attribute and sub-label definitions in all input groundTruth objects.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
