<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="vision" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidSize">{0}은(는) 요소를 2개 가진 벡터여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="minSizeGTMaxSize">MaxSize 값은 MinSize 값보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="modelMinSizeGTMaxSize">MaxSize value must be greater than [{0} {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="minSizeLTTrainingSize">MinSize value must be greater than or equal to [{0} {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="modelNotFound">모델 {0}을(를) 찾을 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="modelNotFoundOnLoad">모델 {0}을(를) 찾을 수 없습니다. 디폴트 분류 모델 {1}을(를) 불러옵니다.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataTableWidthLessThanTwo">Width of the training data table must be greater than or equal to 2.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataFirstColumnNotFilename">First column of the training data must contain image filenames.</entry>
    <entry key="detectionResultsTableWidthLessThanTwo">Width of the detection results table must be greater than or equal to 2.</entry>
    <entry key="detectionResultsMustHaveLabels">Detections results table must contain labels in the third column when there are multiple classes in the ground truth data.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInTrainingDataTable">ground truth 데이터 테이블의 {0}행, {1}열에 있는 경계 상자가 유효하지 않습니다: {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInDetectionTable">검출 결과 테이블의 {0}행에 있는 경계 상자가 유효하지 않습니다: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidScoreInDetectionTable">검출 결과 테이블의 {0}행에 있는 점수 값이 유효하지 않습니다: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelInDetectionTable">검출 결과 테이블의 {0}행에 있는 레이블 값이 유효하지 않습니다: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedLabelInDetectionTable">Label value in row {0} of the detection results table must be one of the following categorical values: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="ROILessThanMinSize">입력 ROI의 크기({0})는 ''MinSize''({1})보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ROILessThanModelSize">입력 ROI의 크기({0})는 분류 모델의 크기({1})보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ImageLessThanMinSize">입력 영상의 크기({0})는 ''MinSize''({1})보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ImageLessThanModelSize">입력 영상의 크기({0})는 분류 모델의 크기({1})보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidObjectSize">Size of the object is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="classHasNoBoxes">{0} 클래스에 대한 훈련 데이터에는 적어도 하나의 경계 상자가 있어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataHasNoBoxes">훈련 데이터에는 적어도 하나의 경계 상자가 있어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInBboxTable">Invalid bounding box in row {0} of the bounding box table: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelInBboxTable">경계 상자 테이블의 {0}행에 있는 레이블 값이 유효하지 않습니다: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedLabelInBboxTable">Label value in row {0} of the bounding box table is undefined. It must be one of the following categorical values: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputImageChannelSize">입력 영상 채널 크기가 유효하지 않습니다. 입력 영상 채널 크기 {0,number,integer}은(는) 신경망의 입력 채널 크기 {1,number,integer}과(와) 같아야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="imageSmallerThanNetwork">입력 영상 크기는 {0}보다 커야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="unSupportedInputClass">입력 데이터형은 uint8형, uint16형, int16형, double형 또는 single형이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidEvaluationDatastoreInput">Evaluation ground truth data input must be a table or a datastore.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidBboxNotInCell">Bounding box from the read method output of the datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidBbox">데이터저장소의 read 메서드의 경계 상자 데이터가 유효하지 않습니다:\n{0} </entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidLabel">Label from the read method output of the datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-1 categorical, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalid">Output of the read method of the input datastore must be an M-by-3 or M-by-2 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTrainingInput">Training data input must be a table or a datastore.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputNotCellTable">Read method of the training input datastore must return an M-by-3 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputNotCellTwoOrThreeColTable">Read method of the training input datastore must return an M-by-3 or M-by-2 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidBbox">Bounding box column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array, containing elements of N-by-4 double matrix, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidLabel">Labels column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-1 categorical, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.\n\nThe categories of the categorical must contain all the label names for all of the training data.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidImage">Images column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-P-by-Q images or N-by-P grayscale images.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBoxesInTrainingData">입력 데이터저장소의 read 메서드의 훈련 데이터에 유효하지 않은 경계 상자가 포함되어 있습니다. 경계 상자는 비어 있지 않아야 하고, 연결된 영상 내에 완전히 포함되어야 하며, 너비와 높이가 양수여야 합니다. 데이터저장소 transform 메서드를 사용하고 유효하지 않은 경계 상자를 제거하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidValidationData">훈련 데이터가 데이터저장소인 경우 검증 데이터도 데이터저장소여야 합니다. 검증 데이터저장소의 read 메서드는 M×3 셀 또는 테이블을 반환해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="validationDataMustBeDatastore">Validation data not supported when training data input is a table. Use a datstore as both validation data and the training data input.</entry>
    <entry key="backgroundUnsupportedWithDatastore">Training option DispatchInBackground is not supported with datastore training data input. The value of ''options.DispatchInBackground'' must be 'false'.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidReadDataFromFile">다음 파일과 연결된 훈련 데이터가 유효하지 않음:\n\n{0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="tooManyClasses">Number of classes in the training data must be 1.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidBboxFileInfo">입력 데이터저장소의 read 메서드에서 반환되는 경계 상자는 N개 상자의 [x y width height] 값을 정의하는 숫자형 N×4 행렬을 포함하는 M×1 셀형 배열이어야 하고, 모든 상자의 너비와 높이는 양수여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidImageClass">입력 데이터저장소의 read 메서드에서 반환되는 영상 데이터의 클래스는 double형, single형, uint8형, int16형, uint16형 또는 논리형이어야 합니다. 또한, 영상 데이터는 비어 있지 않고 희소 형식이 아닌 실수여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidRGBOrGrayscaleImage">입력 데이터저장소의 read 메서드에서 반환되는 영상은 RGB 또는 회색조이고 M×1 셀형 배열에 저장되어야 합니다. 여기서 M은 영상 개수입니다.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataBboxOutsideBounds">Bounding boxes associated with the following image were not all located within the image: {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDetectionInput">입력 데이터는 데이터저장소여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDetectionDatastoreReadOutput">Read method of the input datastore must return a numeric array or an M-by-N cell or table containing elements of N-by-P-by-Q or N-by-P numeric arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToBatchImagesForDetect">Images must have the same size when the MiniBatchSize value is greater than 1. To detect objects in images of varying size, set the MiniBatchSize value to 1.</entry>
    <entry key="noDataFromDatastore">Datastore input does not have any data. Every call to the read method returns empty.</entry>
    <entry key="genericBaseMessageWithFilename">입력 데이터저장소에서 다음 파일을 처리하는 중 오류가 발생했습니다:\n\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="genericBaseMessageWithoutFilename">입력 데이터저장소에서 데이터를 처리하는 중 오류가 발생했습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="nonEmptyMetricsInfoInExperimentMonitor">Metrics property of the Experiment Monitor input must be empty.</entry>
    <entry key="unexpectedTypeForExperimentMonitor">Specified Experiment Monitor must be of type experiments.Monitor.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingPlotWithExperimentMonitor">Training option "Plots" must be "none" when specifying the Experiment Monitor option.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
