<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidYAMLFile">Unable to parse "metadata.yaml" file in the specified folder path. Ensure that the YAML file is correctly formatted.</entry>
    <entry key="YAMLFileNotFound">Unable to find valid "metadata.yaml" file in the specified folder path.</entry>
    <entry key="FileReadingError">Unable to read file ''{0}''. Ensure that MATLAB has read/write permissions for the folder, the YAML file is correctly formatted, and no bag file is corrupted or empty.</entry>
    <entry key="MsgIndicesInvalid">The specified message indices are not within the valid range of [{0},{1}].</entry>
    <entry key="CellStringInvalid" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">The value of the "{0}" argument is invalid. If selecting multiple entries, the input must be a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="FileCorruptError">Unable to read the data recorded on topic "{0}" because the bag file appears to be corrupt. Record this topic again to the bag file.</entry>
	<entry key="PathHasNonASCII">The path {0} contains non ASCII characters. The path must only contain ASCII characters.</entry>
	<entry key="Ros2bagWriterError">{0}</entry>
	<entry key="SerializationFormatError">{0}</entry>
	<entry key="MessageTypeError">{0}</entry>
	<entry key="WriteError">{0}</entry>
	<entry key="MsgTypeNotRegistered">Message type: {0} is not registered with this 'ros2bagwriter'. First register it using 'registerMessageType()' and then write to bag file.</entry>
    <entry key="Ros2bagWriterCreationError">Unable to create the 'ros2bagwriter'.</entry>
    <entry key="TimeStampListError">Length of input timestamp list does not match the length of input messages. While writing multiple messages using 'write', the length of input timestamp list and the length of input messages must be same.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicListError">Length of input topic list does not match the length of input messages. While writing multiple messages using 'write' the length of input topic list and length of input messages must be same. If all messages belong to same topic, a single topic can be given as input.</entry>
    <entry key="Ros2bagWriteError">An error occurred while writing message with topic: {0} and message type: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="InputPathAlreadyHasRos2bagFile">The input path {0} contains .yaml, .db3, or .mcap files. Make sure the input path does not contain any .yaml, .db3, or .mcap file.</entry>
    <entry key="ErrorCalculatingBagSize">An error occurred while calculating the size of the specified bag path.</entry>
    <entry key="DifferentSerializationFormatError">Reading bag file with serialization format "{0}" is not supported. Supported serialization format is "cdr".</entry>
    <entry key="ReadException">{0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownExceptionOccurred">An error occurred while reading the bag.</entry>
    <entry key="UnSupportedFileExtension">Specified file with the "{0}" extension is not supported. The path must point to a bag file with .db3 or .mcap extension, or a bag folder containing .db3, .mcap, or compressed bag files.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPath">The path must point to a bag file with .db3 or .mcap extension, or a bag folder containing .db3, .mcap, or .zstd compressed bag files.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCompressionFormat">Compression format "{0}" is not supported. Supported compression formats are none and zstd.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCompressionMode">Compression mode "{0}" is not supported. Supported compression modes are none, file and message.</entry>
	<entry key="InvalidMCAPCompressionMode">Compression mode "{0}" is not supported. MCAP storage format supports compression modes none and file.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBagFile">Invalid ROS 2 bag file specified.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBagFolder">Invalid input path {0} for a ROS 2 bag folder. Valid path must contain both metadata.yaml and, .db3 , .mcap, or .zstd compressed bag files.</entry>
	<entry key="CompressionModeError">Compression mode must be specified as "file" or "message", if the compression format specified is not "none".</entry>
	<entry key="MCAPCompressionModeError">Supported compression modes for MCAP storage format must be specified as "file", if the compression format specified is not "none".</entry>
    <entry key="CompressionFormatError">Compression format must be specified as "zstd", if the compression mode specified is not "none".</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageType">Invalid bag duration. Bag Duration must be specified as numeric value, ros2time or ros2duration struct.</entry>
	<entry key="ConfigFileAllowedOnlyForCustom">Storage configuration file is used only when the storage configuration profile is custom and storage format is MCAP.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStorageConfigFile">Storage configuration file "{0}" is not valid. </entry>
    <entry key="TopicHasNoMsg">Unable to read messages in topic {0}. Topic {0} is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownMessageType">The message type "{1}" is not a recognized custom message in MATLAB. As a result, messages of the same type belonging to topic "{0}" get skipped during bag file reading. To resolve this issue, use the 'ros2genmsg' function to add the custom message to MATLAB.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
