<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="CreateError">Failed to create a ROS 2 publisher with topic name {0} and message type {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="PublishError">Error publishing a message with message type {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="PublishReturnCallError">Response from ROS 2 network indicated failure to publish.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicNameNotFound">Topic {0} is not available on the ROS 2 network. Use "ros2 topic list" to display available topics.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicTypeNoMatch">Topic {0} with message type {1} is already on the ROS 2 network. Try creating the publisher with type {1}, not {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownError">Error occurred while shutting down the ROS 2 publisher.\n\nCaused by:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="GetInfoError">Error occurred while requesting information on the ROS 2 publisher.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInternalNodeError">ROS 2 node is no longer accessible by the publisher. Recreate the publisher on a valid node.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidServerHandleError">The ROS 2 publisher stored an invalid network reference. Recreate the publisher.</entry>
    <entry key="DuplicatePubHandlesError">Node contains multiple ROS 2 publishers with the same reference. Recreate the node.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicName">Invalid topic name {0}: topic name must not contain characters other than alphanumerics or '_', or start with '~/'.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicErrorText1" note="Error message from ros2 cpp" translate="false">Invalid topic name</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicErrorText2" note="Error message from ros2 cpp" translate="false">topic name unexpectedly valid</entry>
    <entry key="QoSDeadlineDefaultWarning">[{0}]: Missed offered deadline on topic {1}. The publisher failed to meet the expected deadline for publishing messages as per the deadline QoS policy. Total missed deadlines: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="QoSLivelinessDefaultWarning">[{0}]: Lost liveliness on topic {1}. The publisher has not indicated liveliness within the specified lease duration. Liveliness lost count: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="QoSIncompatibleDefaultWarning">[Publisher {0}]: Discovered a subscription on topic {1} requesting incompatible QoS. No messages will be sent to it. Last incompatible policy: {2}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
