<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="CreateError">Unable to create a ROS 2 subscriber with topic name {0} and message type {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="StartError">Unable to start subscriber for topic name {0} and message type {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicNameNotFound">Unable to find topic {0} on the ROS 2 network. Use "ros2 topic list" to display the list of available topics.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicTypeNoMatch">Topic {0} with message type {1} is already on the ROS 2 network. Try creating the subscriber with type {1}, not {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="WaitTimeout">Subscriber did not receive any messages and timed out.</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownStopError">Error occurred while shutting down the ROS 2 subscriber.\n\nCaused by:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownRemoveError">Error occurred while removing the ROS 2 subscriber.\n\nCaused by:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="GetInfoError">Error occurred while requesting information on the ROS 2 subscriber.</entry>
    <entry key="GetLatestMessageError">Error occurred retrieving the latest message from the ROS 2 subscriber.</entry>
    <entry key="GetMessageCountError">Error occurred retrieving the message count from the ROS 2 subscriber.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInternalNodeError">ROS 2 node no longer accessible by the subscriber. Recreate the subscriber on a valid node.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidServerHandleError">The ROS 2 subscriber stored an invalid network reference. Recreate the subscriber.</entry>
    <entry key="DuplicateSubHandlesError">Node contains multiple ROS 2 subscribers with the same reference. Recreate the node.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicName">Invalid topic name {0}: topic name must not contain characters other than alphanumerics or '_', or start with '~/'.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicErrorText1" note="Error message from ros2 cpp" translate="false">Invalid topic name</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTopicErrorText2" note="Error message from ros2 cpp" translate="false">topic name unexpectedly valid</entry>
    <entry key="QoSDeadlineDefaultWarning">[{0}]: Missed requested deadline on topic {1}. The subscription did not receive any messages within the expected duration set by the deadline QoS policy. Total missed deadlines: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="QoSLivelinessDefaultWarning">[{0}]: Liveliness on topic {1} changed. A change in the liveliness of one or more publishers on the topic has been detected. Alive count: {2}, Not alive count: {3}</entry>
    <entry key="QoSMessageLostDefaultWarning">[{0}]: Lost messages on topic {1}. Total lost messages: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="QoSIncompatibleDefaultWarning">[Subscriber {0}]: Discovered a publisher on topic {1} offering incompatible QoS. No messages will be received from it. Last incompatible policy: {2}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
