<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2025 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="PackagesFeatureOff">未启用包功能时，不支持此命令。请使用 -packages 命令行开关启动 MATLAB。</entry>
    <entry key="GupFeatureOff">This command is not supported when the gup feature is not enabled. Start MATLAB with the -gup command line switch.</entry>
    <entry key="PackageNotInstalled">Package {0} is not installed.</entry>
    <entry key="ResourceFileIsInvalid">Cannot install package at {0} because file {1} is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="HandleToUninstalledPackage">Handle to uninstalled package {0}</entry>
    <entry key="NotARegisteredPackageLocation">{0} is not a installed package's root folder.</entry>
    <entry key="ComparisonNotDefined">Comparison between {0} and {1} is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="StringOrCharExpected">Argument must be a string or a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="PackageClaimsFolderOnSearchPath">The following folder(s) have been removed from the MATLAB Search Path, because they now belong to the package {0}:\n\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="PackageClaimsOtherPackageFolders">The following folder(s) claimed by the package already belong to other package(s):\n\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="AmbiguousFunctionName">Reference to function ''{0}'' at this location is ambiguous.\nDefinitions of the function are exported by the following packages:\n\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="CanUseSearchSpaceBeingFalseIsUnsupported">The property 'CanUseSearchSpace' is unsupported in this beta release of MATLAB. Packages with 'CanUseSearchSpace' set to false may not work as expected. We suggest setting the 'CanUseSearchSpace' property to true.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSetDependencyDueToLevelMismatch">Unable to set a dependency from a Package {0} installed at level {1} to the Package {2} installed at level {3}.</entry>
    <entry key="DependencyDoesNotExist">Unable to remove dependency. Package {0} does not depend on Package {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="PermissionErrorWhileWritingToDatabase">Unable to modify install packages database due to permission while modifying the file: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToReadDatabase">Unable to read install packages database while trying to update the database. The detailed error message is :{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PackageFeatureChangeAttempt">Turning the packages feature on or off from within MATLAB is not permitted. Please restart MATLAB using matlab -packages or -nopackages.</entry>
    <entry key="DatabaseIsCorrupt">Unable to get previously installed packages because the database has been corrupted. The current session started with no package installed. You can still use package features normally, but no package installation configuration will be saved after closing the MATLAB.\n\nTo address this issue, please manually delete the file 'packages.mlsettings' under the preferences folder (prefdir). This will erase your previous package installation configuration.</entry>
    <entry key="PackageIsCorrupt">Previously installed package {0} is corrupt because one or more claimed folders are not accessible. This package will be ignored in this session.\nPlease fix the inaccessible folder(s) and re-install the package.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidContextOption">Invalid option {0}. Please provide either 'path' or 'installed'.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
