<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Compiler" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="DEPLOYTOOL_COULD_NOT_EXECUTE_MATLAB_BATCH">Error: Could not find MATLAB executable to execute matlab -batch command. \n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFirstInputOneInput">{0} is an invalid input argument. When using {1} with one input argument, the input must be a valid MATLAB\
      Compiler or MATLAB Compiler SDK Project (.prj) file.\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFirstInputTwoInputs">{0} is an invalid input argument.  When using {1} with two input arguments, the first input must be either "-build" or "-package"\
      and the second input must be a valid MATLAB Compiler or MATLAB Compiler SDK Project (.prj) file.\n</entry>
    <entry key="StandaloneDeploytoolToBeRemoved">System command line building and packaging using the deploytool executable will be removed in a future release. \n \
      Use mcc, deployment scenario specific functions such as compiler.build.standaloneApplication, and compiler.package.installer with matlab -batch instead.\n</entry>
    <entry key="DEPLOYTOOL_USAGE">This command builds and packages existing MATLAB Compiler projects from command line. \n \
    \n \
    USAGE: \n \
    deploytool -build projectname builds a project.\n \
    \n \
    deploytool -package projectname builds and packages a project.\n \
    \n \
    deploytool -? will display this message.\n  \
    \n \
    See also mcc, mbuild.\n\n</entry>
    <entry key="license_checkout_error">Error: Failed to check out a MATLAB Compiler license. \n</entry>
    <entry key="license_checkout_error_sdk">Error: Failed to check out a MATLAB Compiler SDK license. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MatlabOnlineSupport">MATLAB Compiler Apps are not supported in {0}.\n</entry>
    <entry key="DeploytoolFunctionalityToBeRemoved">{0} is scheduled for removal in a future release. To build and package MATLAB code programmatically, use the mcc command or target-specific functions such as compiler.build.standaloneApplication and compiler.package.installer.</entry>
    <entry key="DeploytoolBuildPackageToBeRemoved">{0} will not accept -build or -package in a future release. Use mcc, deployment scenario specific functions such as compiler.build.standaloneApplication, and compiler.package.installer instead.</entry>
    <entry key="OpenProjectRequiresDesktop">Opening a MATLAB Compiler project requires the MATLAB Desktop.\n</entry>
    <entry key="HadoopCompilerRemoved">hadoopCompiler has been removed.  To create standalone MATLAB MapReduce applications, or deployable archives from MATLAB map and reduce functions, use the mcc command.</entry>
    <entry key="ScalarArgument">The 4th argument to updateWinAppResourceBatch should be a scalar numeric.\n</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNumberOfInputArgs">Invalid number of input arguments to {0}. {0} takes {1} input(s).\n</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNumberOfOutputs">{0} returns at most {1} output(s).\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInput">Invalid input passed to {0}. All inputs have to be non-empty strings.</entry>
    <entry key="failedWithWinError">{0} failed with the following system error.\n\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="failedToCreateFile">Failed to open file {0} with error {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="outOfMemory">Insufficient memory to embed payload. Free some memory by deleting files or closing applications and then rerun the package process.</entry>
    <entry key="moreThan2GB">The resource cannot be added to the installer because the total file size would exceed the system limit of 2GB</entry>
    <entry key="errorAllocatingMemory">{0} - Error allocating memory.</entry>
    <entry key="errorReadingIconFile">Error reading icon file.</entry>
    <entry key="errorConvertingToInternalFormat">Error converting icon to internal format.</entry>
    <entry key="iconFileCannotBeEmpty">Icon file cannot be empty.</entry>
    <entry key="fileNotFound">File not found.</entry>
    <entry key="accessDenied">Access denied.</entry>
    <entry key="NotACompilerPRJ">{0} is not a valid Compiler PRJ file.</entry>
    <entry key="JavaAPIToBeRemoved">{0} is scheduled for removal in a future release. To package MATLAB code using the MATLAB Compiler apps, use {1} instead.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
