<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="vision" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="bcstCapabilities"  translate="false">integerSgn,integerUns,fixedptSgn,fixedptUns</entry>
    <entry key="Fnu8">Supports 8-bit unsigned integers.</entry>
    <entry key="FnWlLess16">Supports word lengths less than or equal to 16 bits.</entry>
    <entry key="FnWlLess32">Supports word lengths less than or equal to 32 bits.</entry>
    <entry key="FnOp">This data type is supported at the output port(s).</entry>
    <entry key="FnIp">This data type is supported at the input port(s).</entry>
    <entry key="FnSuppDepOnBlocksInside">The blocks inside the subsystem dictate the data types supported by this block.</entry>
    <entry key="FnHLineInt">The output port supports 32-bit signed integers only. Input ports Theta and Rho support signed integers, while Ref1 supports signed and unsigned integers.</entry>
    <entry key="FnHLineFxpt">Input ports Theta and Rho support signed fixed-point data types with word lengths less than or equal to 32, while Ref1 supports signed and unsigned fixed-point data types.</entry>
    <entry key="FnHLineBool">This data type is only supported at the input port Ref1.</entry>
    <entry key="FnExceptLICMethod"><![CDATA[This data type is not supported for the <tt>Local Intensity Comparison</tt> method.]]></entry>
    <entry key="FnSelFPSupport">Fixed-point data types are not supported at the Major Axis, Minor Axis, Orientation, and Eccentricity output ports.</entry>
    <entry key="FnCGNonFPSuit">Code generation not suitable for fixed-point processors.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingVIPLib">Loading Computer Vision Toolbox Library.</entry>
    <entry key="FnFftwHostOnly"><![CDATA[Generated code will be restricted to MATLAB host computers when you set the <b>FFT implementation</b> parameter to <tt>FFTW</tt>, or when the transform length is not a power of two. ]]></entry>
    <entry key="unrecognizedAction">Unrecognized action.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
