<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2025 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="vision">
  <message>
    <entry key="minMaxLogNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': This block does not support the logging of minimums and maximums using the Fixed-Point Tool.</entry>
    <entry key="inOutImgTypesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be the same as the Image input data type.</entry>
    <entry key="errROIClipOutNotBool">Error in ''{0}'': The Err_roi and Err_clip outputs must be Boolean scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="imgNotMxNOrMxNxP">Error in ''{0}'': The Image input must be a M-by-N or M-by-N-by-P array, where M and N must be two or greater.</entry>
    <entry key="tranMatWrongDims">Error in ''{0}'': The TForm input has incorrect dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="wrongROIDims">Error in ''{0}'': The ROI input has incorrect dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="outDimsSettingDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The output dimensions must match the dimensions specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="tranMatsROIDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The number of transformation matrices must equal the number of ROIs.</entry>
    <entry key="fillValueClrPansDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The number of elements in the 'Background fill value' parameter must equal the number of color panes.</entry>
    <entry key="transMatrixDimInvalid">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Transformation matrix' parameter has incorrect dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="boundBoxROIInvalid">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Bounding box of ROI' parameter has incorrect dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="verticesPolyInvalid">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Vertices of polygon ROI' parameter has incorrect dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsSignMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The input ports must both be signed or unsigned.</entry>
    <entry key="dimI1NotGTDimI2">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Output size' parameter is set to 'Valid', the dimensions of I1 must be greater than the dimensions of I2.</entry>
    <entry key="backPropI1NotAllow">Error in ''{0}'': Cannot back-propagate dimensions of I1 input port.</entry>
    <entry key="backPropI2NotAllow">Error in ''{0}'': Cannot back-propagate dimensions of I2 input port.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsRealOutComplex">Error in ''{0}'': When both inputs are real, the output must be real.</entry>
    <entry key="horVerCompxtyMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The horizontal and vertical coefficients must have the same complexity.</entry>
    <entry key="vertCoefNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The vertical coefficients input must be a vector.</entry>
    <entry key="horzCoefNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The horizontal coefficients input must be a vector.</entry>
    <entry key="pvalNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Pval input must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="firPadNotReal">Error in ''{0}'': When the image input is real, the pad value must be real.</entry>
    <entry key="noStatSelected">Error in ''{0}'': The first argument 'stats' to the Blob Analysis S-function must be nonempty. At least one of the 'Statistics' check boxes must be selected.</entry>
    <entry key="statNotBoolean">Error in ''{0}'': The first argument 'stats' to the Blob Analysis S-function must be Boolean.</entry>
    <entry key="notStatSelected">Error in ''{0}'': At least one of the statistics must be selected.</entry>
    <entry key="statsNotAvailable">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Major axis length,' 'Minor axis length,' 'Orientation,' and 'Eccentricity' statistics are not available for fixed-point data types, or when ''MinMaxAndOverflow'' is specified for the model parameter MinMaxOverflowLogging.</entry>
    <entry key="fillValStatMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Fill values' parameter must be a scalar or a vector with a number of elements equal to the number of selected statistics.</entry>
    <entry key="areaOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Area output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="centroidOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Centroid output must be 2-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="bndBoxOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Bounding box output must be 4-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="majAxisOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Major axis output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="minorAxisOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Minor axis output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="orientOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Orientation output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="eccOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Eccentricity output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="equDiaOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Equivalent diameter squared output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="extentOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Extent output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="perimOutWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimensions of the Perimeter output must be 1-by-(maximum number of blobs).</entry>
    <entry key="areaOutNotInt32">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Area output must be int32.</entry>
    <entry key="bndBoxOutNotInt32">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Bounding box output must be int32.</entry>
    <entry key="labelOutNotUint32">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Label output must be uint32.</entry>
    <entry key="labelOutNotUint16">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Label output must be uint16.</entry>
    <entry key="labelOutNotUint8">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Label output must be uint8.</entry>
    <entry key="labelOutNotDouble">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Label output must be double precision.</entry>
    <entry key="labelOutOntSingle">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Label output must be single precision.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutNotUint32">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Count output must be uint32.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutNotUint16">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Count output must be uint16.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutNotUint8">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Count output must be uint8.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutNotDouble">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Count output must be double precision.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutOntSingle">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the Count output must be single precision.</entry>
    <entry key="codeGenNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': This block does not support code generation when the output is a floating-point data type and min/max logging is enabled. Consider setting the model parameter MinMaxOverflowLogging to 'UseLocalSettings'.</entry>
    <entry key="inWidthNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the input image must be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="inHeightNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The height of the input image must be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="inWdHtNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The height and width of the input image must be each be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="inWidthNotDivFour">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the input image must be divisible by four.</entry>
    <entry key="outWidthNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the output image must be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="outWdHtNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The height and width of the output image must each be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="outWidthNotDivFour">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the output image must be divisible by four.</entry>
    <entry key="outHeightNotDivTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The height of the output image must be divisible by two.</entry>
    <entry key="inputNotMxNx3">Error in ''{0}'': The input must be an M-by-N-by-3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotMxN">Error in ''{0}'': The output must be an M-by-N matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotMxNx3">Error in ''{0}'': The output must be an M-by-N-by-3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="clrSpcConvNotSupport">Error in ''{0}'': The specified color space conversion is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="compositeInputsDimsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The Image 1 and Image 2 inputs must have the same number of dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="compositeInputsWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Image 1 and Image 2 inputs must have equal third dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="compositeInOutDimsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The Image 1 input and the output must have the same number of dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="locationWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Location input must be a two-element vector.</entry>
    <entry key="inOutNotSameFlt">Error in ''{0}'': All inputs and outputs must have the same floating-point data type.</entry>
    <entry key="rowsColsNotGT5">Error in ''{0}'': Gradient-corrected linear interpolation requires that both the number of rows and the number of columns in the input image are equal to or greater than five.</entry>
    <entry key="rowsColsNotGT3">Error in ''{0}'': Bilinear interpolation requires that both the number of rows and the number of columns in the input image are equal to or greater than three.</entry>
    <entry key="outNotMxNSepClrsSet">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Output image signal' parameter is set to 'Separate color signals,' the output must be M-by-N.</entry>
    <entry key="outNotMxNOneDimSet">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Output image signal' parameter is set to 'One multidimensional signal,' the output must be M-by-N-by-3.</entry>
    <entry key="rgbNotVectOrMat">Error in ''{0}'': The R, G, and B inputs must be vectors or matrices.</entry>
    <entry key="dimPropError">Error in ''{0}'': Port dimensions propagation error in mdlSetOutputPortDimensionInfo.</entry>
    <entry key="imageInDimGT3">Error in ''{0}'': The Image input cannot be greater than 3-D.</entry>
    <entry key="thresholdWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': Vector input to the threshold port must have two elements.</entry>
    <entry key="thresholdNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': Input to the threshold port must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="cannyEdgeFixptNotSupport">Error in ''{0}'': Fixed-point input is not supported when the 'Method' parameter is set to 'Canny'.</entry>
    <entry key="frameSizeWrongElements">Error in ''{0}'': The number of elements in the 'Frame size' parameter must be twice the number of components.</entry>
    <entry key="sampleTimeNotRealScalInh">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Sample time' parameter must either be a scalar or -1 (inherited).</entry>
    <entry key="bitsLengthWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The vector length of the 'Bits' parameter must be equal to the number of components.</entry>
    <entry key="bitsNotMult8">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Bit stream format' parameter is set to 'Planar,' the value of the 'Bits' parameter must be a multiple of eight.</entry>
    <entry key="compOrderWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The number of elements in the 'Component order in binary file' parameter must be greater than or equal to the number of components.</entry>
    <entry key="compOrderWrongVal">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Component order in binary file' parameter must contain values between one and the number of outputs.</entry>
    <entry key="compOrderNotUnique">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Bit stream format' parameter is set to 'Planar,' the 'Component order in binary file' parameter must have unique elements.</entry>
    <entry key="fourccNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': This Four Character Code (FOURCC) is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="neighWindowWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': Each dimension of the Neighborhood Window must be less than or equal to the corresponding dimension of the input matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="dtTrueDblsMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When 'Double' is selected for the 'Data type override' parameter on the Fixed-Point Tool, all input and output data types must be double.</entry>
    <entry key="dtTrueSinglesMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When 'Single' is selected for the 'Data type override' parameter on the Fixed-Point Tool, all input and output data types must be single.</entry>
    <entry key="indexOutDouble">Error in ''{0}'': The Index output can only be double precision when all other inputs and outputs are double precision.</entry>
    <entry key="indexOutSingle">Error in ''{0}'': The Index output can only be single precision when all other inputs and outputs are single precision.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutDouble">Error in ''{0}'': The Count output can only be double precision when all other inputs and outputs are double precision.</entry>
    <entry key="countOutSingle">Error in ''{0}'': The Count output data type can be set to single only if all the input/output data types are single.</entry>
    <entry key="inWordLenGT16">Error in ''{0}'': The input word length must be less than or equal to 16.</entry>
    <entry key="outWordLenGT16">Error in ''{0}'': The output word length must be less than or equal to 16.</entry>
    <entry key="inDataOutsideRange">Error in ''{0}'': The input data is outside the specified range.</entry>
    <entry key="maxInLTminOut">Error in ''{0}'': The maximum value of the input must be greater than the minimum value of the input.</entry>
    <entry key="eMetricFixpPtTypeWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The EMetric fixed-point data type attributes must match specifications in the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="histogramWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Histogram input must be a floating-point or built-in integer data type.</entry>
    <entry key="histogramIsFloat">Error in ''{0}'': When the Image input is not floating point the Histogram input cannot be floating point.</entry>
    <entry key="histogramNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The Histogram input must be a vector.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaResWrongVal">Error in ''{0}'': The value of 'Theta resolution' must be greater than zero and less than pi/2.</entry>
    <entry key="houghOutFracLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The fraction length of the Hough output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="houghOutFracLenNotZero">Error in ''{0}'': The fraction length of the Hough output must be zero.</entry>
    <entry key="houghOutWrdLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The word length of the Hough output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaOutWrdLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The word length of the Theta output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaOutFracLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The fraction length of the Theta output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoOutWrdLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The word length of the Rho output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoOutFracLenVariable">Error in ''{0}'': The fraction length of the Rho output cannot be a variable.</entry>
    <entry key="houghSampTimeNotDiscrete">Error in ''{0}'': Continuous sample times are not supported when the block outputs theta and rho values.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoResWrongVal">Error in ''{0}'': The value of 'Rho resolution' must be greater than zero and less than norm(size(BW)).</entry>
    <entry key="houghThetaMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The number of columns of the Hough output must equal the width of the Theta output.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoDimInconsistent">Error in ''{0}'': Output Rho port dimension set inconsistently. The width of the Rho output depends on the dimensions of the BW input and the 'Rho resolution' parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="sineValNotTblLookup">Error in ''{0}'': When the block input is a fixed-point data type or when ''MinMaxAndOverflow'' is specified for the model parameter MinMaxOverflowLogging, the 'Sine value computation method' parameter must be set to 'Table lookup'.</entry>
    <entry key="floatLoggingNotAllowed">Error in ''{0}'': When the block input is a floating-point data type, the model parameter MinMaxOverflowLogging and DataTypeOverride cannot be set to 'UseLocalSettings'.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaRhoWrongTypeOrLen">Error in ''{0}'': The Theta and Rho inputs must have the same signed data type with word length less than or equal to 32.</entry>
    <entry key="sineValNotTrigFcn">Error in ''{0}'': When the block input is a floating-point (nonlogged) data type, the 'Sine value computation method' parameter must be set to 'Trigonometric function'.</entry>
    <entry key="sineTblWrdLenGT32">Error in ''{0}'': The Sine Table word length must be less than or equal to 32.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaRhoWidthsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The Theta and Rho inputs must have the same width.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaRhoNotVectors">Error in ''{0}'': The Theta and Rho inputs must be vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotUint32">Error in ''{0}'': Output data types must be uint32.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotUint16">Error in ''{0}'': Output data types must be uint16.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotUint8">Error in ''{0}'': Output data types must be uint8.</entry>
    <entry key="neighDimsExceedImage">Error in ''{0}'': The neighborhood dimensions must be smaller than the input image dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="setting2Empty">Error in ''{0}'': The S-function parameter 2 derived from the "Neighborhood or structuring element" parameter on the dialog box cannot be empty.</entry>
    <entry key="setting2NotBool">Error in ''{0}'': The S-function parameter 2 derived from the "Neighborhood or structuring element" parameter on the dialog box must be Boolean.</entry>
    <entry key="neighNumEleWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The number of neighborhood elements specified by S-function parameter 2 must match the number of elements described by the neighborhood dimensions matrix specified by S-function parameter 3.</entry>
    <entry key="outputNotUnsigned">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be unsigned.</entry>
    <entry key="inputDimsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': Dimensions of all inputs must be the same.</entry>
    <entry key="inImageRowsLE4">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Method' parameter is set to 'Lucas-Kanade,' the number of rows of the input image must be greater than four.</entry>
    <entry key="inImageColsLE4">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Method' parameter is set to 'Lucas-Kanade,' the number of columns of the input image must be greater than four.</entry>
    <entry key="i1I2DimsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The I1 and I2 ports must have the same dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="codegenNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': Code generation is only supported for single-precision and double-precision inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="inDimErrorReduce">Error in ''{0}'': Unable to determine input port dimensions. Back-propagation of signal dimensions is not possible when the 'Operation' parameter is set to 'Reduce'.</entry>
    <entry key="inDimErrorExpand">Error in ''{0}'': Unable to determine input port dimensions. The current output dimensions are not valid when the 'Operation' parameter is set to 'Expand'.</entry>
    <entry key="angleNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Rotation angle input must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="colorValueWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The size of the 'Color value' parameter must be equal to three.</entry>
    <entry key="colorValueWrongMatSize">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Color value' parameter must be an M-by-3 matrix, where M is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="locationWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Location' parameter must be a two-element array or an M-by-2 matrix, where M is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="locationWrongMatSize">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Location' parameter must be an M-by-2 matrix, where M is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="imageInOutDimMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The image input and output dimensions must match.</entry>
    <entry key="selectNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Select input must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="locInWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The Location input must be a two-element vector or a 2-by-N matrix, where N is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="locInWrongMatSize">Error in ''{0}'': The Location input must be an M-by-2 matrix, where M is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="colorInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Color value input must be a scalar or an N-element vector, where N is the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="variablesInNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The Variables input must be a vector when the conversions specification is {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="variablesInNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Variables input must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="variablesWrongLength">Error in ''{0}'': The maximum number of conversion specifications in the 'Text' parameter must be one or equal to the length of the Variables input.</entry>
    <entry key="variablesWrongMatSize">Error in ''{0}'': The maximum number of conversion specifications in the 'Text' parameter must be one or equal to the number of rows of the Variables input.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Opacity input must be a scalar or a 1-by-N vector, where N is equal to the number of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': When the Image input is a floating-point data type, the Opacity input must be the same floating-point data type.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityWrongFixptType">Error in ''{0}'': When the Image input is an integer or fixed-point data type, the Opacity input must be ufix8_En7.</entry>
    <entry key="convLetterNotSupport">Error in ''{0}'': The conversions letter specified in the 'Text' parameter is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="locClrInColumnMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The Location and Color value inputs must have the same number of rows.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityLocWrongWidth">Error in ''{0}'': The length of the Opacity input must be the same as the number of rows in the Location matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityClrwrongWidth">Error in ''{0}'': The length of the Opacity input must be the same as the number of rows in the Color matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="variablesWrongColWidth">Error in ''{0}'': The number of rows of the Variables input cannot be greater than the largest of the number of rows in the Location input, the number of rows in the Color value input, and the length of the Opacity input.</entry>
    <entry key="backgroundWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Background fill value' parameter must be a scalar or it must have the same length as the third dimension of the Image input.</entry>
    <entry key="firstInputWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimension of the first input must be M-by-N or M-by-N-by-P.</entry>
    <entry key="offsetWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The Offset input must be a two-element vector.</entry>
    <entry key="outDimNotMxNOrMxNxP">Error in ''{0}'': The dimension of the output must be M-by-N or M-by-N-by-P.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidOutDim">Error in ''{0}'': The dimension of the output port is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="videoOutNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': Video output is supported on Windows and Linux platforms.</entry>
    <entry key="novipToVideoDisplayPanel">Error in ''{0}'': Error calling the MATLAB file matlabroot/toolbox/vision/vision/vipToVideoDisplayPanel.m. The file might have been removed or renamed.</entry>   
    <entry key="statNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The first argument 'stats' to the Blob Analysis S-function must be a {1, number, integer} element vector.</entry>
    <entry key="ceontroidOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Centroid output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="majAxisOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Major axis output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="minorAxisOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Minor axis output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="orientOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Orientation output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="eccOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Eccentricity output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="equDiaOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Equivalent diameter squared output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="extentOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Extent output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="perimOutWrongType">Error in ''{0}'': The Perimeter output data type must be consistent with the data type specified on the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="clrConvUnsupDataType">Error in ''{0}'': The R'G'B' to Y'CbCr, Y'CbCr to R'G'B', R'G'B' to intensity, R'G'B' to B'G'R', B'G'R' to R'G'B' and B'G'R' to intensity conversions support double-precision, single-precision, uint8, and corresponding scaled doubles data types. The other conversions support double-precision and single-precision data types.</entry>
    <entry key="inputDimScalarOrVector">Error in ''{0}'': The input {1, number, integer} must have more than one dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="inputDimsWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The input dimensions must be at least {1, number, integer}-by-{2, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="highThreshTooSmall">Error in ''{0}'': The 'high' threshold value must be greater than the 'low' threshold value.</entry>
    <entry key="numInputNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Num input must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="inlierOutNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The Inlier output must be vector.</entry>
    <entry key="videoFileOpenError">Error in ''{0}'': Could not open input video file {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="maxNumBlobsExceededMrkZero">Reported in ''{0}'': Number of found objects exceeded the specified maximum number of blobs. The remaining regions in the output label matrix will be marked using the zero (background) value.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRandomSamples">Reported in ''{0}'': Cannot find valid random samples. Increase the number of points in the Num input.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPtsNum">Reported in ''{0}'': The value of the Num input must be between {1, number, integer} and {2, number, integer}, inclusive.</entry>
    <entry key="inputValsExceedRange1">Reported in ''{0}'': At least one value exceeded the input data range [{1, number, integer}, {2, number, integer}].</entry>
    <entry key="frameRateSetToOne">Reported in ''{0}'': Video display frame rate is set to a rate slower than 1 fps. This may cause a reduction in responsiveness to user input.</entry>
    <entry key="outDataTypesNotDbl">Error in ''{0}'': Output data types must be double precision.</entry>
    <entry key="outDataTypesNotSingle">Error in ''{0}'': Output data types must be single precision.</entry>
    <entry key="inImageWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Image input must have three or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="inputIWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The I input must have two or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="rgbInWrongDims">Error in ''{0}'': The R, G, and B inputs must have two or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="cirInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Clr input must have two or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="outImageWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Image output must have three or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="outputIWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The I output must have two or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="rgbOutWrongDims">Error in ''{0}'': The R, G, and B outputs must have two or fewer dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoOutWidthWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the Rho output must equal the number of rows of the Hough output.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaOutWidthWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the Theta output must equal the number of columns of the Hough output.</entry>
    <entry key="overlapRowsWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The number of rows of the 'Overlap' parameter must be a nonnegative integer with a value less than the height of the block.</entry>
    <entry key="overlapColsWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The number of columns of the 'Overlap' parameter must be a nonnegative integer with a value less than the width of the block.</entry>
    <entry key="blockHeightWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The height of the block must be less than or equal to the number of rows in the image input.</entry>
    <entry key="blockWidthWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the block must be less than or equal to the number of columns in the image input.</entry>
    <entry key="pixelUpperLimitWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The upper limit of the input pixel range must be greater than the lower limit.</entry>
    <entry key="settingNotPositive">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} parameter must be positive.</entry>
    <entry key="sumPixSatTooBig">Error in ''{0}'': The sum of the values in the 'Percentages of pixels to saturate' parameter must be less than 100.</entry>
    <entry key="bitsNotMultiple8">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Bits' parameter must be a multiple of eight.</entry>
    <entry key="compOrderForPackedWrong">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Bit stream format' parameter is set to 'Packed,' the number of elements of the 'Component order in binary file' parameter must be greater than or equal to the number of components.</entry>
    <entry key="compOrderForPlanarWrong">Error in ''{0}'': When the 'Bit stream format' parameter is set to 'Planar,' the number of elements of the 'Component order in binary file' parameter must be equal to the number of components.</entry>
    <entry key="dimRatioCompOrderMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The ratio of port dimensions do not match the specified component order.</entry>
    <entry key="dimRatioFourCCMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The ratio of the port dimensions do not match the required ratios for the specified FOURCC.</entry>
    <entry key="bitsExceedInputSize">Error in ''{0}'': Specified bits must be less than or equal to the input size.</entry>
    <entry key="inputBytesWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The input must be one, two, or four bytes long.</entry>
    <entry key="roiVectorWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The ROI input must be a vector with four elements.</entry>
    <entry key="outTypeNotSgnCpxMotVec">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be signed for complex motion vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="outTypeNotSigMgSqMotVec">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be unsigned for magnitude-squared motion vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="wordLenRangeError">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} word length must be a positive integer between {2, number, integer} and 128, inclusive.</entry>
    <entry key="normalizeOutNotForFixpt">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Normalized output' parameter only applies to floating-point input data types.</entry>
    <entry key="minBlobAreaGTMaxBlobArea">Error in ''{0}'': The minimum blob area must be less than or equal to the maximum blob area.</entry>
    <entry key="inputNotFixptSettingFixpt">Error in ''{0}'': The input must be a fixed-point data type when you specify a fixed-point output data type in the block dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="outDataTypeSettingMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must match the output data type specified on the block dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="grayThreshTypesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': Input I, output Th, and output EMetric must all be double, all single, or all fixed point.</entry>
    <entry key="imageHistTypesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The Image and Histogram data types should be the same when the input is floating point.</entry>
    <entry key="optFlowOutTypeNotFloat">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be double precision or single precision for the Horn-Schunck and  Lucas-Kanade (Gaussian Derivative) methods.</entry>
    <entry key="fixPtTooLongForCodeGen">Error in ''{0}'': Fixed-point data types with word lengths up to 16 bits are supported in code generation.</entry>
    <entry key="fixPtWdLenGT32Bits">Error in ''{0}'': Fixed-point data types with word lengths up to 32 bits are supported.</entry>
    <entry key="maxOffsetTooLarge">Error in ''{0}'': The value specified for the 'Maximum offset' parameter results in output image dimensions that exceed INTMAX number of pixels.</entry>
    <entry key="numColorsChanged">Error in ''{0}'': The number of colors in the image cannot be changed.</entry>
    <entry key="videoBandsSzChanged">Error in ''{0}'': The number of video bands cannot change size during simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="compNotInCompOrder">Error in ''{0}'': Each of the components identified in the 'Number of input components' parameter must be included in the value of the 'Component order in binary file' parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="smoothFltWronNumElem">Error in ''{0}'': The number of coefficients for the separable smoothing filter must be odd and must be at least 3.</entry>
    <entry key="outMetricTooSmall">Error in ''{0}'': The dimension of the Output metric signal cannot be less than {1, number, integer}-by-{2, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="inDataTypeNotFloatInt8Or16OrFixpt">Error in ''{0}'': The input data type must be double precision, single precision, Boolean, int8, uint8, int16, uint16, or any fixed-point data type with word length less than or equal to 16. The scaled doubles version of these data types are also supported.</entry>
    <entry key="outDataTypeNotFloatInt8Or16OrFixpt">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type must be double precision, single precision, Boolean, int8, uint8, int16, uint16, or any fixed-point data type with word length less than or equal to 16. The scaled doubles version of these data types are also supported.</entry>
    <entry key="imgInOutFltTypesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': When the Image input has a floating-point data type, the output must have the same data type.</entry>
    <entry key="roiFltTypeImgInNotFlt">Error in ''{0}'': When the ROI input has a floating-point data type, the Image input must have a floating-point data type.</entry>
    <entry key="roiFltTypeOutNotFlt">Error in ''{0}'': When the ROI input has a floating-point data type, the output must have a floating-point data type.</entry>
    <entry key="imgInOutTypesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type and the Image input data type must be the same.</entry>
    <entry key="imgInOutSgnsDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The output data type and the Image input data type must have the same signedness.</entry>
    <entry key="pts1OrPts2TooSmall">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts1 and Pts2 inputs must have at least {1, number, integer} points.</entry>
    <entry key="inlierOutSzTooSmall">Error in ''{0}'': The Inlier output must have at least {1, number, integer} elements.</entry>
    <entry key="vipDrawNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes and the Pts input has {3, number, integer} shapes. The {4} must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="vipDrawNotSclOrVec">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes and the Pts input has {3, number, integer} shapes. The {4} must be either a scalar providing one color for all shapes, or a {5, number, integer}-element vector providing one color for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="vipDarwNotVector">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes and the Pts input has {3, number, integer} shapes. The {4} must be a {5, number, integer}-element vector.</entry>
    <entry key="vipDrawNotVecOrMat">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes and the Pts input has {3, number, integer} shapes. The {4} must be either a {5, number, integer}-element vector providing one color for all shapes,  or a {6, number, integer}-by-{7, number, integer} matrix providing one color for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="vipDrawNumClrPlaneNumShape">Error in ''{0}'': The number of color planes in input image and the number of shapes in Pts input do not match.</entry>    
    <entry key="opacityNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input has 1 shape. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityNotSclOrVec">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input has {1, number, integer} shapes. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter must be either a scalar value for all shapes, or a {2, number, integer}-element vector providing one value for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityNotSclOrVecForMat">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} is a {2, number, integer}-by-{3, number, integer} matrix. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter must be either a scalar value for all shapes, or a {4, number, integer}-element vector providing one value for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="forNumClrPlanesNotScalar">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter has {3, number, integer} elements. The {4} must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="forNumClrPlanesNotScOrVec">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter has {3, number, integer} elements. The {4} must be either a scalar providing one color for all shapes, or a {5, number, integer}-element vector providing one color for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="forNumClrPlanesNotVecOrMat">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes. The 'Opacity factor(s)' parameter has {3, number, integer} elements. The {4} must be either a {5, number, integer}-element vector providing one color for all shapes,  or a {6, number, integer}-by-{7, number, integer} matrix providing one color for each shape.</entry>
    <entry key="img2SettingDimMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} parameter is a matrix, its dimensions must match the dimensions of the Image2 input.</entry>
    <entry key="img2SignalDimMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} signal is a matrix, its dimensions must match the dimensions of the Image2 input.</entry>
    <entry key="inputNotVectOrMat">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input must be a vector or a matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="outputOneDim">Error in ''{0}'': Output {1, number, integer} must have more than one dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="strSettingEmpty">Error in ''{0}'': Parameter {1, number, integer} must be a non-empty character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="numClrEleNotMult">Error in ''{0}'': The number of elements of the Color input must be a multiple of {1, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="clrNotNStrings">Error in ''{0}'': The Color input or 'Color value' parameter must be a {1, number, integer}-element vector or an M-by-{2, number, integer} matrix, where M is the number of text character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="clrLenNotColsLoc">Error in ''{0}'': The 'Color value' parameter length must be the same as the number of points in the Location matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="rgbSizesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The R, G, and B inputs must have the same size.</entry>
    <entry key="backPropDimsFailed">Error in ''{0}'': Unable to determine input port dimensions based on output port dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="inputIDimsNotGTTemp">Error in ''{0}'': All the dimensions of the I input must be greater than or equal to all the dimensions of the Template input.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsBothNotFloat">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} input is floating point, the {2} input must also be floating point.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsBothNotBool">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} input is Boolean, the {2} input must also be Boolean.</entry>
    <entry key="outDataTypWrongInBool">Error in ''{0}'': When inputs are Boolean, the output data type cannot be set to 'Same as first input'.</entry>
    <entry key="accDataTypWrongInBool">Error in ''{0}'': When inputs are Boolean, the Accumulator data type cannot be set to 'Same as first input'.</entry>
    <entry key="dimIOrTempNotSet">Error in ''{0}'': Unable to determine output dimensions. The dimensions of the I and Template inputs must be set.</entry>
    <entry key="numObjsExceedsDataMrkZero">Reported in ''{0}'': The number of found objects exceeds the output data range. The remaining regions will be marked using the zero (background) value.</entry>
    <entry key="numObjsExceedsDataMrkMax">Reported in ''{0}'': The number of found objects exceeds the output data range. The remaining regions will be marked using the maximum value of the output data type.</entry>
    <entry key="forClrPlanesNotVecMat">Error in ''{0}'': The {1} input has {2, number, integer} color planes. The {3} must be either a {4, number, integer}-element vector, or a {5, number, integer}-by-N matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="outputDimsTooSmall">Error in ''{0}'': The output dimensions must be at least {1, number, integer}-by-{2, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="gradSettingFixPtMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': The back-propagated gradient port fixed-point data type attributes must match specifications in the block mask.</entry>
    <entry key="freeTypeInitFailed">Error in ''{0}'': FreeType library failed to initialize ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="fontFormatUnsupport">Error in ''{0}'': Font file format unsupported by FreeType library.</entry>
    <entry key="fontSizeUnsupport">Error in ''{0}'': Font file size unsupported by FreeType library.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsDataTypeMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} input has a {2} data type, the {3} input must have a {4} data type.</entry>
    <entry key="inptOutptDataTypeMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When the {1} input has a {2} data type, the output must have a {3} data type.</entry>
    <entry key="outptInptDataTypeMismatch">Error in ''{0}'': When the output has a {1} data type, the {2} input must have a {3} data type.</entry>
    <entry key="fontLoadFailure">Error in ''{0}'': FreeType library font file could not be loaded ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="fontPartialLoadFailure">Error in ''{0}'': The FreeType library could not load font bitmaps for all characters ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="numClrPlanesChanged">Error in ''{0}'': You cannot change the number of color planes in the image during simulation. The number of color planes is the third dimension of the image input.</entry>
    <entry key="rowsColsOutZero">Error in ''{0}'': The number of rows and the number of columns in the output cannot be zero. Consider changing the 'Resize factor' parameter to larger values.</entry>
    <entry key="pts1AndPts2SizesDiffer">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts1 and Pts2 inputs must have the same size.</entry>
    <entry key="allowVarSizeNotSelected">Error in ''{0}'': The input must be a fixed-size signal. To support variable-size input signals, the 'Allow variable-size signal input' check box must be selected.</entry>
    <entry key="imageAndTFormSameType">Error in ''{0}'': The Image input, TForm input and Image output must have the same data type.</entry>
    <entry key="imageTFormAndROISameType">Error in ''{0}'': When the ROI input has a floating-point data type, the Image input, TForm input, ROI input and Image output must have the same data type.</entry>
    <entry key="imgSmallerThanBlkSize">Error in ''{0}'': The size of each dimension of the Image input must be greater than or equal to the corresponding dimensions specified by the 'Block size' parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="transToInfinity">Error in ''{0}'': A portion of the input image was transformed to the location at infinity. Only transformation matrices that do not transform any part of the image to infinity are supported.</entry>
    <entry key="iterCountNotSame">Error in ''{0}'': The number of steps computed for blocks to traverse entire inputs must be the same for all inputs. Resize the inputs or modify block sizes and overlap sizes as needed.</entry>
    <entry key="wbfMinInputSize">Error in ''{0}'': The minimum number of input rows must be {1, number, integer}, and the minimum number of input columns must be {2, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="opacityFactorLT0GT1">Error in ''{0}'': The opacity factor must be between 0 and 1, inclusive.</entry>
    <entry key="angleInfOrNaN">Error in ''{0}'': The Angle input cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="videoFileOpenForWriteError">Error in ''{0}'': Could not open video file {1} for writing.</entry>
    <entry key="allInportsScDoubles">Error in ''{0}'': If any input port data type is scaled doubles, then all input port data types must be scaled doubles.</entry>
    <entry key="inputScDblOutputDblScDblBool">Error in ''{0}'': If the input port data type is scaled doubles, the output port data type must be boolean or double or scaled doubles.</entry>
    <entry key="outputScDblInputDblScDblBool">Error in ''{0}'': If the output port data type is scaled doubles, the input port data type must be boolean or double or scaled doubles.</entry>
    <entry key="rgbCurInputDimsWrong">Error in ''{0}'': All inputs must have same current dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="varSizeNotSupportedAutomaticMode">Error in ''{0}'': varSizeNotSupportedAutomaticMode internal error</entry>
    <entry key="numPlanesNot3for3dInput">Error in ''{0}'': When the input is a 3-D array, the number of input planes must be 3.</entry>
    <entry key="rhoThetaOutportForVarS">Error in ''{0}'': When the input is a variable-size signal,  the 'Output theta and rho values' checkbox must not be selected.</entry>
    <entry key="pts1Pts2NotMx2">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts1 and Pts2 inputs must be M-by-2 matrices.</entry>
    <entry key="rectPtsInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input must be an M-by-4 matrix. Each row specifies a different rectangle and is of the form [x y width height].</entry>
    <entry key="polyLnPtsInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input must be an M-by-2L matrix. Each row specifies a different polyline with points connected in consecutive order, and is of the form [x1 y1 x2 y2 ... xL yL].</entry>
    <entry key="polygonPtsInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input must be an M-by-2L matrix. Each row specifies a different polygon with points connected in consecutive order, and is of the form [x1 y1 x2 y2 ... xL yL].</entry>
    <entry key="cirPtsInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input must be an M-by-3 matrix. Each row specifies a different circle and is of the form [x y radius].</entry>
    <entry key="cntrPtsInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input must be an M-by-2 matrix. Each row specifies a different center and is of the form [x y].</entry>
    <entry key="ptsInputInvalidSize">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input size is not valid.</entry>    
    <entry key="roiInWrongDim">Error in ''{0}'': The ROI input must be a four-element vector and of the form [x y width height].</entry>
    <entry key="forDrawPtsDimsWrong">Error in ''{0}'': The Pts input has {1, number, integer} shapes. The {2} must be either a {3, number, integer}-element vector or a {4, number, integer}-by-N matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="shearInfOrNaN">Error in ''{0}'': The shear values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="offsetInfOrNaN">Error in ''{0}'': The offset values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="roiInfOrNaN">Error in ''{0}'': The ROI values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="locationInfOrNaN">Error in ''{0}'': The Location values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="startPtsWrongSize">Error in ''{0}'': The Start points input must be a two element vector.</entry>
    <entry key="maxNumBlobsExceeded">Error in ''{0}'': Number of found objects exceeded the specified maximum number of blobs.</entry>
    <entry key="inputNotMxN">Error in ''{0}'': The input must be an M-by-N matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="mapBlkLineWidth">Line width</entry>
    <entry key="image2OutsideImage1">Error in ''{0}'': The Image 2 input is outside the boundaries of the Image 1 input.</entry>
    <entry key="inputValsExceedRange">Error in ''{0}'': At least one value exceeded the input data range.</entry>
    <entry key="toVideoDisplayStartWarning">Error in ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="toVideoDisplayStartError">Error in ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="toVideoDisplayUpdateError">Error in ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="outColsNotFour">Error in ''{0}'': The output must have four columns.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaRhoAndOutDimsDiffer2">Error in ''{0}'': The width of the Theta and Rho inputs must be the same as the number of rows of the output.</entry>
    <entry key="fixptVarSize">Error in ''{0}'': Image must be double or single to process variable-size input.</entry>
    <entry key="hwBitsPerCharNot8">Error in ''{0}'': "char", in Production hardware settings in Hardware Implementation pane of Configuration Parameters dialog box, must be defined to be 8 bit long.</entry>
    <entry key="videoViewerDescription">Display binary, intensity, or RGB images or video streams.</entry>
    <entry key="pointCloudViewerDescription">Display Point Clouds.</entry>
    <entry key="trueDoubleSingleUnsupported">Error in ''{0}'': <![CDATA[This block does not support double or single-precision data types. These types may be introduced by the 'Data type override' parameter in the Fixed-Point Tool.
    <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
        <action type="fixit">
            <cmd>fxptui.setDTOValueOnModel(gcs,'ScaledDouble')</cmd>
            <txt>To observe floating-point behavior, override data types with Scaled doubles.</txt>
        </action>
        <action type="fixit">
            <cmd>fxptui.setDTOValueOnModel(gcs,'ForceOff')</cmd>
            <txt>Remove data type override from the model.</txt>
        </action>   
      </actions>]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="inputsMustBeMxNx3">Input data to block {0} must be a vector, a MxN matrix, or a MxNx3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="pointCloudInputsMustBeMxNx3">Input data to block {0} must be a vector, a Mx3 matrix, or a MxNx3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="colormapAndValueRangeIgnored">Colormap and value range information is used only when displaying intensity images or video.</entry>
    <entry key="colormapIgnored">Colormap information is used only when displaying intensity images or video.</entry>
    <entry key="valueRangeIgnored">Value range information is used only when displaying intensity images or video.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsMustBe2D">Input data to R, G, or B port of block {0} must be a vector or a MxN matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidColormapParam">Colormap must be an Nx3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataRangeParam">Maximum input value must be greater than Minimum input value.</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedParam">The {0} is undefined.</entry>
    <entry key="nonNumericParam">The {0} must be a numeric value.</entry>
    <entry key="nonRealParam">The {0} must be real valued.</entry>
    <entry key="infOrNaNParam">The {0} cannot be NaN or Inf.</entry>
    <entry key="sparseParam">The {0} cannot be a sparse matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="nonIntegerParam">The {0} must be integer(s).</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRangeParam">The {0} has invalid value(s).</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDimenParam">The {0} has invalid dimensionality.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedDataType">Fixed-point and custom data types are not currently supported by the Video Viewer block</entry>
    <entry key="ImagePortsMultidimensionalSignal_CB" translate="false">One multidimensional signal</entry>
    <entry key="ImagePortsSeparateSignals_CB" translate="false">separate color signals</entry>
    <entry key="PointCloudLocationPort_CB">Location Port</entry>
    <entry key="PointCloudColorPort_CB">Location and Color Port</entry>
    <entry key="PointCloudIntensityPort_CB">Location and Intensity Port</entry>
    <entry key="pointCloudIntensityPortExportWarning">The block port option is set to ''{0}'' for Point Cloud Viewer Block ''{1}''. This port option does not exist prior to the R2025a release. As a result, the port option is set to ''{2}'' in the exported model.</entry>
    <entry key="InputRGB_CB" translate="false">RGB</entry>
    <entry key="InputIntensity_CB" translate="false">Intensity</entry>
    <entry key="InputObsolete_CB" translate="false">Obsolete</entry>
    <entry key="InputObsolete7b_CB" translate="false">Obsolete7b</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMagnificationSetting" translate="false">Magnification must be a positive scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="VideoViewerLicenseFailed">Video Viewer requires a Computer Vision Toolbox license.</entry>
	<entry key="simulinkImageInvalidColorValue">The color format ''{0}'' is not compatible with the Video Viewer. Either use 'RGB', 'Intensity', or 'BGR' color formats.</entry>
	<entry key="simulinkImageInvalidColorConversionValue">The color format input to ''{0}'' is not compatible with this conversion.</entry>
	<entry key="simulinkImageInvalidOrientationValue">The input image orientation must be Column Major.</entry>
	<entry key="colorspaceSimulinkImageInvalidOrientationValue">Change the input image orientation to ''{0}'' to column-major.</entry>
    <entry key="imageInportMinSizeTwo">Error in ''{0}'': The Image input dimensions must be at least 2-by-2 for 'Valid' output size.</entry>
    <!--svipvideotowks-->
    <entry key="numInputsGreaterThanOne">Error in ''{0}'': Number of inputs should be an integer >= 1.</entry>
    <entry key="paramScalarInteger">Error in ''{0}'': Limit data points to last: parameter should be a scalar integer >= 1.</entry>
    <entry key="paramGreaterThanOne">Error in ''{0}'': Limit data points to last: parameter should be an integer >= 1.</entry>
    <entry key="decimationFactorGrThanOne">Error in ''{0}'': Decimation factor should be an integer >= 1.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidVariableName">Error in ''{0}'': Invalid MATLAB variable name specified.</entry>
    <entry key="fixedPointNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': This fixed-point word length is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="memoryAllocError">Error in ''{0}'': Memory allocation error.</entry>
    <entry key="memoryAllocFailed">Error in ''{0}'': Memory allocation failed.</entry>
    <entry key="couldNotCreateVarWS">Error in ''{0}'': Could not create variable in MATLAB workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="when3DInput">Error in ''{0}'': When input is 3-D, the parameter 'Number of inputs' must be 1</entry>
    <!--svipvideofromwks-->
    <entry key="signal3Dor4D">Error in ''{0}'': Signal should be either 3-D or 4-D.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidMovieStructure">Error in ''{0}'': Invalid movie structure format specified. cdata field could not be found.</entry>
    <entry key="colormapDataNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': Colormap data is not supported by this block.</entry>
    <entry key="dataTypeNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': The data type of the signal specified not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="sampleMustBePositiveScalar">Error in ''{0}'': Sample time must be a positive scalar or -1.</entry>
    <entry key="onlySupports32CG">Error in ''{0}'': This block only supports fixed-point data type with word length of 32 bits or less in code generation.</entry>
    <entry key="errorFixedDTReg">Error in ''{0}'': Error occurred during fixed-point data type registration.</entry>
    <entry key="scaledDoubleNotSupported">Error in ''{0}'': Scaled double data type is not supported.</entry>
    <!--svipshear-->
    <entry key="backgroundFillScalar">Error in ''{0}'': Background fill value(s) must be scalar or same length as the third dimension of input image</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeAllocFailed">Error in ''{0}'': Run time parameter allocation failed</entry>    
    <entry key="vectorShearValInput">Error in ''{0}'': A vector of size 2 is expected for the 'shear values' input port.</entry>
    <entry key="backPropOutSpec">Error in ''{0}'': Back-propagated output port fixed-point data type attributes do not match specifications in block mask.</entry>
    <!--svipindexgenol-->
    <entry key="traverseDirection" note="This message not visible on block mask or UI">Error in ''{0}'': Traverse direction must be 1 or 2.</entry>
    <entry key="needAssignPorts" note="This message not visible on block mask or UI">Error in ''{0}'': The value of the needAssignPorts input must be 0 or 1 .</entry>
    <entry key="outputOnlyStartVal" note="This message not visible on block mask or UI">Error in ''{0}'': The output index start value must be 0 or 1.</entry>
    <!--svipblockprociter-->
    <entry key="paramTwoElement">Error in ''{0}'': Parameter must be a two element vector.</entry>    
    <entry key="cellArrayAtleastOne">Error in ''{0}'': Cell array must have at least one element.</entry>    
    <entry key="blockSizeAtleastOne">Error in ''{0}'': Block size must be at least 1 in each dimension.</entry>    
    <entry key="overlapSizeAtleast0">Error in ''{0}'': Overlap size must be at least 0 in each dimension.</entry>    
    <entry key="blockSizeGrOverlapSize">Error in ''{0}'': Block size must be greater than the overlap size.</entry>   
    <!--sviptextrender-->    
    <entry key="fltptVariablesMayNotBeSupported">Warning in ''{0}'': The generated code contains a fixed-point input from the image port and a floating-point data type from the Variables port. You must check if the embedded target supports both fixed-point and floating-point datatypes.</entry> 
    <entry key="selectValueOutOfRangeNewCoords">Error in ''{0}'': Input to the Select port must be in the range [1, Number of text strings].</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedTargetDevice">Error in ''{0}'': This block generates code only for the host target. You must set the target hardware device type to match the host.</entry>
    <entry key="TextPointCloudVisualization" note="">Video visualization</entry>
    <entry key="PointCloudLabel" note="">Point Cloud</entry>



      <!-- Axes Panel -->
    <entry key="XLimits">XLimits</entry>
    <entry key="YLimits">YLimits</entry>
    <entry key="ZLimits">ZLimits</entry>
    <entry key="MarkerSize">Marker Size</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAxesLimits">The Axes Limits must be a numeric vector of two elements "min, max"</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMarkerSize">The Marker Size must be a positive scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MenuPCInfo"><![CDATA[Point Cloud &Information]]></entry>
    <entry key="PointCloudSampleTimeConflict">All inputs to the Point Cloud visual must have the same sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLocation">Invalid Location Input</entry>
    <entry key="invalidColor">Invalid Color Input</entry>
    <entry key="TTXLimits">xmin, xmax</entry>
    <entry key="TTYLimits">ymin, ymax</entry>
    <entry key="TTZLimits">zmin, zmax</entry>
    <entry key="TTMarkerSize">Set Marker Size</entry>
    <entry key="inport">Input Port</entry>
    <entry key="colormapValue">Color Map Value</entry>
    <entry key="specRange">Specify Range</entry>
    <entry key="minInputVal">Minimum Input Value</entry>
    <entry key="maxInputVal">Maximum Input Value</entry>
    <entry key="figPos">Figure Position </entry>
    <entry key="figSettings">Figure Settings Value </entry>
    <entry key="AxisZoom">Axis Zoom </entry>
    <entry key="OpenAtMdlStart">Open at Model Start</entry>
    <entry key="trueSizedOnce">True Sized Once</entry>
    <entry key="useColorMap">Use Color Map </entry>
      
  </message>
</rsccat>

