<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="vision" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="invalidBoxesInTable">The size of bounding box data must be M-by-4, M-by-5, or M-by-9, where M is the number of boxes in each table element. The column in the training data table that contains the bounding boxes must be a cell array.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidLabelsInTable">Label data must be an M-by-1 categorical array, where M specifies the number of labels in a row. The column in the training data table that contains the labels must be a cell array.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidNumLabelsInTable">The number of bounding boxes does not equal the number of labels in row {0,number,integer} of the training data table. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')&quot;&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidMixOfTables">Multiple tables must be in the same format. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')&quot;&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidDataInTableColumn">Invalid data in column {1} of input table {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidDataInTableRow">Invalid data in row {1} of input table {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidDataInTable">Invalid bounding boxes found in input table {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidMixOfBoxesInTable">The size of all bounding box matrices contained in the input tables must be the same. The size of each matrix must be M-by-4, M-by-5, or M-by-9, where M is the number of boxes in each table element. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')&quot;&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidImageNumberInBlockSet">The maximum image number in the BlockLocations property must not exceed the number of rows ({0}) in the boxLabels table input. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')&quot;&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBoxFormatForBlockSet">The bounding boxes must be M-by-4 or M-by-5 when blockLocationSet is provided as an input. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')&quot;&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidNDBlockOrigin">Invalid BlockOrigin in the blockLocationSet input. n-D BlockOrigin values in the blockLocationSet are not supported in boxLabelDatastore.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
