<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="vision" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>

        <entry key="mustBeDetectorName">Input object keypoint detector name must be a valid pretrained HRNet deep learning network.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidInputDimensionality">Dimension of input data of numeric type cannot exceed 4.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidInferenceInput">Input must be either a numeric array or a datastore.</entry>
        <entry key="thresholdMustBeScalar">Threshold value must be scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidKeypointClasses">Invalid keypoint classes. Specify keypoint classes as a string array, a cell array of character vectors, or a categorical array.</entry>
        <entry key="nonUniqueKeypointClasses">Keypoint classes must be unique.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidInputSize">Height and width of input image must be divisible by 32.</entry>
        <entry key="mustBeImageandBBox">ImageDatastore object must have images and bounding boxes.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBBoxDimension">Bounding box must be a 4-element vector.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBBoxSize">Bounding box height and width must be less than or equal to the respective height and width of the image.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidConnections">Keypoint connections must be a matrix of size J-by-2 where each row represents a pair of Keypoint class indices.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidSizeKeypointsScoresValidity">The number of keypoints, scores, and validity flags must match the number of Keypoint classes.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidObjectCount">The number of objects in the scores, keypoints, and validity flag must be the same.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidKeypoints">The KeyPoints must be two-dimensional.</entry>
        <entry key="emptyBboxes">Bounding boxes value must not be empty.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidPretrainedNetwork">Specify a valid pretrained network as input.</entry>
        <entry key="requiresKeypointclasses">Keypoint classes must be specified in order to configure the network for transfer learning.</entry>
        <entry key="loadHRNETMATFileDoesNotExist">MAT-file does not exist.</entry>
        <entry key="loadHRNETNoHRNetObjects">No object of class hrnetObjectKeypointDetector in MAT-file.</entry>
        <entry key="loadHRNETTooManyHRNetObjects">Specified MAT-file must contain only one hrnetObjectKeypointDetector object.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidInputImage">Input image must be single RGB image.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidKeypointConnectionIndices">The indices of the keypoint connections must be less than the total number of keypoint classes.</entry>
        <entry key="datastore">Datastore must return cell array on the read method with 2 cell, first cell for image and second for bounding box.</entry>

        <!-- For trainHRNetObjectKeypointDetector -->
        <entry key="trainingHeader">Training a HRNet Object Keypoint Detector for the following keypoint classes:</entry>
        <entry key="noGPUFound">Supported GPU not found. Update the 'ExecutionEnvironment' on trainingOptions to 'cpu'. Or, to automatically determine if a GPU is available, use 'auto'.</entry>
        <entry key="trainingFooter">Keypoint detector training complete.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidChannelImage">The number of channels in training images and inputSize must be same.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidDatastore">The trainingData must either be a valid transformed or combined datastore.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidKeypointSize">The number of keypoints must be N-by-2 or N-by-3 where N is number of keypoint classes.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidVisibilityFlag">Visibility must be either zero or one.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidKeypointCount">The number of keypoints must be equal to number of keypoint classes.</entry>
        <entry key="bboxesCanNotBeZero">Bounding box must be positive.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidbboxesHeightWidth">Height and width of bounding box can not be unit size.</entry>
        <entry key="NumOfbboxesAndKeypointMustBeSame">Number of keypoints set and bounding box must be same.</entry>
        <entry key="computingInputNormalization">Computing Input Normalization Statistics.</entry>

        <!-- Codegen -->
        <entry key="imageSizeConstant">The input image to the 'detect' method must be fixed-size for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="ignoreInputArg">Code generation does not support the argument ''{1}'' passed to ''{0}'' method. This argument will be ignored.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
