<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="vision" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
      <!-- Network Creation -->
      <entry key="duplicateClassNames">The classNames must be unique.</entry>
      <entry key="incorrectClassNameType">The classNames must be one of the following types: cell array of char vectors, string array, or a categorical array.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidImageInput">The input to segmentObjects must be a grayscale or RGB image, or a batch of images, or a datastore returning images.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidFeatureLayer">The feature layer must produce an array with only one non-singleton dimension.</entry>
      <entry key="incorrectInputSize">The input size must be 1x3 vector. The first two elements should be multiples of 32 and the third element should be equal to 3.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidClassificationNetwork">The classification network must be a dlnetwork.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidClassificationNetworkMissingFC">The classification network must be a dlnetwork with a fully-connected layer.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNetwork">The input network must have a fully-connected, global average pooling, or convolutional layer that produces an array with only one non-singleton dimension.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNormalizationStatisticsStruct">The NormalizationStatistics structure must contain the following fields: Mean and StandardDeviation.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNormalizationStatisticsSize">The 'Mean' and 'StandardDeviation' field values of the NormalizationStatistics structure must be a vector of size [1 {0}].</entry>

      <!-- Reidentification Network Verbose -->
      <entry key="verboseHeaderExtraction">Running Reidentification network</entry>
      <entry key="verboseProgressTxt">* Processed {0} images.</entry>
      <entry key="verboseFooter">Finished processing images.</entry>
      
      <!-- Datastore input -->
      <entry key="invalidDatastore">The trainingData must be a valid datastore.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidImageDatastore">The trainingData imageDatastore must have labels.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNumberOfLabels">The trainingData must have a label for every image file.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidLabelCategories">The ground truth labels in the trainingData input must have the same categories as the ClassNames on the reidentificationNetwork object.</entry>

      <!-- Training -->
      <entry key="noGPUFound">Supported GPU not found. Update the 'ExecutionEnvironment' on trainingOptions to 'cpu'. Or, to automatically determine if a GPU is available, use 'auto'.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidReIDNetwork">Invalid reidentification network. The network must be an object of type reidentificationNetwork. Please use the reidentificationNetwork() function to create the network.</entry>

      <!-- Evaluation Metrics -->
      <entry key="invalidMetricsLabelEmpty">The input labels must not be empty.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidMetricsLabelType">The input labels must be a string array, a cell array of character vectors, or a categorical array.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidRanks">Ranks must not have any repeating values.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidRankType">Rank must be one or more numerical values from 1 to the total number of classes or specified as 'all'.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNuminstances">There must be at least two instances of every object to evaluate reidentification metrics.</entry>

      <!-- Evaluation Metrics Plot -->
      <entry key="invalidLineColorRange">RGB triplets of type 'single' or 'double' must be specified with values in the range [0,1].</entry>
      <entry key="invalidLineColorHex">LineColor value must not be hexadecimal.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNumLineColors">The number of colors specified must be scalar or match the number of classes in the reidentificationMetrics object.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidLineColorNotScalar">LineColor must be a scalar string/char array or a 1-by-3 RGB triplet for plotType 'cmc' and 'precision-recall'.</entry>

      <!-- Evaluation Metrics Verbose -->
      <entry key="verboseHeader">Configuring reidentification metrics</entry>
      <entry key="verboseSetQueries">* Setting all query images.</entry>
      <entry key="verboseBuildGallerySets">* Building gallery sets.</entry>
      <entry key="verboseMetricCalculation">Calculating {0} metric</entry>
      <entry key="verboseClassMetricCalculation">* Calculating {0} metric for class {1}.</entry>
      <entry key="verboseFinalizeTxt">* Aggregating and finalizing the metrics.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
