<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="instrument">
  <message>
    <!-- visadevlist / visadev -->
    <entry key="unsupportedPlatform">visadevlist, visadevfind, and visadev are not supported on Linux.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTimeout">Timeout must be greater than or equal to 2.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindResourcesDefaultTimeout">Unable to find any VISA resources during the default timeout period of {0} seconds. Specify a larger "Timeout" value or open the vendor's control software to search for available VISA resources.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToSetTimeoutValue">Unable to set the timeout value to {0}. Setting timeout to {1} instead.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindResources">Unable to find any VISA resources during the specified timeout period. Open the vendor's control software to search for available VISA resources.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindPreferredVISA">Unable to find VISA installations. &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:instrument.internal.supportPackageInstaller&quot;&gt;Open the Support Package Installer&lt;/a&gt; to install VISA. </entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindEnabledVISA">Unable to find any enabled VISA installations. Open the vendor's control software and enable an installation using the Conflict Manager.</entry>
    <entry key="timeoutExpiredEnumeration">Unable to find any resources during the specified timeout period.</entry>
    <entry key="timeoutExpiredPartialList">Timeout expired while searching for available resources.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToDetermineInterfaceType">Resource string is invalid or resource was not found.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedFlowControlType">Combined hardware and software control is not supported. Supported flow control modes are "none", "software", and "hardware".</entry>
    <entry key="resourceBusy">The VISA library is unable to access this resource because it is already in use. </entry>
    <entry key="resourceUnavailable">The VISA library is unable to access this resource. </entry>
    <entry key="noSave">Saving VISA resource objects to a MAT-file is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="noLoad">Loading VISA resource objects from a MAT-file is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToSetPropertyValue">The value of {0} property was set to {1} because this device does not support setting it to {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="multipleIdenticalResources">Creating a second device for the {0} resource is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="terminatorTimeout">The specified terminator was not read before the timeout period expired.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToEstablishPreferredVISAOnMac">Multiple VISA installations are available. To use one of them, select &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:visalib.utility.setPreferredVisaMacNI&quot;&gt;NI VISA&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:visalib.utility.setPreferredVisaMacRS&quot;&gt;RS VISA&lt;/a&gt;. </entry>  
    <entry key="setOnlyOnTheMac">This preference is only used on macOS. For other platforms, set the preferred VISA using the vendor's control software.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidVisaForMac">{0} is not a supported VISA vendor on macOS. Valid vendor settings include "NI" and "RS".</entry>
    <entry key="visaStatusUnavailableAsConfigured">Unable to determine status for {0} resource in the current configuration.</entry>    
    <entry key="niVisaSelectedForTheMac">The preferred VISA on macOS is set to "NI".</entry>
    <entry key="rsVisaSelectedForTheMac">The preferred VISA on macOS is set to "RS".</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyNotSupportedForVISA">The {0} property is no longer supported for visadev objects.</entry>
    <entry key="MethodNotSupportedForVISA">The {0} method is no longer supported for visadev objects.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToReadDataVISADriver">Failed to read data from the instrument due to a driver error.</entry>
    <entry key="visadevWorkaroundUnsupported">Method visadevWorkaroundForBugReport2495604 is only supported in MATLAB versions R2021a (starting in update 6) and R2021b (starting in update 3). Use visadev instead.</entry>    
    <entry key="invalidNVPairValue">Value must be true, false, or a string array of resource names and identification commands.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidResourceName">Invalid resource name {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="unexpectedOneDimensionalArrayFormat">Expected a logical or an N-by-2 string array, where each row contains a resource name and its corresponding identification command.</entry>
    <entry key="duplicateResourceName">Repeated resource name {0}. Ensure all resource names are unique.</entry>
    <entry key="resourceNotIdentified">Resource {0} is not identified. Specify a valid identification command.</entry>

    <!-- Internal -->
    <entry key="interfaceTypeMismatch">Provided type ''{0}'' does not match desired resource type ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidWriteDataType">Data being written must be a row vector of uint8 data.</entry>
    <entry key="resourceDoesNotSupportThisSetting">This device does not support the specified attribute value.</entry>    
    <entry key="inconsistentAttributeState">Unable to set this attribute because this value puts the instrument in an invalid state.</entry>    
    <entry key="operationTimedOut">Timeout expired before the operation completed.</entry>
    <entry key="systemError">Unknown VISA system error has occurred. Clear visadev object and verify that connection is still valid before creating object again.</entry>        
    
    <!-- Internal: Resource Manager-->
    <entry key="invalidCommand">Invalid command ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToCompleteOperation">Unable to fully execute command ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="standardAdaptorCommandFailed">Adaptor command ''{0}'' failed with status code: {1}.</entry>	
    <entry key="invalidPropertyValue">Method ''{0}'' requires an ''options'' structure containing a field ''{1}'' of type ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="codeDoesNotMatchPlatform">Internal error: code for the ''{0}'' platform should not run on a ''{1}'' platform.</entry>
    <entry key="pluginOnlySupportsSpecificMode">Internal error: plugin can only run in ''{0}'' mode.</entry>
    <entry key="validOnlyInNormalMode">Adaptor command ''{0}'' only valid in "Normal" mode.</entry>

    <entry key="noDefaultResourceManager">Unable to create or open a session for the default resource manager.</entry>
    <entry key="driverErrorOccurred">VISA driver command failed and returned \nStatus code: {0}  \nDiagnostic: ''{1}''\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSearchExpression">Invalid expression specified for search.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownPreferredVISA">Unable to determine preferred VISA.</entry>

    <!-- Internal: Conflict Manager -->
    <entry key="unableToLoadConfManagerSharedLib">Failed to load the ''{0}'' shared library file (error code: {1}). The ''init'' method must have an ''options'' structure with a field ''ConflictManagerPath'' of type ''char'' pointing to the location of the conflict manager shared library.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindEntryPointInSharedLibrary">Unable to find entry point ''{0}'' in conflict manager shared library.</entry>
    <entry key="sharedLibraryInitializationFailed">Unable to initialize shared library.</entry>
    <entry key="noVisaLibraryFoundForResource">Currently configured VISA installation is unable to handle the specified resource. Open the vendor's control software to make sure that a preferred VISA is set and enabled.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToGetVISACount">Unable to get VISA installation count from shared library.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToGetVISAInfo">Unable to get VISA installation information from the shared library because no preferred VISA was found. Open the vendor's control software to set and enable the preferred VISA.</entry>
    <entry key="conflictManagerUnavailable">Unable to load conflict manager or establish entry points.</entry>
    <entry key="conflictManagerUnavailableOnPlatform">Unable to load conflict manager or establish entry points on macOS.</entry>
    <entry key="unhandledExceptionInSharedLibrary">Unhandled exception caught while calling conflict manager method ''{0}''.\n{1}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
