<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <entry key="EmptyFolder">At least one folder is required.</entry>
        <entry key="EmptyNamespace">At least one namespace is required.</entry>
        <entry key="EmptyFileOrFolder">At least one file or folder name is required.</entry>
        <entry key="FolderDoesNotExist">Unable to find folder ''{0}''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSource">Unable to generate a code coverage report because {0} is not a valid file or folder name.</entry>
        <entry key="NamespaceDoesNotExist">Namespace ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableToGenerateReport">Unable to generate report for folder ''{0}''.\nCaused by:\n{1}</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFileType">Unable to generate a code coverage report for file {0}. Specify a valid MATLAB source file with a .m, .mlx, or .mlapp extension.</entry>
        <entry key="ReportSaved">MATLAB code coverage report has been saved to:\n {0} </entry>
        <entry key="RemoveProfileReportFormat">''{0}'' has been removed. Use one of the following report formats instead:\n''{1}'',\n''{2}'' </entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMetric">Unable to generate a code coverage report because the value of MetricLevel is invalid. Specify MetricLevel as "statement",  "decision", "condition", or "mcdc" if you have a MATLAB Test license, or specify it as "statement" if you do not have a MATLAB Test license.</entry>
        <entry key="MissingLicense">Unable to find a MATLAB Test license to support advanced coverage metrics. Defaulting to basic metrics instead.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFilterFileType">Unable to apply filters from file ''{0}'' because it is not an XML file.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMetricToLoadFilterFile">Unable to apply coverage filters. To apply filters to code coverage results, specify MetricLevel as "decision", "condition", or "mcdc".</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMetricToApplyFilterFileToResult">Unable to apply coverage filters. Applying filters requires code coverage results to include information at the decision-coverage level or above.</entry>
        <entry key="MissingLicenseForFilter">Unable to find a MATLAB Test license to apply the coverage filters. Defaulting to coverage results without any filters instead.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  rsccat mlx mcdc
-->
