<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2012-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="MustCallSuperclassMethod">All runner plugin methods must call the corresponding superclass method.</entry>
    <entry key="PluginDataMismatch">All runner plugins calling the superclass ''{0}'' method must call it with the same PluginData as received.</entry>
    <entry key="QualificationUsingDifferentContext">All plugin qualifications must be performed using the supplied context.</entry>
    <entry key="RunningGroupsOnWorkers">Split tests into {0} groups and running them on {1} workers.</entry>
    <entry key="RunningGroupsOnWorker">Split tests into {0} groups and running them on 1 worker.</entry>
    <entry key="RunningGroupOnWorker">Running test using 1 group on 1 worker.</entry>
    <entry key="RunningTestsOnGroupOnWorker">Running tests using 1 group on 1 worker.</entry>
    <entry key="FinishedGroup">Finished Group {0}</entry>
    <entry key="NoPool">Using runInParallel requires an active parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="PluginDoesNotSupportParallel">Plugin {0} does not support running tests in parallel.</entry>
    <entry key="PluginDoesNotSupportParallelThreadPool">Plugin ''{0}'' is not supported on a thread-based parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="ParallelRunException">Exception occurred. Any unfinished groups were cancelled.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreadPoolArtifacts">Storing artifacts is not supported on a thread-based parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreadPoolFileBasedSuite">To run a test suite on a thread-based parallel pool, create the suite using either the fromName, fromClass, fromMethod, or fromNamespace static method of matlab.unittest.TestSuite or the testsuite function with the test content on the path and test names specified using the names of classes or functions, without file extensions.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreadPoolSuiteNotSupported">Test authoring interface is not supported. Thread-based parallel pools support only class-based and function-based tests.</entry>
    <entry key="VerificationFailureInPlugin">A plugin produced a verification failure in method ''{0}'' but qualifications are not allowed in this context.</entry>
    <entry key="MustBeAWritableFolder">''{0}'' value must be a writable folder.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToFindTestMethod">Unable to find the {0} Test method in the {1} class. If the method has been renamed or deleted, create a fresh test suite.</entry>
    <entry key="QualificationInUnsupportedScope">Qualifications are not supported in plugin method ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FixtureDoesNotSupportParallel">Fixture {0} does not support running tests in parallel.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
 <!-- LocalWords:  rsccat AWritable
-->
