<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="mpm">
  <message>
      <entry key="UnsupportedRelease">Error: Unsupported release version: {0}. mpm supports products and support packages for these releases only:\n\tProducts - R2017b or later\n\tSupport Packages - R2019a or later</entry>
      <entry key="UnrecognizedRelease">Error: Unrecognized release version: {0}. mpm supports products and support packages for these releases only:\n\tProducts - R2017b or later\n\tSupport Packages - R2019a or later</entry>
      <entry key="UnrecognizedCommand">Error: Unrecognized command.</entry>
      <entry key="NoCommandSpecified">Error: No command specified.</entry>
      <entry key="ParsingError">Error: Invalid arguments. For argument descriptions, see {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="ExistingProducts">All specified products are already installed.\n</entry>
      <entry key="ExistingDownloadedProducts">All specified products are already downloaded.\n</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleReleaseVersion3">Error: Unable to install because of conflicting release versions. The specified release {0} conflicts with the existing product {1} that is part of release {2}.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleReleaseVersion">Error: Unable to install because of conflicting release versions. The specified release conflicts with the existing installation.</entry>
      <entry key="NoValidProducts">Error: No valid products in specified product list.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingMatlabRootArg">Error: --matlabroot must be specified when using the install-doc command.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidMatlabRootPath">Error: --matlabroot folder is invalid. Specify a valid matlabroot folder.</entry>
      <entry key="NoProductsInMatlabRoot">Error: Unable to find products in MATLAB root folder: {0}</entry>
      <entry key="NoProductsInMatlabRootWithoutFolder">Error: Unable to find products in specified MATLAB root folder.</entry>
      <entry key="InstallDocCmdNotCompatibleWithMatlabRoot">Error: install-doc command is supported in R2023a and later releases only. Specify the matlabroot that is R2023a or later release.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingDependentProducts">Error: Missing product dependencies. Add these products to the product list:</entry>
      <entry key="MissingControllingProducts">Error: Unable to install because of missing products. Add these products to the product list:</entry>
      <entry key="UnsupportedProducts">Error: These are not supported by mpm:</entry>
      <entry key="NonExistantProducts">Error: Unrecognized products:</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationNotWritable">Error: Unable to write to "{0}". Check folder permissions.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationIsFile">Error: Failed to create destination folder. Specified folder exists as a file.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationIsEmptyPath">Error: Invalid destination. Specified destination must not be an empty path.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationIsInstallerRoot">Error: Unable to install into the same folder as the installer. Select a different folder.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationNotAbsolutePath">Error: Specify the full path to the destination folder.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationIsUserProfileFolder">Error: Unable to install into the user profile folder. Select a different folder.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationContainedUnicodeCharacters">Error: Invalid destination. Destination must not contain unicode characters.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationContainedInvalidCharacters">Error: Invalid destination. Destination folder contains invalid characters.</entry>
      <entry key="PostInstallStepsFailed">Error: Unable to complete installation setup.</entry>
      <entry key="DownloadError">Error: Download failed. Check the network connection and retry.</entry>
      <entry key="UnexpectedError">Error: Installation failed.</entry>
	  <entry key="UnexpectedDownloadError">Error: Download failed.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidDWSCredentials">Error: mpm version {0} is not supported. Download the latest version of mpm.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidArchivesPath">Error: Invalid source folder. Specify a valid source folder.</entry>
      <entry key="IOError">Error: Unable to continue due to lack of disk space.</entry>
      <entry key="NotAnArchivesPath">Error: Invalid source folder. Specify a valid source folder containing extracted MathWorks product installation files.</entry>
      <entry key="InaccessibleArchivesPath">Error: Unable to access the source folder. Check read permission.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingArchivesPath">Error: Unable to find installation files in the source folder. Specify a valid source folder.</entry>
      <entry key="ProvidedArchivesMatlabRootNotCompatible">Error: Unable to install. Conflicting release versions found in matlabroot and the documentation ISO image. Specify the matlabroot that is of the same release as the documentation ISO image. </entry>
	  <entry key="OptionNotSupportedForInstall">Error: Option {0} is not supported for install.</entry>
	  <entry key="OptionNotSupportedForRelease">Error: Option {0} is supported only for {1} and later versions.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingRequiredOption">Error: Option {0} is required but missing.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingOptionValueInInputFile">Error: Option {0} in input file is missing a value.</entry>
      <entry key="ConflictingOptions">Error: Invalid option combination. Specify either {0} or {1}.</entry>
      <entry key="UnknownOption">Error: Unrecognized option: {0}</entry>
      <entry key="MissingDestinationInInputFile">Error: Unable to find destination in the input file.</entry>
      <entry key="NoProductSelectedInInputFile">Error: Unable to get the selected products. Uncomment the products in the input file.</entry>
      <entry key="InputFileParsingError">Error: Unable to read the input file. Check the read permission and specify valid path to the input file.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidInputFileSyntax">Error: Input file option must not be specified with any other option.</entry>
      <entry key="DestinationIncompatibleError">Error: Destination folder contains a {0} installation, but this MPM installs packages only for {1}. Either specify a different destination folder or download MPM for {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="MissingOrInvalidChecksumInInputFile">Error: Unable to validate input file. Obtain a new input file from the MPM GitHub page and retry installation. See https://github.com/mathworks-ref-arch/matlab-dockerfile/blob/main/MPM.md.</entry>
      <entry key="SourceIncompatibleError">Error: Source folder contains installation files for {0}, but this MPM installs packages only for {1}. Either specify a different source folder or download MPM for {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="SourceDestinationIncompatibleError">Error: Source folder contains installation files for {0}, but the destination folder contains a {1} installation. Specify either a different source folder or destination folder.</entry>
      <entry key="SourceRootIncompatibleError">Error: Source folder contains installation files for {0}, but the MATLAB root folder contains a {1} installation. Specify either a different source folder or MATLAB root folder.</entry>
      <entry key="ThirdPartyInstallError">Error: Failed to install this third-party software: {0}\nFor help, see https://www.mathworks.com/matlabcentral/answers/307164\n</entry>
      <entry key="ThirdPartyDownloadError">Error: Failed to download this third-party software: {0}\nFor help, see https://www.mathworks.com/matlabcentral/answers/307164\n</entry>
      <entry key="ThirdPartyExtractError">Error: Failed to download the specified products. Try rerunning the mpm command.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidReleaseForMaca64">Error: Native Apple silicon MATLAB is not available for the specified release. To install MATLAB R2023a and earlier, download MPM for Intel-based Macs.\nFor more information: https://www.mathworks.com/mpm_install_incompat_asmac\n</entry>
      <entry key="DownloadConfigurationError">Error: Unable to configure the downloaded files. Try downloading again.</entry>
      <entry key="ProductFilesVersionInfoParseError">Error: The downloaded product files are corrupted and cannot be used. Try rerunning MPM.</entry>
      <entry key="ProductFilesVersionInfoChecksumError">Error: The downloaded product files are corrupted and cannot be used. Try rerunning MPM to download new product files.</entry>
	  <entry key="SameFolderDownloadError">Error: Destination folder already contains downloaded files. Delete existing files or download to a different folder.</entry>
	  <entry key="UnrecognizedPlatform">Error: Unrecognized platform: {0}. Valid platforms: glnxa64 win64 maci64 maca64</entry>
      <entry key="ProductNotSupportedOnPlatform">Error: The following products are not supported on the specified platforms:</entry>
	  <entry key="DependentProductNotAvailable">Error: Unable to find the following dependent products:</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
