<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2016-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    

    <!-- Error messages related to Code Importer -->
    <entry key="FunctionToImportMismatch">Functions ''{0}'' do not exist, are undefined, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="TypeToImportMismatch">Types ''{0}'' do not exist, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="AmbiguousTypeToImport">Unable to import types ''{0}'' because the types have the same name under different namespaces. Select types, functions or class methods so that only one of the types is imported.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindOutputFolder">Unable to find the specified output folder ''{0}''. Check your output folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableOutputFolder">Output folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify an output folder that is not write-protected. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseUnsuccessful">Failed to parse custom code. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyParseResult">Code Importer parser returned empty result. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseErrors" translate="false" note="translate=false set due no translatable content">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="BuildUnsuccessful">Failed to build custom code executable. </entry>
    <entry key="BuildErrors" translate="false" note="translate=false set due no translatable content">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceHeader">Specify at least one interface header file for import. Interface headers can be computed from specified source files by calling method ''computeInterfaceHeaders''.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceHeaderUI">Specify at least one interface header file for import. Interface headers can be computed from specified source files by clicking the Auto-fill button.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptySourceFile">Specify at least one source file for import. </entry>
    <entry key="InferringHdrWithEmptySrc">Specify at least one source file to compute interface headers. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotLoadFile">Unable to load the specified file ''{0}''. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotReadFunctionSettings">Failed to read Code Importer settings. The specified file ''{0}'' is not a Code Importer settings file, or is corrupted. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsFilePath">Unable to load the file ''{0}'' because it does not exist on the computed file path ''{1}''. Check your full path specification ''{2}'' against output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsPath">Unable to find the directory ''{0}''. Check your directory folder specification against the output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="MetadataFileNotCompatible">Unable to load the metadata file. Code Importer only supports MAT-file and ASAP2 format metadata files. </entry>
    <entry key="ASAP2WindowsOnlyWarn">ASAP2 file can only be imported on Windows.</entry>
    <entry key="GRLWindowsOnlyWarn">GRL file can only be imported on Windows.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindMetadataFile">Unable to find the specified metadata file ''{0}''. Check the specified MetadataFile path in CustomCode property.</entry>
    <entry key="DuplicateVariableNameInMetadataFile">Variable name ''{0}'' has duplicate entries in the metadata file. </entry>
    <entry key="NonexistentProjectFile">Unable to load project file. Specified project file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="ImportRequiredBeforeAddToProject">Cannot add files to the project. Perform an import before adding to project.</entry>
    <entry key="ProjectWithinIncludeDir">Unable to add file or folder ''{0}'' to the project. File or folder must be inside of specified project root folder ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSaveFile">Failed to save Code Importer settings. </entry>
    <entry key="FilePathNotExist">The specified folder or file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotOverwrite">File ''{0}'' already exists. Specify a different file name, or to overwrite, set 'Overwrite' to 'on'. </entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotWritable">File ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a file that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="NoFileToLoad">Specify one file to load. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableFolder">Folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a folder that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToOpenSLBlocksFile">Unable to create ''slblocks.m'' in directory ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLibraryFileName">''{0}'' is not a valid library file name. Specify a valid Simulink model file name.</entry>
    <entry key="NothingToImport">There are no Simulink compatible functions or types to import. To import classes, specify classes by namespace qualified names.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotInferHeaderFile"> Interface header information is empty. Check the source files and include directories specifications or explicitly specify the interface header files. </entry>
    <entry key="InferHeadersUnsupported">Computation of interface header files is not applicable for Unit Testing workflow. </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToLoadSLTestSavedFileToBase">Unable to load import settings file saved by Simulink Test Code Importer. To load the file, open Simulink Test Code Importer from Test Manager. </entry>
    <entry key="ClassSimulinkInterfaceUndefined">Simulink interfaces for imported classes ''{0}'' must be defined.</entry>
    <entry key="ClassTypeToImportMismatch">Class types ''{0}'' do not exist, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="OptionsCreateSLBlocks_Ignored">Unabled to add model ''{0}'' to Simulink Library Browser. The model must be a library model.</entry>
    <entry key="ValidateSimulinkInterfaceUnsuccessful">Failed to validate ''{0}'' in the Simulink interface of class ''{1}''. </entry>
    <entry key="ValidateSimulinkInterfaceSuccessful">Successfully validated Simulink interface of class ''{0}''. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceErrorResult">Code Importer validating Simulink interface returned empty result. </entry>
    <entry key="ValidateInterfaceErrors">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="ConflictLoadedModelPath">Specified output folder ''{0}'' is inconsistent with the path of the loaded model or library ''{1}''. The specified output folder must either match the path of the loaded model or library, or you can move the loaded model or library to output folder ''{0}''. </entry>
    
	
	<!-- SLTest CodeImporter Errors -->
	<entry key="IncorrectTestTypeForSandboxCreation">Sandbox cannot be created for Integration Testing workflow. To create a sandbox change the ''TestType'' property to ''UnitTest''.</entry>
	<entry key="SandboxDoesNotExistError">Sandbox does not exist. Use createSandbox method to create a sandbox.</entry>
	<entry key="MoreThanOneSrcSingleSrcSbxError"> ''GenerateAggregatedHeader'' sandbox should contain only one source file. Custom code has {0} source files: {1}</entry>
	<entry key="SandboxUpdateError">Sandbox files have changed. Use createSandbox method to refresh the sandbox.</entry>
	<entry key="CustomCodeChangedSandboxUpdateError">Custom code files specified in the ''CustomCode'' property have changed. Use createSandbox method to refresh the sandbox.</entry>
	<entry key="SandboxCreationFailedError">Code Importer failed to create the sandbox.</entry>
	<entry key="SandboxParseFailedError">Code Importer sandbox parse was unsuccessful.</entry>
	<entry key="AutoStubGenerationFailedError">Code Importer failed to generate auto stub files.</entry>
	<entry key="SLTestCodeImporterFailureCause" translate="false" note="translate=false set due no translatable content">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="GenerateSLBlocksIgnored">Code Importer option ''LibraryBrowserName'' is not applicable for testing workflow.</entry>
    <entry key="GenerateTestHarnessIgnored">Simulink Test is required to create test harness for imported library blocks. </entry>
    <entry key="MissingSymbolsInSandbox">Declarations for the following symbols are missing. These symbols cannot be automatically stubbed. Declare these symbols in the sandbox manual stub files and execute ''createSandbox'' method to update the sandbox and proceed.</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingInSandbox">Missing symbols:{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MissingSymbolsInSandboxUI">Declarations for the following symbols are missing. These symbols cannot be automatically stubbed. Declare these symbols in the sandbox manual stub files and click on ''Update Sandbox'' button to proceed.</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingFunction">Functions:</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingType">Types:</entry>    
    <entry key="ImportSpecialTypesError">Code Importer failed to import selected types into a Simulink data dictionary.</entry>
	
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords: -->
