<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    
    <!-- Error messages related to Python Importer -->
    <entry key="FunctionToImportMismatch">Functions ''{0}'' do not exist, are undefined, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="TypeToImportMismatch">Types ''{0}'' do not exist, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindOutputFolder">Unable to find the specified output folder ''{0}''. Check your output folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindPackageFolder">Unable to find the specified package folder ''{0}''. Check your package folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableOutputFolder">Output folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify an output folder that is not write-protected. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseUnsuccessful">Failed to parse custom code. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyParseResult">Python Importer parser returned empty result. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseErrors" translate="false" note="translate=false set due no translatable content">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="NoCodeToImport">Unable to find any code to import. Specify at least one source file or include file. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotLoadFile">Unable to load the specified file ''{0}''. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptySourceFile">Specify at least one source file for import. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotReadFunctionSettings">Failed to read Python Importer settings. The specified file ''{0}'' is not a Python Importer settings file, or is corrupted. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsFilePath">Unable to load the file ''{0}'' because it does not exist on the computed file path ''{1}''. Check your full path specification ''{2}'' against output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsPath">Unable to find the directory ''{0}''. Check your directory folder specification against the output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonPackageName">Invalid python package name ''{0}''. Python package name starting with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonModuleName">Invalid python module name ''{0}''. Python module name starting with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonClassName">Invalid python class name ''{0}'' in python file ''{1}''. Python class name starting with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonFunctionName">Invalid python function name ''{0}'' in python file ''{1}''. Python function name starting with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPackageNameWithRelativePath">Invalid python package name ''{0}''. Use absolute path to specify python package. </entry>
    <entry key="NonexistentProjectFile">Unable to load project file. Specified project file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="ImportRequiredBeforeAddToProject">Cannot add files to the project. Perform an import before adding to project.</entry>
    <entry key="ProjectWithinIncludeDir">Unable to add file or folder ''{0}'' to the project. File or folder must be inside of specified project root folder ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="SaveTheNewLibraryModel">Python Importer tool requires that you save the library model first.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSaveFile">Failed to save Python Importer settings. </entry>
    <entry key="FilePathNotExist">The specified folder or file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotOverwrite">File ''{0}'' already exists. Specify a different file name, or to overwrite, set 'Overwrite' to 'on'. </entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotWritable">File ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a file that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="NoFileToLoad">Specify one file to load. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableFolder">Folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a folder that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToOpenSLBlocksFile">Unable to create ''slblocks.m'' in directory ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLibraryFileName">''{0}'' is not a valid library file name. Specify a valid Simulink model file name.</entry>
    <entry key="NothingToImport">There are no Simulink compatible functions or types to import. </entry>
    <entry key="MissingPythonInitFile"> A python package must contain a __init__.py file. The specified folder ''{0}'' is missing the __init__.py file. </entry>
    <entry key="StaticAnalysisFailedIOTypes"> Static analysis failed to identify python function inputs and outputs in python module ''{0}''. Simulink is unable to import ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecificationDataType"> Simulink Python Import port specification data type must be one of ''double'', ''uint8'', ''int64'', ''boolean'', ''string'' or a Simulink bus. </entry>
    <entry key="NoAvailableFunctionsToImport"> There are no python functions available for import. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecificationLabel"> Simulink Python Importer port label beginning with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecification"> Simulink Python Importer does not support python functions with no inputs and outputs. </entry>
    
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords: -->
