<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2009-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
      
    <!-- From Workspace Errors -->
    <entry key="FromwksNoExtrapWithoutInterp"><![CDATA[Invalid configuration for block ''{0}''. Unable to extrapolate output values after final workspace data value because interpolation is not enabled.
      <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
        <action type="fixit" id="FromwksNoExtrapWithoutInterpFix">
          <cmd>set_param_action(''{0}'', 'Interpolate', 'on');</cmd>
          <txt>Enable interpolation.</txt>
        </action>
      </actions>]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUnsupportedDimensions">Unable to load data in structure ''{1}'' specified as input data for block ''{0}''. The dimensions of each sample in the signals.values field of structure ''{1}'' ({2}) must match the dimensions specified in the signals.dimensions field (''{3}'').</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumRows">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Time and data values must have the same number of rows</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumRows2">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Values in valueDimensions field and data values must have the same number of rows.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumTSteps">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The last dimension of each ''signals.values'' field must be the same as the number of rows in the ''time'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="BlockNotSupportedWithDictionary">This model cannot contain {0} block ''{1}'' because the model is linked to a data dictionary.  For a test harness model, configure it to use the base workspace instead of a data dictionary.  Otherwise, replace this block with a root Inport or other source block.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumTSteps2">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The last dimension of each ''signals.values'' field must be the same as the number of rows in the ''valueDimensions'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsNumDimsMismatch">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The number of columns of values in the ''valueDimensions'' field does not match the number of dimensions specified by signal data.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInvTimeValues">Invalid workspace variable ''{0}'' specified as {1} input in ''{2}''. Time values must be a real vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInvMatrixParam">Invalid matrix variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The matrix data must be a real, double, have two dimensions, and at least two columns. The first column must contain time values and the remaining columns the data values.  Matrix values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksNonMontonicTime_ss">Invalid workspace variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Time values must be non-decreasing.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksCyclicOnlyWithNoTime">Cannot specify cyclic repetition in ''{0}'' when the time vector is explicitly specified for the data. The cyclic option is supported only when the data is in the form of a structure with an empty time vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUnsupportedDataType">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Only numeric, logical and enumerated values are supported. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN). </entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInfValueInParam">Invalid data values within variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Data values must neither be Inf nor NaN. Also, the values should be specified using matrices that are neither empty nor sparse.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDiscCannotInterp">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When time field is not specified in ''{2}'' parameter, interpolation has to be turned off and the extrapolation option cannot be chosen for forming the output after the final data value.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotInterpWithTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Interpolate data" checkbox and the parameter "Form output after final data value by" can only be set to "Hold final value".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotInterpWithoutTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Interpolate data" checkbox and the parameter "Form output after final data value by" can only be set to "Hold final value" or "Cyclic repetition".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotZeroCrossing">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Enable zero-crossing detection" checkbox.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsFinalValWithTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, the "Form output after final data value by" parameter can only be set to "Hold final value".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsFinalValWithoutTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, the "Form output after final data value by" parameter can only be set to "Hold final value" or "Cyclic repetition".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksCannotInterpFiOrEnum">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. The variable ''{2}'' cannot be interpolated.  When the ''{3}'' parameter refers to a workspace variable that contains fixed point, enumeration, or string data, interpolation must be turned off and the extrapolation option cannot be chosen for forming the output after the final data value.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksCannotInterpFiEnumString">Variable ''{0}'' contains string, enum, or fixed-point data. To load the data, disable interpolation and specify an option other than extrapolation to form the output after the final data value.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksNonScalarStructure">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The input structure must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUndefinedDataField">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. If the input signal is a bus signal, the variable must be a structure of MATLAB timeseries objects. Otherwise, the variable must include ''time'' and ''signals'' fields, and the ''signals'' field must be a structure with a ''values'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksMultipleSignals">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The ''signals'' structure has {2,number,integer} elements instead of {3,number,integer} elements.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksTsArrayNotSupported">Invalid TsArray object specified as input to ''{0}''. The From Workspace block does not support TsArray objects.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksTimeseriesStructNotSupported">Invalid structure specified as input to ''{0}''. The From Workspace block does not support structure of timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksNotSupportedFormat">Unsupported input format for From Workspace block ''{0}''. Input data must use a supported format such as timeseries or timetable and must not contain Inf or NaN values.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksOnlyDiscSampleTime">Invalid continuous sample time specified for ''{0}''. Continuous sample time is not permitted when the input from workspace is a structure with no time data. To eliminate this error, select a discrete sample time or change the input data to include time data.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksDataTypeMismatch">Inconsistent data type for From Workspace block ''{0}''.  The workspace variable has data type ''{1}''.  This data type does not agree with the data type, ''{2}'', that is being set for this block.  Change the data type of the input data to ''{3}'' or change the "Output data type" of this block to ''Inherit: auto''.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksFastRestartDimensionsMismatch">The dimensions of data for block ''{0}'' specified for this Fast Restart run are different from the dimensions used in the previous Fast Restart run. To run in Fast Restart mode again, use data with dimensions that match those of the From Workspace output signal. Otherwise, exit Fast Restart mode and start a new simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksFastRestartComplexityMismatch">The complexity of data for block ''{0}'' specified for this Fast Restart run is different from the complexity used in the previous Fast Restart run. To run in Fast Restart mode again, use data with the same complexity as the From Workspace output signal. Otherwise, exit Fast Restart mode and start a new simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksBlkDescr"><![CDATA[
Read data values specified in timeseries, matrix, or structure format from the MATLAB workspace, model workspace, or mask workspace.\n\nMATLAB timeseries format may be used for any data type, complexity, or fixed dimensions. To load data for a bus signal, use a MATLAB structure that matches the bus hierarchy and specify timeseries for each leaf signal.\n\nFor matrix formats, each row of the matrix has a time stamp in the first column and a vector containing the corresponding data sample in the subsequent column(s).\n\nFor structure format, use the following kind of structure:\n
    var.time=[TimeValues]\n
    var.signals.values=[DataValues]\n
    var.signals.dimensions=[DimValues]\n
    ]]></entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStringMode">From Workspace block ''{0}'' loads string data. From Workspace blocks can only load string data in normal and accelerator modes.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStringModeMdlRef">From Workspace block ''{0}'' loads string data. From Workspace blocks in referenced models can only load string data when the referenced model is simulated in normal mode.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStrNonScalar">From Workspace block ''{0}'' cannot load non-scalar string data.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStrMissing">From Workspace block ''{0}'' cannot load string data that contains missing values.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStrNonAscii">From Workspace block ''{0}'' cannot load string data that contains non-ASCII characters.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksStrLenExceedsMax">From Workspace block ''{0}'' cannot load a string whose length exceeds the maximum string length, ''{1}'', as specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksNonDoublePortLoadingMatrix">From Workspace block ''{0}'' is configured to load a ''{1}'' matrix. From Workspace blocks only support loading double matrices. To load non-double data, consider using structure or timeseries format.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksEmpty">Data loaded by From Workspace block "{0}" must contain at least one signal value for all supported data formats and must contain at least one time value for all data formats except Structure without time.</entry>
    
    <!-- Root Inport Errors -->
    <entry key="MdlUTNotSupportedFormat">Input format not supported. Available formats include: (1) a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object, (2) a double non-complex matrix, (3) a structure with or without time, (4) a MATLAB timeseries object, (5) a timetable object, (6) a matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore object, (7) a structure with MATLAB timeseries objects, timetable objects, matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore objects (or some mixture of these) at all leaves (for bus input). All formats require the data to be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTNonScalarDataset">A non-scalar Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object used for external input. When using a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object for external input, even though it may contain multiple elements, the object itself must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTNonScalarDatasetRef">A non-scalar Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object used for external input. When using a Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object for external input, even though it may reference a Dataset with multiple elements, the object itself must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTSimulinkAndMatlabTimeseries">Model input cannot combine Simulink.Timeseries or Simulink.TsArray formats with MATLAB timeseries formats (including structure of MATLAB timeseries).</entry>
    <entry key="TimeseriesUnsupportedDataType">Data in timeseries object ''{0}'' specified as {1} input for block ''{2}'' not supported. Data must not contain Inf or NaN values and must have a built-in numeric, logical, fixed-point, or enumerated data type.</entry>
    <entry key="TimeseriesUnsupportedIsTimeFirst">The timeseries variable ''{0}'' specified as {1} input in ''{2}'' cannot be loaded.  For this timeseries, the combination of the IsTimeFirst property and the dimensionality of the Data property is not supported. To load data for this input, update the dimension of the Data property of the timeseries object:\n
      -If the signal is a scalar or a 1-D vector, time must be the first dimension.\n
      -If the signal has more than 1 dimension, time must be the last dimension.
    </entry>
    <entry key="SimTimeseriesUnsupportedDataType">Invalid Simulink.Timeseries variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The Data property must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type. The dimensions of the Data property must be non-zero.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDiscSampleTime">Invalid sample time for root level port ''{0}''. Since the external input corresponding to the inport does not specify any time values, the sample time must be discrete.</entry>           
    <entry key="InportInvalidMatrixDataLoading">Invalid matrix variable entered in the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog of model {0}. For this model, the input variable must be a structure. Matrix input can only be used if all the signals connected to the root Inports are real (non-complex), double vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeMismatch">Invalid data type for root level port ''{0}''. The model is configured to load its root level ports from the workspace.  These external inputs have data type ''{1}''.  This data type does not agree with the data type, ''{2}'', that is being set for this root level port.
        <![CDATA[
            <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
                <action type="suggestion">
                    <txt>Change the data type of the input data to type ''{3}''</txt>
                </action>
                <action type="fixit">
                    <cmd>slprivate(''simulinkfixes'',''InportDataTypeMismatch'',''{0}'')</cmd>
                    <txt>Turn off external input loading.</txt>
                </action>
            </actions>
        ]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeMismatchFix">Executed the command 'set_param(model, 'LoadExternalInput', 'off')'</entry>           
    <entry key="FcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Invalid workspace data format for root Inport ''{0}''. The model is configured to load its root level ports from the workspace. This root Inport is configured to output a function call. Use one of these approaches: \n\t1) For the workspace data to be loaded, use a column vector of monotonically non-decreasing time values; \n\t2) For this root Inport, clear the ''Output function call'' block parameter; \n\t3) Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Unable to load input data for top-level Inport block ''{0}'' because loading a column vector is supported only for blocks configured to produce a function-call output. Input data for other types of signals must include both time and signal values.
    <![CDATA[
             <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>Specify the input data using another format, such as timetable or timeseries.</txt>
             </action>
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>Format the data as a 2-D matrix where the first column contains time values and subsequent columns contain the signal value for each time value.</txt>
             </action>
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>To load function-call data, select ''Output function call'' for this block and check that the model is configured as an export-function model.</txt>
             </action>
             </actions>
    ]]> </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTsForFcnCallInportWithSpecifiedTs">Invalid workspace data for root-level Inport ''{0}''. Because the Inport is configured to output a function call with a discrete sample time of {1}, the time vector must be empty if any of the function-call subsystems it drives are configured to execute periodically. Consider using one of these approaches: \n\t1) For the workspace data to be loaded, use an empty vector []; \n\t2) Configure every function-call subsystem this Inport drives to a triggered function-call subsystem, by setting 'Sample time type' parameter of the Trigger Port block inside the function-call subsystem to 'triggered'; \n\t3) For this Inport, specify the ''Sample time' to inherited (-1); \n\t4) Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="InportArrayNonDblDataType">Inport block ''{0}'' specifies ''{1}'' data type but receives external input data of type 'double'. To load external data of a data type other than double, use a structure, timeseries, or timetable format.</entry>
    <entry key="InportComplexityMismatch">Invalid signal type for port ''{0}''. Although the external inputs specified for the block diagram indicate that the data is complex, the port is not set to complex.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDiscCannotInterp">Invalid setting for parameter ''Interpolate'' in ''{0}''. When time field is not specified in the workspace variable corresponding to a root level port, interpolation must be turned off.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataMustBeFinite">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains Inf or NaN. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="InportTimeDiffMustBeLessThanDoubleMax">Unable to interpolate external input data ''{1}'' using Inport block ''{0}'' because the data contains consecutive times that differ by more than the largest possible double value. To load the data, clear the interpolation setting for Inport block ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InportCannotInterpFiOrEnum">Unable to interpolate fixed-point, string, or enumeration data loaded by block ''{0}'' using variable ''{1}''. To load the data, disable interpolation for block ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidSpecifiedFcnCallTime">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The difference between the time value ({1}) specified by this variable and the offset ({3}) specified on the port is not an integer multiple of the step size ({2}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidSpecifiedFcnCallTimeNoOffset">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({1}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the step size ({2}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidFcnCallTime">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({1}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({2}) of the model.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatch">Invalid port dimensions for port ''{0}''. The external inputs specified for the block diagram indicate that the port dimensions should be {1}. Instead, the port dimensions are being set to {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatchAOB">The dimensions {1} of input data {3} are inconsistent with the dimensions {2} of port ''{0}''. The number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of port dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding port dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatchAOBForHier">The dimensions {1} of input data {3} for port ''{0}'' are inconsistent with the dimensions {2} of bus object {4}. The number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of bus object dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding bus object dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="InportNonScalarTimeseries">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' is a non-scalar timeseries array. External input loading supports input from timeseries objects within a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset instance only if it is a scalar timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportNonScalarSimulationDatastore">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' is a non-scalar SimulationDatastore (matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore) array. External input loading supports input from SimulationDatastore objects within a Dataset instance only if it is a scalar SimulationDatastore object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportNonMatFileBackedSimulationDatastore">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' specifies a SimulationDatastore that is backed by a MAT file.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidNumberOfSamplesTimeseries">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' is a timeseries instance. External input loading supports input from timeseries objects within a Dataset instance only if each timeseries in the dataset contains a non-zero number of data points.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidNumberOfSamplesSimulationDatastore">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset.  The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' is a SimulationDatastore (matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore) instance. External input loading supports input from SimulationDatastore objects within a Dataset instance only if each SimulationDatastore in the Dataset contains a non-zero number of data points.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportDimsModeMismatch1">Workspace data loaded by root-level Inport block ''{0}'' contains a variable-size signal, but the 'Variable-size signal' parameter for the block is set to 'No'.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportDimsModeMismatch2">Root-level Inport block ''{0}'' loads data for a fixed-size signal but the 'Variable-size signal' parameter is set to 'Yes'.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportNonVirtBusDimsModeMismatch">The Bus Object specified on ''{0}'' contains a variable-size Bus element. However, the workspace data corresponding to this root Inport does not have the ''valueDimensions'' field for the Bus element. Fix the Bus Object ''DimensionsMode'' field to match the workspace data.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksNonVirtBusDimsModeMismatch">The bus object specified on ''{0}'' contains a variable-size bus element. From Workspace blocks do not support loading data for variable-sized bus elements.</entry>

    <entry key="BlockDataValuesType">The variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains an unsupported Values property.  The Values property must be a scalar timeseries, MATLAB structure with timeseries at the leaves, timetable, or MATLAB structure with timetables at the leaves.</entry>

    <entry key="DatasetEmpty">The variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains a Dataset with no elements.
    Use the addElement method to add elements to this dataset for loading.</entry>
    <entry key="DatasetNestedElements">The Dataset variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains a nested Dataset
    at element {2,number,integer}.  To use Dataset objects to load external inputs, create a flat list of elements
    using the addElement method.</entry>
    
    <entry key="MultipleDatasets">Multiple external inputs are using Dataset objects. To load external
    input data using a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object, you must add all inputs to a single Dataset.</entry>
    <entry key="MultipleDatasetRefs">Multiple external inputs are using DatasetRef objects. To load external
    input data using a Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object, you must have all inputs in a single DatasetRef object.</entry>
    <entry key="ExtraTriggerData">The model ''{0}'' specifies external input data for a trigger port but does not contain
    any root-level trigger ports. </entry>
    <entry key="ExtraEnableData">The model ''{0}'' specifies external input data for a enable port but does not contain
    any root-level enable ports. </entry>
    <entry key="InportNonDoubleTimeValues">Invalid data type. Time values for input data ''{0}'' loaded by block ''{1}'' must be double scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="InportNonDoubleTimeValuesStruct">Invalid data type. Time values for input data ''{0}'' must be double scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="DatasetExtInputInvalidElementContents">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. Simulink supports external input of this type only if each of the dataset elements is one of the following: a double real matrix of kind [time data] containing a sequence of non-decreasing values in the first column, a double real column vector containing a sequence of non-decreasing values (used only for function call signal loading), a scalar timeseries object, a structure of scalar timeseries objects, a scalar timetable object, a structure of scalar timetable objects, or an object derived from Simulink.SimulationData.BlockData with the Values property being a scalar timeseries or matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore object or a structure of scalar timeseries or matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore objects.</entry>
    <entry key="ExtInputSparseInvalidElementContents">Loading sparse matrix data into block ''{0}'' not supported. </entry>
    <entry key="RootInportResumeInvalidFile">File {0} containing external input data was deleted or modified between pause and resume. This is an invalid file for the current simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableUnsupportedDataType">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as input in ''{1}''. The input is a Dataset with elements containing timetables. The Data property of the timetable must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableUnsupportedDataTypeNonDs">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as input in ''{1}''. The input is either a timetable or a Dataset with elements containing timetables. The Data property of timeseries or timetable must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableUnsupportedDataTypeFromWks">Data property of timetable input ''{0}'' for ''{1}'' must have a built-in, fixed-point, or enumerated data type and must not contain Inf or NaN values.</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableUnsupportedTimeFormat">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as input in ''{1}''. Time must be a Duration vector.</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableRILDecreasing">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as input in ''{1}''. Time must be non-decreasing.</entry>
    <entry key="TimetableRILOneVar">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as input in ''{1}''. Timetable for simulation input cannot have more than one variable.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportTimeExpressionRapid">Unable to load external input data ''{0}''. Rapid accelerator mode does not support loading time expressions.</entry>
    
    <!-- Bus Errors -->
    <entry key="InportDataNonBusDataForBus">The root level port ''{0}'' specifies a bus object, but the external input workspace variable ''{1}'' is not compatible with buses. To load external inputs for bus ports, use a structure containing MATLAB timeseries objects or modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataNonBusDataForBus"> Unable to load variable ''{1}'' using From Workspace block ''{0}'' with data type specified using a Simulink.Bus object. To load bus data using the From Workspace block, provide input data as a structure that contains a timeseries or timetable object for each signal in the bus.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksAobBusLeafFormat">''{0}'' must be a timeseries, timetable, or empty MATLAB array.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeNotBus">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load a TsArray object from the workspace but its data type ''{1}'' is not a Bus data type. Modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStructDataTypeNotBus">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load a structure of timeseries objects from the workspace but its data type ''{1}'' is not a Bus data type. Modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksStructDataTypeNotBus">The From Workspace block ''{0}'' is configured to load a structure of timeseries objects from the workspace, but its data type ''{1}'' is not a bus data type. To load bus data in a From Workspace block, set the "Output data type" to ''Bus: BusObjectName''.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusDataTypeMismatch">Invalid data type for root level inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the data type is ''{2}''. This data type does not agree with the data type ''{3}'' that is being set by the BusObject. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusComplexityMismatch">Invalid signal type for inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the data should be complex. Instead, the corresponding element in the BusObject is set to real. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusDimsMismatch">Invalid port dimensions for inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the dimensions should be {2}. Instead, the element dimensions is specified to be {3} by the BusObject. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksArrayOfSubBus">The From Workspace block ''{0}'' specifies a bus object containing a nonscalar sub-bus. Loading external data for arrays of buses is not supported.  To avoid this error, use a separate From Workspace block for each scalar bus and use a Vector Concatenate block.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksNotSupportArrayOfBus">Unable to load nonscalar structure data ''{1}'' using From Workspace block ''{0}''. To load data for an array of buses using a From Workspace block, the block must be in a top model simulated in normal or accelerator mode or in a referenced model that executes in normal mode.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructDataTypeMismatch">Inconsistent data type for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the data type is ''{3}''. This data type does not agree with the data type ''{4}'' that is being set by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructComplexityMismatch">Inconsistent signal type for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the data is complex. The corresponding element in the bus object is set to real.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructDimsMismatch">Inconsistent port dimensions for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the dimensions are {3}. The element dimensions are set to {4} by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTSAndBusTypeDoNotMatch">The bus data type specified by the root level Inport ''{0}'' does not match the TsArray object in the workspace. The TsArray object must contain the same number of TimeSeries elements as specified by the BusObject.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructForNonBus">The bus data type specified by the root level Inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure must be a timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructForNonBus">The bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure must be a timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructLeafForBus">The bus data type specified by the root level Inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is a timeseries object but the bus object indicates this bus element is a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructLeafForBus">The bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is a timeseries object but the bus object indicates this bus element is a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataEmptyHierStructForBus">The external input specified for root Inport ''{0}'' contains bus data with no fields.  To use ground values for this input port, change the variable ''{1}'' to an empty MATLAB array (i.e. "[]").</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataEmptyHierStructForBus">Workspace data specified for From Workspace block ''{0}'' is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructExtraField">The Bus data type specified by the root level Inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is not an element of the bus.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructExtraField">The Bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is not an element of the bus.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStrLenExceedsMax">The length of the string being loaded in the root input port ''{0}'' exceeds the maximum string length, ''{1}'', as specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStrNonScalar">The root-level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains a non-scalar MATLAB string.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStrMissing">The root-level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains missing MATLAB strings.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStrInterp">The root-level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains MATLAB string data. Interpolation must be turned off.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStrNonAscii">The root-level port ''{0}'' is configured to load string data from variable ''{1}'' that contains non-ASCII characters.</entry>
    <entry key="InportEmpty">Timetable must contain at least one row time and one data value.</entry>
    
    <!-- Utility Function Errors -->
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructTsArrayArg">To construct a hierarchy from a Simulink.TsArray object, only 1 argument is permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructBusObjArg">To construct a MATLAB structure from a bus object, the first argument must be the name of a bus object. The optional second argument can be either a cell array of MATLAB timeseries objects, or a structure of timeseries objects. If you specify a cell array of timeseries objects, you can use a third argument that specifies the dimension of the resulting structure. If you specify a structure of timeseries objects, that structure must have the same hierarchy as the bus object. However, the names of the fields in the structure of timeseries can be different from the nodes defined in the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructArg">The first argument must be a Simulink.TsArray object or the name of a valid Simulink.Bus object from the base workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructBusObj">Unable to determine bus hierarchy. Verify the first argument is a name of a valid bus object in the base workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataNumData">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization. The number of leaf elements in the first and second arguments do not match.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateBusSignalName">Simulink.TsArray contains field ''{0}'' that is not a MATLAB-valid identifier. Structure format requires all bus signals to use valid MATLAB identifiers.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataElement">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization. Cell array must contain only MATLAB timeseries or Simulink.Timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataType">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is of type {1} but the bus object requires type {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructFiMismatch">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is a fixed point type but does not match Bus object fixed point settings.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataComplexity">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is complex but the bus object requires real data.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataDims">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} contains ''Data'' of dimension {1} but the bus object requires dimension {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="ConvertTimeseriesFrames">Simulink.Timeseries cannot be converted to MATLAB timeseries because this Timeseries contains frames.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructFromStruct">To construct a MATLAB structure from a bus object, if the second argument is a structure of MATLAB timeseries objects, then the structure of timeseries must have the same hierarchy as the bus object. However, the names of the fields in the structure of timeseries can be different from the nodes defined in the bus object.</entry>

    <!-- Legacy Format Phase-out Errors -->
    <entry key="InportLegacyFormatLoading">The input data ''{1}'' for model ''{0}'' is of a format that is no longer supported.  Please use MATLAB timeseries in place of Simulink.Timeseries and structures of MATLAB timeseries objects in place of Simulink.TsArray.</entry>


    <!-- Dataset root inport, non-Dataset root inport, From Workspace unification errors -->
    <entry key="DatasetRootInportError">Error loading external input data into root-level Inport block {0} in model ''{1}'' using Dataset format.</entry>
    <entry key="NonDatasetRootInportError">Error loading external input data into root-level Inport block {0} in model ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FlexibleFromWorkspaceError">Error loading data into Flexible Source Block ''{0}'' in model ''{1}''.</entry>
    
    <entry key="FromWorkspaceError">Error loading data into From Workspace block ''{0}'' in model ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SignalEditorError">Error loading data into Signal Editor block ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingSparseMatrix">Variable ''{0}'' contains a sparse matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingBlockDataValuesType">Variable ''{0}'' contains an unsupported Values property.  The Values property must be a scalar matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore, scalar timeseries, timetable, MATLAB structure with matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore, timeseries, or timetables at the leaves.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidElementContents"><![CDATA[Invalid data type supplied. For a list of supported data types, see <a href="matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot,'simulink','helptargets.map'), 'formsofinputdata')">Forms of Input Data</a> in the root Inport loading documentation.]]></entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStructDataTypeNotBus">Block is configured to load bus data as a structure with leaves representing signal data, but the data type is set to ''{0}''. To load bus data, you must set the data type as a bus data type.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataHierStructExtraField">The bus data type does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{0}'' of the structure is not an element of the bus.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonScalarTimeseries">Invalid data type. Input timeseries data ''{0}'' must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidNumberOfSamplesTimeseries">Input timeseries data ''{0}'' must contain a non-zero number of data and time points.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonDoubleTimeValues">Invalid data type. The time values of input data ''{0}'' must be of type double.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingVariableUnsupportedDataType">The Data property of timeseries variable ''{0}'' must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type and all data values must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonScalarSimulationDatastore">Input ''{0}'' must be scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonMatFileBackedSimulationDatastore">Input ''{0}'' specifies a SimulationDatastore that is not backed by a MAT file.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidNumberOfSamplesSimulationDatastore">Number of data points in input ''{0}'' must be greater than zero.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingCannotInterpFiOrEnum">Loaded variable contains enumeration data. To load enumeration data, turn off interpolation by clearing the ''Interpolate Data'' option.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingTimetableUnsupportedTimeFormat">Time in timetable variable ''{0}'' must be a Duration vector.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingTimetableRILOneVar">Timetable input ''{0}'' cannot contain more than one variable.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingTimeDecreasing">Time in variable ''{0}' must be non-decreasing and must be finite (not Inf or Nan).</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInportStrMissing">Variable ''{0}'' contains ''missing'' MATLAB strings. To identify ''missing'' values on an array of strings, use the ismissing function.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInportStrMissingBus">String data being loaded at field ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for the block contains ''missing'' MATLAB strings.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrInterp">Variable ''{0}'' contains MATLAB string data. To load string data, turn off interpolation by unchecking the ''Interpolate Data'' checkbox on the block.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrLenExceedsMax">The length of the string loaded in variable ''{0}'' exceeds the maximum string length, ''{1}'', expected by the block.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrLenExceedsMaxBus">The length of the string loaded at field ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for the block exceeds the maximum string length, ''{1}'', expected by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrLenExceedsAbsoluteMax">The length of the string being loaded in variable ''{0}'' exceeds the upper limit of ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrLenExceedsAbsoluteMaxBus">The length of the string being loaded at field  ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for the block exceeds the upper limit of ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrNonAscii">String data in variable ''{0}'' contains non-ASCII characters.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrNonAsciiBus">String data at field ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for the block contains non-ASCII characters.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrNonScalar">Variable ''{0}'' contains a non-scalar MATLAB string.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrNonScalarBus">Field ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for the block  contains a non-scalar MATLAB string.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStrInStruct">External inputs in the structure with time and structure without time formats must not contain string or character vector data.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataMustBeFinite">Variable ''{0}'' contains Inf or Nan values. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidTsForFcnCallInportWithSpecifiedTs">Because the Inport is configured to output a function call with a discrete sample time of {0}, the time vector must be empty if any of the function-call subsystems it drives are configured to execute periodically. Consider using one of these approaches: \n\t1) For the workspace data to be loaded, use an empty vector []; \n\t2) Configure every function-call subsystem this Inport drives to a triggered function-call subsystem, by setting 'Sample time type' parameter of the Trigger Port block inside the function-call subsystem to 'triggered'; \n\t3) For this Inport, specify the ''Sample time' to inherited (-1); \n\t4) Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingFcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Invalid data loaded for Inport configured with a function call output. Use one of these solutions: \n\t1) To load workspace data, use a column vector of monotonically non-decreasing time values; \n\t2) Clear the 'Output function call' parameter of the Inport; \n\t3) Turn off external input loading.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonFcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Loading a column vector is supported only for Inport blocks configured to produce a function-call output. Input data for other types of signals must include both time and signal values.
    <![CDATA[
             <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>Specify the input data using another format, such as timetable or timeseries.</txt>
             </action>
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>Format the data as a 2-D matrix where the first column contains time values and subsequent columns contain the signal value for each time value.</txt>
             </action>
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>To load function-call data, select ''Output function call'' for this block and check that the model is configured as an export-function model.</txt>
             </action>
             </actions>
    ]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataTypeMismatch">Invalid data type. The model is configured to load its root level ports from the workspace.  These external inputs have data type ''{1}''.  This data type does not agree with the data type, ''{2}'', that is being set for this root level port.
    <![CDATA[
             <actions exclusiveFixIts="yes">
             <action type="suggestion">
             <txt>Change the data type of the input data to type ''{3}''</txt>
             </action>
             <action type="fixit">
             <cmd>slprivate(''simulinkfixes'',''LoadingDataTypeMismatch'',''{0}'')</cmd>
             <txt>Turn off external input loading.</txt>
             </action>
             </actions>
    ]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataTypeMismatchFix">Executed the command 'set_param(model, 'LoadExternalInput', 'off')'</entry>
    <entry key="Loading64BitDataTypeMismatch">External input data loaded in this port is of type ''{0}'' whereas the inherited data type for this block is ''{1}''. When the port is configured to load data of type int64 or uint64, the loaded input data must be fixed-point and must be compatible with the inherited data type.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingBusStruct64BitDataTypeMismatch">External input data loaded in field ''{0}'' of the input structure is of type ''{1}'' whereas the inherited data type for this bus element is ''{2}''. When the port is configured to load leaf bus data of type int64 or uint64, the loaded input data must be fixed-point and must be compatible with the inherited data type.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingBusStructDataTypeMismatch">Data type of the input structure specified for the block is ''{1}''. Field ''{0}'' of the input structure must match data type ''{2}'' specified by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingBusStructDimsMismatch">Field ''{0}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the dimensions are {1}. The element dimensions are set to {2} by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingPortDimsMismatch">The external inputs specified for the block diagram indicate that the port dimensions should be {0}. Instead, the port dimensions are being set to {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingBusStructComplexityMismatch">Complexity of field ''{0}'' in the input structure must be compatible with the complexity specified by the corresponding element of the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingComplexityMismatch">Inport expects real data but receives complex data.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataNonBusDataForBus">The block expects bus data but receives workspace variable ''{0}'' that does not represent bus data. To load bus data, use a structure with a mixture of timeseries, timetable, and matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore objects at the leaves.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDataHierStructLeafForBus">Input variable structure must match the bus data type specified by the block. The bus object indicates the element corresponding to field ''{0}'' is a bus, but field ''{0}'' of the input structure is not a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingPortDimsMismatchAOB">The dimensions {0} of the input data {2} are inconsistent with the dimensions {1} of the port. When loading array of bus data, the number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of port dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding port dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingPortDimsMismatchAOBForHier">The dimensions {0} of input data {2} for the block are inconsistent with the dimensions {1} of bus object {3}. The number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of bus object dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding bus object dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStructUnsupportedDataType">The values field of structure variable ''{0}'' must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed-point, or enumerated type, and the data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingStructEmptyUnsupportedDataType">The values field of structure variable ''{0}'' must not be empty.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingVardimOnBlkButNotData">Block loads data for a fixed-size signal but the 'Variable-size signal' parameter is set to 'Yes'.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingVardimOnDataButNotBlk">Workspace data loaded by block contains a variable-size signal, but the 'Variable-size signal' parameter for the block is set to 'No'.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInportInvalidMatrixData">When loading a matrix input, the blocks loading the corresponding data columns of the matrix must specify dimension using a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingUnsupportedDimensions">The dimensions field of structure variable ''{0}'' must be a scalar or a vector with two elements and must match the dimensions of the signal stored in the values field.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidValueDimensions">The value of the dimensions field of structure variable ''{0}'' is out of range for the 'Port dimensions' specified for the block. The valueDimensions for structure variable ''{0}'' must be in the range of 0 to {1,number,integer} ('Port dimensions' specified in the block).</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDifferentNumTSteps">Invalid structure format. The last dimension of each values field must be the same as the number of rows in the valueDimensions field.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingVarDimsNumDimsMismatch">The number of value columns in the valueDimensions field does not match the number of dimensions of the signal.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDiscCannotInterp">Invalid setting for 'Interpolate' block parameter. When a workspace variable does not specify time, turn off interpolation for the corresponding block.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDiscSampleTime">Invalid 'Sample time' for root level Inport block. When the external input corresponding to an Inport does not specify time values, 'Sample time' must be discrete.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingDifferentNumRows">Invalid format specified for structure variable ''{0}''. Number of rows for time and data values must match.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvNumSignalsInStructFormat">The number of signals in loaded structure variable ''{0}'' does not match the number of root-level input blocks, which includes Enable blocks and Trigger blocks with 'Trigger type' set to rising, falling, or either. Specify external input data as a comma-separated list of structure variables, or update the structure so the number of signals matches the number of root-level Inport blocks in the model.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidFcnCallNoOffsetTime">Port is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({0}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({1}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidFcnCallTime">Port is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The difference between time value ({0}) specified by this variable and the offset ({1}) specified on the port is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({2}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingInvalidFcnCallTimeBaseRate">Port is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({0}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({1}) of the model.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingSimDatastoreStr">Input data ''{0}'' uses string data type, which is not supported when loading matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore objects.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingMultiColumnTimetablePortMismatch">The number of variables in external input timetable ''{0}'' must match the number of root-level Inport blocks, {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingMultiColumnTimetableVarsMismatch">Too many input arguments. When a timetable maps to multiple input ports, the timetable must be the only item specified as the external input.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingMultiColumnTimetableLeafMismatch">The number of variables in timetable ''{0}'' must match the number of leaves in the bus specified by root-level Input block ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="LoadingNonScalarBlockData">Input data ''{0}'' of type Simulink.SimulationData.BlockData must be scalar.</entry>
    <!-- Flexible From Workspace Errors -->
    <entry key="FlexibleFromWksDstOnly">Flexible From Workspace block only supports loading matlab.io.datastore.SimulationDatastore objects.</entry>

    <!-- Bus Element Port Errors -->
    <entry key="BusElementPortOverspecified">Input data ''{0}'' does not correspond to any bus element port.</entry>
    <entry key="BusElementPortNonSupportedStruct">Input data (''{0}'') loaded by In Bus Element block ''{1}'' must be a scalar structure with scalar SimulationDatastore, timeseries, or timetable objects at the leaf nodes or an object derived from Simulink.SimulationData.BlockData whose Values field is a structure that meets those requirements.</entry>
    <entry key="BusElementPortNonLeafElement">In Bus Element block ''{0}'' must specify an individual (nonbus) signal based on external input data.</entry>
    <entry key="BusElementPortInvalidStructForPartialSpec">In Bus Element block ''{0}'' selects bus element ''{1}''. The input data structure (''{2}'') for this block must partially or fully match the signal hierarchy of the bus element.</entry>
    <entry key="BusElementPortTimeExpression">Unable to load external input data {0}. In Bus Element blocks do not support loading time expressions.</entry>
    <entry key="MessageInportNotEmpty">Inport block ''{0}'' is configured to generate a message and can load only empty ([]) external input data.</entry>
    <entry key="LegacyFormatPhaseOut">In a future release, loading these data types as simulation input will not be supported: Simulink.Timeseries, Simulink.TsArray, Simulink.SubsysDataLogs, ScopeDataLogs, and StateflowDataLogs.</entry>
    <entry key="LegacyFormatNotSupported">Loading these data types as simulation input is not supported: Simulink.Timeseries, Simulink.TsArray, Simulink.SubsysDataLogs, ScopeDataLogs, and StateflowDataLogs.</entry>
    
    <!-- Software Architecture Function Hit Time Evaluation Errors -->
    <entry key="FunctionHitTimeEvalErr">Invalid value ''{0}'' for 'Hit Times' property of function ''{1}''.</entry>    
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  Datastore datastore ismissing simulinkfixes nonbus
-->
