<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <!-- ECB edit time warning START-->
        <entry key='ObsoleteSlEnvironmentControllerBlock'>Environment Controller block will be removed</entry>
        <entry key='ObsoleteSlEnvironmentControllerBlock_cause'>Replace Environment Controller block with Variant Source block with the Variant control mode parameter set to 'sim codegen switching'. Use &lt;a href="matlab: internallinktoadvisor.launchAdvisor(bdroot);"&gt;Model Advisor&lt;/a&gt; to do this automatically.</entry>
        <entry key='ObsoleteSlEnvironmentControllerBlockCauseWithArg'>Environment Controller block will be removed in a future release. Replace Environment Controller block ''{0}'' with Variant Source block with the Variant control mode parameter set to 'sim codegen switching'. Use &lt;a href="matlab: internallinktoadvisor.launchAdvisor(bdroot);"&gt;Model Advisor&lt;/a&gt; to do this automatically.</entry>
        <!-- ECB edit time warning END-->
        <!-- ECB to variant source Model Advisor Check START-->
        <entry key="MAObsoleteBlksTaskTitle">Replacing Blocks That Will Be Removed</entry>
        <entry key="MAObsoleteBlksTaskTitleTips">Replace blocks that have been removed or will be removed in a future release</entry>
        <entry key="MATitleReplaceECBByVariantSource">Identify Environment Controller blocks to be replaced with Variant Source blocks</entry>
        <entry key="MATitletipReplaceECBByVariantSource">Identify all Environment Controller blocks and replace them with Variant Source blocks with the Variant control mode parameter set to 'sim codegen switching'.</entry>
        <entry key="MAReplaceECBByVariantSourceActionButtonName">Replace blocks</entry>
        <entry key="MAReplaceECBByVariantSourceActionDescription">Click here to replace Environment Controller blocks with Variant Source blocks. Save the model to keep these changes.</entry>
        <entry key="MAMsgReplaceECBByVariantSourceWarn">The Environment Controller block will be removed in a future release. These Environment Controller blocks have been identified in the model:</entry>
        <entry key="MAMsgReplaceECBByVariantSourceSuggest"><![CDATA[<p /> Replace the listed blocks with Variant Source blocks. Click Replace blocks and save your model. ]]></entry>
        <entry key="MAMsgReplaceECBByVariantSourcePass">The model does not contain any Environment Controller blocks.</entry>
        <entry key="MAReplaceECBByVariantSourceActionResults">The Environment Controller blocks in the model have been replaced with these Variant Source blocks. Save the model to keep these changes:</entry>
        <entry key="MAEmptyObjectError">Model Advisor failed to load.</entry>
        <!-- ECB to variant source Model Advisor Check END-->
        <entry key="MATitleIdentifyNonSVCBlksWithInherit">Identify variant blocks with VariantActivation set to ''inherit from Simulink.VariantControl'' but do not use Simulink.VariantControl</entry>
        <entry key="MATitletipIdentifyNonSVCBlksWithInherit">Identify the variant blocks that do not use Simulink.VariantControl objects for the Variant control expressions but have Variant Activation time set to ''inherit from Simulink.VariantControl''.</entry>
        <entry key="MAInheritVATByTaskDisplay">Inherit from Simulink.VariantControl</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  ECB
-->
