<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="nav">
    <message>
        <entry key="EncodingSizeMustBeZero">
            EncodingSize must be zero when the dataset has a single column containing paths.
        </entry>
        <entry key="DropoutProbabilitiesSize">
            Length of the DropoutProbabilities vector must be smaller than or equal to the HiddenSizes vector.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectDatasetSize">
            Number of columns in the dataset must be equal to 1 or 2.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectStateBoundsMPNET">
            Number of states in the StateBounds property of the mpnetSE2 object must be equal to the NumStateVariables property of the stateSpaceSE2 object.
        </entry>
        <entry key="MinimumNumLayers">
            Number of layers in Network property must be greater than or equal to 2.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectLastLayer">
            Last layer in the Network property must be a fullyConnectedLayer.
        </entry>
        <entry key="DLNetworkMustBeScalar">
            The Network input must be a scalar.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectNetworkInputSize">
            Minimum number of inputs to the Network must be equal to {0}.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncompatibleNetworkInputSizeAndEncodingSize">
            Product of elements in the EncodingSize vector must be equal to {0}.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectNetworkOutputSize">
            Number of outputs from the Network must be equal {0}.
        </entry>
        <entry key="EnvironmentMustBeSpecified">
            Environment must be specified as an input, if the 'EncodingSize' value of MPNet non zero.
        </entry>
        <entry key="MaxAttemptsExceeded">
            {0} start and goal pairs were found. Increase the maximum number of attempts to generate the desired number of start and goal pairs.
        </entry>
        <entry key="InvalidStateValidator">
            Missing property name or value. Input state validator object must have a property named 'Map' or 'Environment' with a valid value.
        </entry>
        <entry key="IncompatibleStateValidatorAndMPNET">
            For mpnet of class ''{0}'', the number of state space variables in the StateSpace property of the state validator must be equal to {1}.
            <!-- E.g., For mpnet of class 'mpnetSE2', the number of state space variables in the StateSpace property of the state validator must be equal to 3. -->
        </entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
