<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="nav">
    <message>
        <entry key="InvalidLinkWeightFcn"> Incorrect function handle. The Link weight function signature must be: function [cost] = functionName(STATE1,STATE2) or function [cost] = functionName(STATEID1,STATEID2,GRAPHOBJ). </entry>
        <entry key="InvalidStateInput"> Each state vector must have two or more elements.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidWeightInput"> The number of rows in 'Weight' argument must be equal to the number of links. </entry>
        <entry key="InvalidNameInput"> The number of rows in 'Name' argument must be equal to the number of states.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidNameValuePairs"> Invalid input combination. {0} input only supports 'LinkWeightFcn' name-value argument. </entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFindStateInput"> stateData argument must be a column vector of character vectors, column vector of string scalars, cell array of character vectors, matrix with each row representing a state vector, or table that has all columns identical to the States table.</entry>
        <entry key="StatesInLinkNotFound"> Link.EndStates have stateID which is not present.
        Expected EndStates to be an array with all of the values less than or equal to {0}.  </entry>
        <entry key="CodegenNotSupported"> Code generation is not supported for this function.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidUpdate"> Updating {0} is not valid.</entry>
        <entry key="StatesNotPresent"> navGraph is empty. Links cannot be added without states.</entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectNumOfInputColumn">
            <!--{0}: States / Links property-->
            <!--{1}: state / link -->
            <!--{2}: number of columns in the table -->
            Incorrect number of input arguments.
            The table in the {0} property of the navGraph object contains {2} column variables to define a {1}.
            To add a new {1}, you must specify all the {2} variables in the same order.
        </entry>
        <entry key="MismatchedColumns"> Column names of input must match with the columns of ''{0}'' table.</entry>
        <entry key="EditEndStates"> Updating the 'EndStates' column is not supported. Use addlink or rmlink instead.</entry>
        <entry key="SetStates"> Direct editing of 'States' is not supported. Use addstate or rmstate instead. </entry>
        <entry key="SetLinks"> Direct editing of 'Links' is not supported. Use addlink or rmlink instead. </entry>
        <entry key="MissingNameColumn"> 'Name' argument must be specified when the links input contains state names.</entry>
        <entry key="NameColumnDuplicates"> 'Name' column in the 'States' table must not contain duplicate names.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
