<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2017-2021 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<!-- Error Definitions for the OMPL wrapper MCOS Code -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="nav">
  <message>

    <!-- Errors used in the OMPL MCOS Code -->
    <entry key="InvalidOMPLObject">Invalid OMPL object used as an argument. Expected objects of type:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDataType">Expected {0} to be of type {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDataSize">{0} is not compatible with a 2D state space. Expected the vector to have dimensions [{1,number,integer}, {2,number,integer}].</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBoundaries">{0} is not a valid boundary, the lower bound is greater than or equal to the upper boundary.</entry>
    <entry key="StateOutOfBounds">{0} falls outside of the bounds of the defined state space. Truncating to fit within the defined limits of the state space.</entry>
    <entry key="MapUninitialized">Occupancy Map has not yet been assigned, the planner will solve under the assumption that all states in the designated state space are valid</entry>
    <entry key="NoSolutionAvailible">No path information exists as no solution has been found yet. Either "solve" has not yet been called, or it was unsuccessful in finding a valid path.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFiniteData">Data is non-finite (Inf or -Inf), expected finite value.</entry>
    <entry key="NanData">Data is Not A Number (NaN), expected a real number input</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMapDimensions">Invalid map data. Expected map data to have dimension {0}, instead the map data had dimension {1}.</entry>

    <!-- Errors to used in the MATLAB OmplInterface class -->
    <entry key="InterfaceNoSolutionAvailable">No solution exists yet. Either solve has not been called, or the planner was unable to find a valid solution to the planning problem.</entry>
    <entry key="InterfaceSolverSoftTimeout">The time to solve for a path is larger than or equal to the specified timeout, the solution provided may be incomplete</entry>
    <entry key="InterfaceSolutionFailure">A solution was not able to be calculated for the problem as defined. Please review the parameters to ensure that there exists a possible path to the goal state</entry>
    <entry key="InterfaceInvalidPlannerType">Invalid planner type for OmplInterface.PlannerType. Choices are: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="InterfaceInvalidStateSpaceType">Invalid state space type for OmplInterface.StateSpaceType. Choices are: {0}.</entry>

  </message>
</rsccat>
