<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="nav">
  <message>
    <entry key="MinPathPoints">Path argument must contain minimum of 3 path points for optimization.</entry> 
    <entry key="InvalidPathInput">Invalid value for path argument. Value must be a double matrix of size N-by-2 or N-by-3.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidArgument">Invalid argument at position 2. The second argument of optimizePath function must be binaryOccupancyMap, occupancyMap, vehicleCostmap, or optimizePathOptions class.</entry> 
    <entry key="CutoffLessThanInclusion">ObstacleCutOffDistance must be greater than ObstacleInclusionDistance.</entry>
    <entry key="DelTVelGreaterThanMap">ReferenceDeltaTime*MaxVelocity is greater than the diagonal of the map. Either increase map size, reduce ReferenceDeltaTime, or reduce MaxVelocity.</entry>
    <entry key="InputPathOutsideMap">Some or all poses in the path are out of map bounds. Path must be in world frame. Choose a different path or map.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStart">Start state of the path is not obstacle-free. Choose a different start state or map.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidGoal">Goal state of the path is not obstacle-free. Choose a different goal state or map.</entry>
    <entry key="DelTVelGreaterThanSafetyMargin">ReferenceDeltaTime * MaxVelocity is greater than 2*ObstacleSafetyMargin, this can lead to path skipping over obstacles. Either increase ObstacleSafetyMargin, reduce ReferenceDeltaTime, or reduce MaxVelocity.</entry>
    <entry key="SafetyMarginGreaterThanMap">2*ObstacleSafetyMargin is greater than the diagonal of the map. Increase map size or reduce ObstacleSafetyMargin.</entry>
    <entry key="TrajectoryParameters">Trajectory Parameters</entry>
    <entry key="ObstacleParameters">Obstacle Parameters</entry>
    <entry key="SolverParameters">Solver Parameters</entry>
    <entry key="Weights">Weights</entry>
    <entry key="PoseMoreThanMaxPathStates">Unable to reduce the number of poses in path less than the value of MaxPathStates. Either increase the value of MaxPathStates or ReferenceDeltaTime.</entry>
    <entry key="NumPoseTooLarge">Number of poses in the path is large. Reduce the number of poses in the path or increase the value of ReferenceDeltaTime.</entry>
    <entry key="InputPathOrthogonality">The input path must contain at least one pose where the travel direction is non-orthogonal to the orientation vector. The travel direction is distance vector connecting the consecutive poses of the input path.</entry>
    <entry key="AngleBetweenPosesLarge">The angle differences between consecutive poses in the input path are more than 90 degrees. Improve the output by interpolating input path to reduce the angle differences.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
