<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2012-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->

<!--
This file contains the text for messages produced by the
Code Analyzer Refactoring module.
-->

<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="CodeAnalyzer">
    <message>
        <entry key="Arguments">Refactoring selected code that is in or contains an arguments block is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="SyntaxError">Refactoring is not supported in a file that contains syntax errors.</entry>
        <entry key="Classdef">Refactoring is not supported in a class definition. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ClassdefFile">Refactoring is not supported in a class definition file.</entry>
        <entry key="ClearUsage">The selection cannot be analyzed for refactoring unless the variables to clear are specified explicitly. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideAtDirectory">Refactoring is not supported in a file in a class folder.</entry>
        <entry key="PartialStatement">Selection must contain one or more complete statements.</entry>
        <entry key="FunctionDefinition">Refactoring selected code that contains function definitions is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideLoop">Refactoring is not supported inside a loop. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideNestedFunction">Refactoring is not supported inside a nested function. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideParforLoop">Refactoring is not supported inside a parfor loop. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="LocalFunctionCallToExternal">Selection that is converted to a function in a separate file must not contain local function calls. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="LocalFunctionCallToLiveTask">Selection that is converted to a live task must not contain local function calls. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="LoadUsage">To clarify which variables are needed in the refactored code, specify variables to load from the file. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="SaveUsage">To ensure the intended variables are saved after refactoring, specify variables to save to the file. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="NestedFunctionCall">Refactoring selected code that contains nested function calls is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="GlobalUsage">Refactoring selected code that contains global variables is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="PersistentUsage">Refactoring selected code that contains persistent variables is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ImportUsage">Refactoring is not supported within the scope of an import list. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ReturnUsage">Refactoring selected code that contains return statements is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidContinueBreak">Selection must contain the loop that uses the break or continue statement. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ParforStatement">Refactoring selected code that contains parfor statements is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="TransparencyViolation">To be analyzable, the script or function containing the selection must not use ''{0}''. See line {1,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="IntrospectionViolation">Refactoring selected code that contains a variable or function call that depends on the current function context is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="AnsUsage">Script or function containing the selection must not use 'ans'. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideFunction">Refactoring to a live task is not supported inside a function. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="PartialBlockComment">Refactoring selected code that contains an incomplete block comment is not supported. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>

        <!--
            Depending on how the editor team decides to show messages when users refactor in a case with a warning, these messages may need to be adjusted.
        -->

        <entry key="InsideLoopRelaxedWarning">Variables defined and used within a loop may be excluded as necessary input or output for function refactoring. Verify the input and output of your refactored function. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="InsideLoopRelaxedError">Refactoring to a live task is not supported inside a loop. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ClearUsageRelaxedWarning">Ensure that the variables originally intended to be cleared are still properly cleared following refactoring. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>
        <entry key="ClearUsageRelaxedError">To refactor to a live task, allow the selection to be analyzed by specifying variables to clear explicitly. See line {0,number,integer} of the current file.</entry>

    </message>
</rsccat>
