<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
      <entry key="WrongHeight">Both tables must have the same height for this operation.</entry>
      <entry key="FunWrongHeight">Applying the function ''{0}'' to variable ''{1}'' must return an output with the same height.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidObjectArray">This operation is not defined between ''{0}'' and ''{1}''. The input that is not a table or timetable must be a numeric or logical array.</entry>
      <entry key="ArrayWrongHeight">The height of the array input must be the same as the height of the table or it must be 1.</entry>
      <entry key="ArrayWrongWidth">The width of the array input must be the same as the width of the table or it must be 1.</entry>
      <entry key="NDArray">N-dimensional arrays are not supported for this operation when one of the inputs is a table.</entry>
      <entry key="DifferentVars">Both tables must have the same variables.</entry>
      <entry key="DifferentRowLabels">Both inputs must have the same row labels.</entry>
      <entry key="MixedRowLabels">Both inputs must have the same type of row labels.</entry>
      <entry key="ImplicitExpansionRowLabels">Both inputs must have the same height. Implicit expansion is not supported when the 1 row input has row labels.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleUnits">The input tables have incompatible VariableUnits for this operation.</entry>
      <entry key="AssumeSameUnits">One or more table variables have the VariableUnits defined for one input and not for the other. The operator ''{0}'' assumes the undefined unit to match the other unit.</entry>
      <entry key="AssumeUnitless">One or more table variables have the VariableUnits defined for one input and not for the other. The operator ''{0}'' assumes the undefined unit to mean unitless.</entry>
      <entry key="CustomPropsClash">Arithmetic operations are not supported when the same custom property name is a per-table property in one table and a per-variable property in the other table.</entry>
      <entry key="MinMaxLinearIndices">Linear indices output I is not supported for tabular inputs.</entry>
      <entry key="MinMaxAllLinearIndices">Indices output I is not supported for tabular inputs when applying ''{0}'' over all elements.</entry>
      <entry key="MultiColumnVarAmbiguous">All variables must be column vectors when the dimension input is greater than 1.</entry>
      <entry key="TabularVarAmbiguous">Variables cannot be tabular when the dimension input is greater than 1.</entry>
      <entry key="RowOperationUnitsMismatch">Row operation requires all variables to have the same unit.</entry>
      <entry key="UnsortedRowtimes">Row times must be sorted (ascending) to use ''{0}'' on a timetable input.</entry>
      <entry key="FunWrongSize">The output of this function must match the size of the input.</entry>
      <entry key="VarFunFailed">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the variable ''{1}'' generated an error.</entry>
      <entry key="RowFunFailed">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the rows of the input table generated an error.</entry>
      <entry key="FunFailed">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the input table generated an error.</entry>
      <entry key="VarReductionWrongHeight">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one row when applied to variable ''{1}'' in the input table.</entry>
      <entry key="RowReductionWrongHeight">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the rows of the input table must return an output with the same height.</entry>
      <entry key="NoopReductionWrongHeight">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the input table with an empty vector of dimensions or a dimension argument greater than 2 must return an output with the same height.</entry>
      <entry key="ReductionWrongHeight">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one row when applied to the input table.</entry>
      <entry key="ReductionWrongWidth">The function ''{0}'' returned an output with more than one column when applied to the input table.</entry>
      <entry key="DiffND">Dimension input cannot be greater than 2 to use ''diff'' on a tabular input.</entry>
      <entry key="TabularOption">Argument at position {0} cannot be of type ''{1}''.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>