<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>
    <entry key="resolutionLevelSizesBeyondImageDims" note="Occurs only in constructor">Resolution level sizes must be less than or equal to the number of rows and columns in the image.</entry>
    <entry key="multiresolutionNotSupportedByAdapter" note="Happens when trying to write multiresolution images">This adapter does not support multiresolution imagery.</entry>
    <entry key="missingClassNamesOrLabelIDs" note="Occurs only in constructor">The ClassName and PixelLabelIDs parameter must be specified at the same time.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownPixelFormat" note="The file format contains an unknown color type">Unknown pixel format.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedPixelFormat" note="The file format contains a color type we can't handle">Unsupported pixel format: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="partialReadsNotSupported" note="">This file format does not support partial file reading.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidResolutionLevel" note="Resolution level is the requested magnification level in the multiresolution image">Resolution level must be an integer in the range [1, {0}].</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLocation" note="">The location is not within the image extents.</entry>
    <entry key="readallNotSupported" note="'readall' is a method name">The readall method is not supported for datastores that use bigimage.</entry>
    <entry key="missingInfoFields" note="'infoStruct' is an input variable">infoStruct must have the following fields: Level, ImageNumber, BlockStartWorld, BlockEndWorld</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleResultSizes" note="'apply' is a method name">Output {0} of apply for the block at location ({1}, {2}) had the wrong size.\nExpected ({3}, {4}). Result was ({5}, {6}).</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFile" note="">Invalid file or file not present.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFileMode" note="">Invalid file mode, only 'r' and 'w' allowed</entry>
    <entry key="nitfWriteNotAllowed" note="">NITF write not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="rsetWriteNotAllowed" note="">RSET write not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="tiffImagesDoNotMatch" note="BitsPerSample and SamplesPerPixel are fields of IMFINFO. This says that a single file, having many images in it, dont all have the same value for these fields">All TIFF images (levels) do not have the same BitsPerSample or SamplesPerPixel. bigimage properties will be derived from the finest level image.</entry>
    <entry key="tiffUnsupportedFormat" note="">Unsupported TIFF options.</entry>
    <entry key="logScaleNotSupported" note="log scale on an axes is not supported by bigimshow">Log scale axes are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="transformNotSupported" note="">transform objects are not supported as a Parent of bigimageshow object.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownImageFormat" note="">Could not determine the file format for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="doesNotExist">Could not find file: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="applyNotImageOrParameter" note="">The fourth argument to apply must be an array of optional bigimage inputs or a parameter name.</entry>
    <entry key="maskTooManyLevels" note="">Masks must have only one level.</entry>
    <entry key="maskChannels" note="">Masks must have only one channel.</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleMaskSizes" note="">Masks must have the same X and Y world limits as the bigimage. Check that the images have the same size.</entry>
    <entry key="nothingToApply" note="">The mask supplied resulted in no blocks being processed. Use a different mask or adjust the InclusionThreshold parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="maskAndThresholdMismatch" note="Happens when setting MaskThresholds">Expected either one value for MaskThreshold or one for each mask.</entry>
    <entry key="categoricalRequiresLabelsAndClasses" note="Happens during construction">Specifying a datatype of 'categorical' requires also specifying the 'PixelLabelIDs' and 'Classes' properties.</entry>
    <entry key="categoricalIgnoresDatatype" note="Happens during construction">When providing Classes and PixelLabelIDs, the datatype will always be "categorical".</entry>
    <entry key="allOutOfBounds" note="Happens when reading data">The area defined by regionStartWorld and regionEndWorld does not overlap the image data.</entry>
    <entry key="waitbarTitle" note="Retain the % sign, its filled in with a number">Processing %d blocks</entry>
    <entry key="waitbarTitleGUI" note="">Processing:</entry>
    <entry key="waitbarCompletedTxt" note="Retain the % sign, its filled in a number each">Completed %d of %d blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="extraImageLevelsValue" note="">ExtraImageLevels values must be less than or equal to the number of levels in the corresponding image.</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleExtents" note="">ExtraImages must have the same spatial extents as the bigimage. Use the ExtraImageLevels parameter if necessary.</entry>
    <entry key="scalarAdapter" note="">Expected Adapter to be a scalar object.</entry>
    <entry key="oneShouldBeNaN" note="">One element of the required image size should be NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="onlyDownSize" note="">Requested image size should be smaller than the image size at specified reference level. </entry>
    <entry key="addingNewLevel" note="This is adding a new image level to the existing bigimage object">Adding a new lower resolution level</entry>
    <entry key="processingNBlocks" note="Leave the %d as-is, code fills it in">Resizing %d blocks</entry>
    <entry key="endShouldBeGreaterThanOrEqualToStart" note="">REGIONEND should be greater than, or equal to REGIONSTART</entry>
    <entry key="tiffChannelCount" note="This happens when writing new TIFF files">Only 1- and 3-channel TIFF files are currently supported.</entry>
    <entry key="couldNotOpenPool" note="This is thrown by apply()">UseParallel requires Parallel Computing Toolbox and a parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="amountOfBlockData" note="">The specified block is bigger than the image's block size or has the wrong number of channels.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedInterpolation" note="">Only nearest neighbor interpolation is supported for categorical data</entry>
    <entry key="NoWriteSupport" note="">This bigimage adapter does not support writing operation.</entry>
    <entry key="destinationexists" note="">Cannot overwrite existing file or directory.</entry>
    <entry key="notAValidDir" note="">DIRNAME is not a valid binary block directory name.</entry>
    <entry key="missingDatatype" note="">If NUMCHANNELS is specified, DATATYPE must be specified too.</entry>
    <entry key="readOnlyAdapter" note="">Cannot set block for a read-only bigimage object.</entry>
    <entry key="changedBlockSize" note="">TIFF file format requires block sizes to be multiples of 16. The block size of the written file has been increased to be a multiple of 16.</entry>
    <entry key="imageSizeDoNotMatch" note="">The ImageSize property of the given imref2d object does not match the image size of the underlying image data.</entry>    
    <entry key="notGray" note="">The bigimage input to bigimageshow has 2 channels, only displaying the first as a grayscale image.</entry>
    <entry key="notRGB" note="">The bigimage input to bigimageshow has more than 3 channels, only displaying the first three as an RGB truecolor image.</entry>    
    <entry key="noMoreData" note="">No more data to read. Use reset method to reset the datastore to the start of the data. Before calling the read method, check if data is available to read by using the hasdata method.</entry>
    <entry key="couldNotCreate" note="">Could not create output in specified OutputLocation at {0}. Check if the parent folder is valid and has write permissions for this user.</entry>
    <entry key="parallelLoadFailed" note="">Unable to transfer a bigimage to the workers. Verify that all workers have access to the location specified in the DataSource property of each bigimage object.</entry>
    <entry key="couldNotCreateOutputDir" note="">Could not create output folder {0}. {1}</entry>
    <entry key="spmdRequired" note="">The currently open parpool does not support SPMD. This function requires a parpool with SPMD enabled to run in parallel mode.</entry>
    <entry key="LocationNotAvailableToParallelWorkers" note="">This location ({0}) is not a valid file or folder on all workers. If using relative paths, use the following code to change the working directories of the workers: \n spmd\n    cd(relative path root)\n end</entry>
    <entry key="OutputNotAvailableToParallelWorkers" note="">This location ({0}) is not a valid folder on all workers. Specify an OutputLocation value that is a valid path on all workers. If using relative paths, use the following code to change the working directories of the workers: \n spmd\n    cd(relative path root)\n end</entry>
    <entry key="dataChannelsIncorrect" note="">bigimage/setBlock expects DATA to have {0} channel(s).</entry>
    <entry key="readRelativeLevelDoestMatch" note="">The given level, {0}, does not match the level specified for this image during construction ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedClassRequired" note="">When using 0 as a value for PixelLabelIDs, an additional mapping for a &lt;undefined&gt; or missing ClassName is required in PixelLabelIDs.</entry>
    <entry key="largeFlatFile" note="">No overview levels found. Displaying a single level image file is inefficient. Use xlim and ylim functions to limit the display region to a smaller region.</entry>
    <entry key="singleStripTiff" note="">The image at level {0} of the {1} is stored in a stripped form, with all image data in a single strip. This format is not ideal for efficient partial reads and will result in slow processing. Consider changing the data source to create tiled TIFF files.</entry>
    <entry key="uniquePixelLabelsIDsRequired" note="">Values of PixelLabelIDs must be unique.</entry>
    <entry key="uniqueClassesRequired" note="">Values of Classes must be unique.</entry>
    <entry key="NotInClasses" note="">UnloadedValue given is not an element of Classes.</entry>
    <entry key="ClassAndIdsNumelShouldMatch" note="">The number of elements in Classes and PixelLabelIDs must be the same.</entry>
    <entry key="readonly" note="Used in custom disp">Read Only Properties.</entry>
    <entry key="readwrite" note="Used in custom disp">Read Write Properties.</entry>
    <entry key="pxidNotColVectorOrMatrix" note="">PixelLabelIDs cell array must be column vectors or M-by-3 matrices.</entry>
    <entry key="pxidNotVectorOrMatrix" note="">PixelLabelIDs must be a vector or M-by-3 matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="missingClassesOrLabelIDs" note="Occurs only in constructor">The Classes and PixelLabelIDs parameter must be specified at the same time.</entry>    
    <entry key="IncorrectRGBSpecification">For RGB data, underlying pixel data should be uint8, three channel RGB values, and PixelLabelIDs must be RGB triplets.</entry>
    <entry key="IncorrectChannelsForCategorical">Number of channels in the DataSource has to be 1 for categorical data.</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedIDShouldBeUnique">UndefinedID ({0}) should not be an element of PixelLabelIDs ({1}). Specify a unique value for UndefinedID which does not exist in the PixelLabelIDs array in the bigimage constructor.</entry>
    <entry key="RGBPixelLabelIDsNotuint8">UndefinedID should be convertible to uint8 type for RGB data.</entry>
    <entry key="RGBUndefinedIDNotuint8">PixelLabelIDs should be convertible to uint8 type for RGB data.</entry>
    <entry key="NotCategorical">Invalid parameters. Classes, PixelLabelIDs or UndefinedID is only applicable for a bigimage object with ClassUnderlying of categorical. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadString">PadMethod is not one of 'replicate', 'symmetric' or a valid categorical class name.</entry>
    <entry key="IDClassesNotEqual">PixelLabelIDs and UndefinedID must have the same class.</entry>    
    <entry key="CategoricalAlphaNotSupported">AlphaData cannot be a categorical bigimage.</entry>       
    <entry key="NotATIFF">TIFFCompression can only be specified when writing to a TIFF file.</entry>
    <entry key="LossyCompression">Categorical data is being written with a lossy compression scheme. Written pixel values will not be limited to the specified PixelLabelIDs.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedExtension">Unsupported file extension. Only .tif and .tiff file formats are supported for writing.</entry>    
    <entry key="classesShouldBeUnique">While writing categorical images, specified Classes must have unique elements.</entry>
    <entry key="padPartialShouldbeTrue">When BatchSize is greater than 1, PadPartialBlocks must be set to true.</entry>
    <entry key="BatchSizeResultIncorrect">When BatchSize is greater than 1, Output cell array must have BatchSize number of entries</entry>    
    <entry key="ScalarStructExpected">When BatchSize is equal to 1, Output struct should be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleWithBLS">Levels, BlockSize, BlockOffsets, Masks or InclusionThreshold cannot be specified when BlockLocationSet is specified.</entry>
    <entry key="badImageNumber">Invalid image indices specified in the ImageNumber field of the specified blockLocationSet. Maximum index value for the given set of bigimages is {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectNumLevels">The input set of bigimages requires {0} number of elements for the Levels property in the blockLocationSet.</entry>
    <entry key="badLevel">Specified level for bigimage at index {0} exceeds the number of levels available ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="outOfBounds">A blocklocation for image index {0} is outside the image bounds.</entry>
    <entry key="expectedScalar">Input is an array. Only scalar blockedImage objects are supported.</entry>
    <entry key="singleChannelAlpha">AlphaData must have a single channel.</entry>    
    <entry key="ClassToBeRemoved">bigimage will be removed in a future release. Use blockedImage instead.</entry>        
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->
