<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>
    <entry key="LevelMismatch" note="">Specified BlockLocationSet object is at a different Level ({0}) than the one being processed ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleSource" note="">Specified source: {0}, cannot be opened with specified adapter: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="unableToCreateDir" note="mkdir is a function">Unable to create directory: {0}, mkdir failed with this message: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSourceFolder" note="description.mat is the name of a file that we expected to find">Invalid blockedImage folder. Specified folder: {0} does not contain a description.mat file.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMultiLevelSetBlockInTIFF" note="">The images.blocked.TIFF adapter does not support writing blocks to multiple levels.</entry>
    <entry key="TIFFLevelIsClosed" note="">This level is closed for writing additional data.</entry>
    <entry key="levelImagesShouldHaveSameDims" note="LevelImages is a name-value pair">All images in LevelImages should have the same number of dimensions as the first blockedImage.</entry>
    <entry key="levelImagesMustbeSingleLevel" note="LevelImages is a name-value pair">All images in LevelImages should contain a single level.</entry>    
    <entry key="cannotOverwrite" note="Hole is the name of the directory">{0} already exists. Cannot overwrite.</entry>        
    <entry key="notInReadMode" note="">Unable to read. 'Mode' is not set to 'r'.</entry>
    <entry key="notInWriteMode" note="">Unable to write. 'Mode' is not set to 'w'.</entry>
    <entry key="cantWriteToInMem" note="">The images.blocked.InMemory adapter cannot be used to write data.</entry>    
    <entry key="h5BlockSizeLargerThanImageSize" note="">images.blocked.H5 Adapter requires IOBlockSize to be less than or equal to the image size.</entry>    
    <entry key="onlyScalarWrite" note="Mode is a name-value pair for the constructor. The first input is the destination parameter.">Cannot open multiple destinations for write. Only one destination is supported when 'Mode' == 'w'.</entry>
    <entry key="writeConstructorIncomplete" note="">When opening a blockedImage in write mode, ImageSize, BlockSize and InitialValue must be specified.</entry>    
    <entry key="invalidImageNumberInBLS" note="">The specified BlockLocationSet argument is not valid. The ImageNumber property of the given BlockLocationSet object must either be all 1's, or less than the number of input blockedImages.</entry>
    <entry key="uniqueBlocksRequired" note="">BlockLocationSet should not contain duplicate block entries.</entry>
    <entry key="nonRegularGridBlocks" note="">BlockLocationSet should contain blocks on a regular BlockSize grid</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedEXT" note="Hole is a file name">Adapter does not support {0}. Write a custom adapter to read data from this source. See images.blocked.Adapter for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="singleResolutionOnly" note="">Detected multiple images in source. This adapter does not support multi-resolution images.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedMeta" note="Hole is a file name">Unsupported BitDepth and Datatype in {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="processingImages" note="%d should NOT be translated, it gets replaced with a number">Processing %d images</entry>
    <entry key="processingBlocks" note="%d should NOT be translated, it gets replaced with a number">Processing %d blocks</entry>
    <entry key="readOnlyProps" note="Title for a display of properties that are read-only">Read only properties</entry>
    <entry key="settableProps" note="Title for a display of properties that can be set">Settable properties</entry>    
    <entry key="various" note="This string is used to indicate that a property has different values across elements of an array">Various</entry>
    <entry key="invalidExtraLevel" note="">ExtraLevels exceeds the number of levels in ExtraImages.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidOutputBatchSize" note="">The last dimension of the output for a block ([{0}]) does not match the expected batch size ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="setPadPartial" note="">When BatchSize>1, PadPartial must be set to true.</entry>
    <entry key="blockSizeAndBlockLocationSet" note="">BlockSize and BlockLocationSet cannot be specified at the same time.</entry>
    <entry key="couldNotFindFile" note="">{0} is not a valid file or a folder name.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidWriteModeArgs" note="">SIZE and INITIALVALUE optional inputs are not supported in read mode.</entry>
    <entry key="noParallelSupport" note="">This adapter does not support parallel mode. An implementation of the openInParallelToAppend method was not detected. See images.blocked.Adapters for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCropEnd" note="">CEND must be greater than CSTART and less than the image size at the finest level.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBlockSub" note="">BLOCKSUB must be less than or equal to [{0}]</entry>
    <entry key="mustHaveNumDimsElements" note="">Must have number of elements that match the number of dimensions in the image.</entry>
    <entry key="mustHaveLessThanOrEqualNumDimsElements" note="">Must have number of elements that is less than or equal to the number of dimensions in the image.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPixelSub" note="">PIXELEND must be greater than PIXELSTART and less that the image size at the specified level.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidGetIOBlockSize" note="0 is the class name of an adapter.">getIOBlock implemented in {0} returned data larger than the expected IOBlockSize at I/O level {1} and block subscript [{2}]</entry>
    <entry key="onlyRModeAllowed" note="">Can not switch to 'w' mode. 'Mode' can only be set to 'w' in the constructor.</entry>
    <entry key="cantSetBlockSizeInWriteMode" note="">BlockSize can not be set when 'Mode' is 'w'.</entry>
    <entry key="destinationMustBeEmpty" note="">When using images.blocked.InMemory, DESTINATION must be set to [].</entry>
    <entry key="adapterMustBeInMemory" note="">When DESTINATION is [], Adapter specified must be images.blocked.InMemory.</entry>
    <entry key="outputLocationRequired" note="">OutputLocation is required for the specified Adapter(s).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedOutput" note="">Unsupported output. Output of FCN must either be numerical, logical, a scalar struct or a categorical array.</entry>
    <entry key="scalarStructOnly" note="">Output of FCN must be a scalar struct.</entry>
    <entry key="resumeNotSupported" note="">This adapter does not support the Resume mode of operation.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDescription" note="">{0} does not contain a valid Adapter description</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindWriteAdapter" note="">Unable to find a suitable Adapter. Specify an Adapter explicitly with the Adapter Name-Value pair.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNumCols" note="0 is a property name">Invalid {0}. {0} has more columns than NumDimensions of the blockedImage</entry>
    <entry key="notAllLevels" note="0 is a property name">Invalid {0}. {0} must be a single row, or it must be specified for all levels of the blockedImage.</entry>
    <entry key="missingInfoFields" note="0 is the class name of an adapter object, 1 is a list of fields of a structure">The implementation of getInfo in {0} returned a structure with these fields: {1}. This does not contain all the required fields: Size, IOBlockSize, Datatype and InitialValue. See help images.blocked.Adapter/getInfo for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectInfo" note="0 is the class name of the adapter">info struct returned by getInfo of {0} does not contain a scalar struct.</entry>
    <entry key="sizesNotConsistent" note="0 is the classname of the adapter">In the info struct returned by getInfo of {0}, Size and BlockSize are not of the same size.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDatatype" note="0 is the classname of the adapter">In the info struct returned by getInfo of {0}, Datatype was not a string array with one element for each level.</entry>
    <entry key="inconsistentNumDims" note="">All blockedImages in the input array must have the same number of dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNumDims" note="0 is a prop name">Specified {0} does not have the same number of dimensions as the input array of blockedImages.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedFormat" note="0 is a file extension like bmp, jpg">images.blocked.GenericImageBlock Adapter does not support {0} format.</entry>
    <entry key="cantChangeExtension" note="">Changing the BlockFormat for this adapter is not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="openToWriteIsNotImplemented" note="">openToWrite is not implemented in this adapter. This adapter does not support any writing operation.</entry>
    <entry key="openInParallelNotImplemented" note="">openInParallelToAppend is not implemented in this adapter. This adapter cannot be used when "UseParallel" is true.</entry>
    <entry key="setIOBlockNotImplemented" note="">setIOBlock is not implemented in this adapter. This adapter does not support writing.</entry>
    <entry key="alreadyWrittenNotImplemented" note="">alreadyWritten is not implemented in this adapter. This adapter does not support Resume operation.</entry>
    <entry key="singleBlockOnly" note="">Cannot use images.blocked.GenericImage adapter with multiple I/O blocks. This adapter supports images files with a single I/O block which encompasses the whole image.</entry>
    <entry key="grayAndRGBTIFFOnly" note="">images.blocked.TIFF adapter only supports Grayscale (M-by-N) and RGB (M-by-N-by-3) images.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedTIFF" note="">images.blocked.TIFF adapter does not support this format of TIFF files. Consider writing a custom Adapter using the Tiff object. For more information on how to write one, see images.blocked.Adapter</entry>        
    <entry key="firstBlockShouldBeFull" note="">First input block is a partial block. To accurately determine output size, the first input block must be of specified BlockSize. Reduce BlockSize to ensure that the first block is always full.</entry>
    <entry key="inconsistentTypes" note="For example: Image number 5 is not of type uint8">All blockedImages must have the same ClassUnderlying type. Image number {0} is not of type {1}</entry>
    <entry key="classesWasProvided" note="">The input blockedImages are categorical. Classes and PixelLabelIDs must not be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="classesNotProvided" note="">The input blockedImages are not categorical. Classes and PixelLabelIDs must be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedType" note="">blockedImages of type {0} are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="inconsistentCategories" note="">Expected categorical ordering derived from the first image is {0}. But image {1} has {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="onlySingleLevel" note="">This adapter only supports single resolution level images.</entry>
    <entry key="maskMoreDimsThanImage" note="">The MASK blockedImage has higher number of dimensions than the input blockedImage</entry>
    <entry key="cannotAppendToDestination" note="">This Adapter does not support opening a destination in append mode.</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleAppend" note="Hole is a property name, e.g. ImageSize, BlockSize or InitialValue">Existing blockedImage data in DESTINATION is not compatible with the constructor parameters. Parameter {0} is not the same.</entry>    
    <entry key="onlyGrayOrRGBblockedImage" note="">bigimageshow only supports MxN numeric, logical or categorical image or MxNx3 numeric images.</entry>
    <entry key="emptyResult" note="">FCN returned empty data.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadValueClass" note="">Invalid PADMETHOD, expected a scalar value of type {0}</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadValueStruct" note="">Invalid PADMETHOD, expected struct scalar to have the same fieldnames as the InitialValue of the first blockedImage in the input array.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadValueCat" note="">Invalid PADMETHOD, expected categorical input to have the same categories as the InitialValue of the first blockedImage in the input array.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedByAdapter" note="">The {0} Adapter does not support the following type: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="onlySingleResolutionGrayOrRGB" note="">This Adapter only supports single resolution MxN logical, MxN uint8 or MxNx3 uint8 blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="onlyGrayOrRGB" note="">This Adapter only supports MxN logical, MxN uint8 or MxNx3 uint8 blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="onlyGrayOrRGBu16" note="">This Adapter only supports MxN logical, MxN uint8/uint16 or MxNx3 uint8/uint16 blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="endMustBeGreaterThanStart" note="">WorldStart must be less than WorldEnd.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidAdapterHandle" note="">Specified Adapter value is an invalid object handle.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToWriteBlock" note="0 is a file name">Unable to create and open {0} for writing. Ensure folder has write permissions and enough disk space.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidH5" note="0 is a file name">{0} is not a valid HDF5 file created by the images.blocked.H5 adapter.</entry>
    <entry key="noMoreData" note="">No more data to read. Use reset method to reset the datastore to the start of the data. Before calling the read method, check if data is available to read by using the hasdata method.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidUserData" note="Hole is the name of a class">{0} returned invalid UserData. UserData must be a scalar structure.</entry>
    <entry key="fieldNamesMismatch" note="">Field names in BLOCKDATA do not match field names in the InitialValue property.</entry>
    <entry key="categoriesMismatch" note="">Categories in BLOCKDATA do not match the categories of InitialValue property.</entry>
    <entry key="pixelSubsTooLarge" note="">PIXELSUBS must be less than image size (SIZE property).</entry>
    <entry key="unableToFindReadAdapter" note="0 is an existing folder">Unable to find a suitable Adapter to read {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="outOfBoundBlocks" note="">The given BLOCKLOCATIONSET contains blocks which are outside the image bounds.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectBlockSize" note="">For block subscript [{0}], received DATA of size [{1}]. DATA has to match BlockSize of [{2}].</entry>
    <entry key="exceedsSizeInBlock" note="">BLOCKSUB exceeds the number of blocks in image.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectArraylength" note="">The given BLOCKLOCATIONSET requires an input blockedImage array of size {0}</entry>
    <entry key="emptyInput" note="">Input was an empty blockedImage (blockedImage()). Unable to process.</entry>
    <entry key="parallelNeedsOutputLocation" note="">When UseParallel is true, OutputLocation must be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="blockSizeNotMod16" note="">TIFF files require blockSize to be multiples of 16.</entry>
    <entry key="duplicateSources" note="">Duplicate sources detected.</entry>
    <entry key="invalid3DDimensions" note="">First argument must be a blockedImage with a NumDimensions property value greater than or equal to 3.</entry>    
    <entry key="couldNotSetOutputLocation" note="">Unable to save the output blockedImage to the location specified by the Source property of the input blockedImage. Specify the output location using the OutputLocation name-value argument.</entry>
    <entry key="scalesChangedForTiff" note="">TIFF format requires block sizes to be multiples of 16 pixels. The specified 'Scales' value has been changed to [{0}] to meet this requirement.</entry>
    <entry key="switchingToSerial" note="">The specified 'Adapter' value does not support parallel processing. Switching to serial mode.</entry>      
    <entry key="unsupportedClassForResize" note="">ClassUnderlying property of the input blockedImage must specify a logical, numeric, or categorical data type.</entry>
    <entry key="resizeTitle" note="Used to show a title in the wait bar. The formatting is filled with a single number">Resizing %d blocks</entry>  
    <entry key="NotSameDims" note="">Input blockedImage objects must have the same number of dimensions specified by the NumDimensions property.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectJP2kIOBlockSize" note="">IOBlockSize must have {0} elements to match the number of dimensions in the JPEG2000 image file.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedWriteAllFormat" note="">OutputFormat must be one of {0} when using the default WriteFcn.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInterpolationForCategorical">Invalid Interpolation value for categorical data. Categorical data only supports "nearest" interpolation.</entry>
    <entry key="emptyElement">All input blockedImages should have a non-empty source.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
