<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2018 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>
    <entry key="tooManyOutputArguments" note="">Too many output arguments.  When the ''Destination'' parameter is specified, BLOCKPROC does not return any output.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidOutputClass" note="">Invalid output class.  The user function, FUN, returned an invalid result.  The class of the result was {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="emptyFile" note="">Cannot write empty file.  The user function, FUN, cannot return empty when the ''Destination'' parameter has been specified.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidImageSize" note="">Invalid image size.  BLOCKPROC expects the input image to be M-by-N or M-by-N-by-P.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputImage" note="">Invalid input image.  The input image to BLOCKPROC should be either a numeric matrix, a string or character vector filename, or an ImageAdapter object.  See the documentation for BLOCKPROC for a list of readable file formats and their extensions.  See the documentation for ImageAdapter for information on making ImageAdapter objects.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBlockSize" note="">Invalid block size.  BLOCKPROC expects the BlockSize parameter to be a 1 by 2 positive numeric vector.</entry>
    <entry key="fractionalBlockSize" note="">BLOCKPROC did not expect a fractional ''BlockSize'' parameter.  It will be truncated before use.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFunction" note="">Invalid block function.  BLOCKPROC expects the user function, FUN, to be a valid function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="paramMissingValue" note="">Named parameters must have a corresponding value.</entry>
    <entry key="badParamName" note="">Parameter names be character arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownParamName" note="">Unknown parameter "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="ambiguousParamName" note="">Ambiguous parameter "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="invalidParallelSource" note="">Invalid input image for parallel execution.  When calling BLOCKPROC with the UseParallel option, the input image must be a matrix or a file name of a supported image format.  Instead, it was specified as an ImageAdapter object.  Executing serially.</entry>
    <entry key="FileNotAvailableToParallelWorkers" note="">Input file not available to workers.  The input file is not available to all workers in the parpool.  This is often caused by issues with the PATH on the workers.  Refer to the documentation for &lt;a href="matlab:doc parpool"&gt;parpool&lt;/a&gt; for information on configuring the PATH for workers in the parpool.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDestination" note="">Invalid destination.  The destination for BLOCKPROC, if specified, must be a string or character vector filename or an ImageAdapter object.  See the documentation for BLOCKPROC for a list of writable file formats.  See the documentation for ImageAdapter for information on how these classes are used with BLOCKPROC.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBorderSize" note="">Invalid border size.  BLOCKPROC expects the BorderSize parameter to be a 1 by 2 positive numeric vector.</entry>
    <entry key="fractionalBorderSize" note="">BLOCKPROC did not expect a fractional ''BorderSize'' parameter.  It will be truncated before use.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadMethodParam" note="">Invalid ''PadMethod'' parameter.  BLOCKPROC expects the PadMethod parameter to be ''replicate'', ''symmetric'', or a scalar value.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPadPartialBlocksParam" note="">Invalid ''PadPartialBlocks'' parameter.  BLOCKPROC expects the PadPartialBlocks parameter to be either true or false.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTrimBorderParam" note="">Invalid ''TrimBorder'' parameter.  BLOCKPROC expects the TrimBorder parameter to a logical scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidUseParallelParam" note="">Invalid ''UseParallel'' parameter.  BLOCKPROC expects the UseParallel parameter to a logical scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="spmdRequired" note="">The currently open parpool does not support SPMD. BLOCKPROC requires a parpool with SPMD enabled to run in parallel mode.</entry>
    <entry key="errorUserSuppliedFunc" note="">BLOCKPROC encountered an error while evaluating the user-supplied function handle, FUN.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->
