<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>      
    <entry key="InsufficientRegistrationPoints" note="">Unable to detect sufficient number of feature points for successful chart import. Check if image is valid and consider increasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>
    <entry key="NotFoundRegistrationPointOne" note="">Unable to detect registration point 1 (top left). Check if image is valid and consider increasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="NotFoundRegistrationPointTwo" note="">Unable to detect registration point 2 (top right). Check if image is valid and consider increasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="NotFoundRegistrationPointThree" note="">Unable to detect registration point 3 (bottom right). Check if image is valid and consider increasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="NotFoundRegistrationPointFour" note="">Unable to detect registration point 4 (bottom left). Check if image is valid and consider increasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="UnalignedRegistrationPoints" note="">Registration points may not be correctly aligned. Check if image is valid and consider decreasing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="IntensityMismatchAlignmentPoints" note="">Detected alignment points may not be correct. Check if image is valid and consider changing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="IntensityMismatchGrayPatches" note="">Detected gray patches may not be correct. Check if image is valid and consider changing detection sensitivity in case no registration points are provided.</entry>    
    <entry key="fitgeotransErrorWrapper" note="">Unable to detect chart due to invalid registration points.</entry>    
    <entry key="invalidROIOrientation" note="">Valid options are 'horizontal', 'vertical' or 'both'.</entry>    
    <entry key="invalidRegistrationPoints" note="">Registration points outside image bounds.</entry>    
    <entry key="noSlantedEdgeROIs" note="">No valid edge ROIs specified.</entry> 
    <entry key="invalidImageFormat" note="">{0} is not a RGB image.</entry>     
    <entry key="smallImageSize" note="">Dimensions of {0} are not large enough for successful chart import.</entry>     
    <entry key="invalidAxes" note="">Parent is not a valid axis handle.</entry>     
    <entry key="ROIContrastSharpnessComment" note="">Sharpness measurement may not be accurate as ROI contrast is less than 20%.</entry>     
    <entry key="SlopeAngleSharpnessComment" note="">Sharpness measurement may not be accurate as slope of slanted edge deviates significantly from 5 degrees.</entry>  
    <entry key="SharpnessTableDescription" note="">Sharpness measurement table. The rows of the sharpnessTable correspond to individual slanted edge ROIs numbered as displayed when using the displayChart function.</entry>
    <entry key="ROIIndexVariableDescription" note="">Index of an ROI.</entry> 
    <entry key="SlopeAngleVariableDescription" note="">Measured angle in degrees between the slanted edge and the horizontal or vertical depending on the orientation of the edge.</entry> 
    <entry key="ConfidenceFlagVariableDescription" note="">A flag which is true when sharpness measurement is reliable. It is false when the sharpness measurement is not reliable due to the following conditions, (i) the slopeAngle is less than 3.5 or more than 15 degrees or (ii) the contrast within the ROI is less than 20%.</entry> 
    <entry key="SFRVariableDescription" note="">Table containing SFR measurements for R,G,B and Y edge profiles.</entry> 
    <entry key="CommentVariableDescription" note="">In case confidenceFlag is false, outlines the reason for unreliable sharpness measurement.</entry> 
    <entry key="AggregateSharpnessTableDescription" note="">Average sharpness measurement table.</entry> 
    <entry key="ROIOrientationDescription" note="">Direction of ROI Orientation.</entry> 
    <entry key="MTFVariableDescription" note="">Frequencies for R, G, B and Y at which frequency response is {0}%.</entry> 
    <entry key="MTFPVariableDescription" note="">Frequencies for R, G, B and Y at which frequency response is {0}% of peak frequency response.</entry> 
    <entry key="ChromaticAberrationTableDescription" note="">Chromatic aberration measurement table. The rows of the aberrationTable correspond to individual slanted edge ROIs numbered as displayed when using the displayChart function.</entry>
    <entry key="AberrationVariableDescription" note="">Chromatic aberration measured as the area between the maximum and the minimum R,G and B edge profiles.</entry> 
    <entry key="PercentAberrationVariableDescription" note="">Aberration expressed as a percentage of the distance between the center of the image and the center of the ROI.</entry> 
    <entry key="EdgeProfileVariableDescription" note="">R,G,B and Y edge profiles averaged along the slanted edge.</entry> 
    <entry key="NormalizedEdgeProfileVariableDescription" note="">edgeProfiles normalized between [0,1] using 5% of the front end and tail end data.</entry> 
    <entry key="ColorTableDescription" note="">Color measurement table. The rows of the colorTable correspond to individual color ROIs sequentially numbered as displayed when using the displayChart function.</entry>
    <entry key="Measured_RVariableDescription" note="">Mean of R channel pixels in a ROI.</entry> 
    <entry key="Measured_GVariableDescription" note="">Mean of G channel pixels in a ROI.</entry> 
    <entry key="Measured_BVariableDescription" note="">Mean of B channel pixels in a ROI.</entry> 
    <entry key="Reference_LVariableDescription" note="">Reference L values.</entry> 
    <entry key="Reference_aVariableDescription" note="">Reference a values.</entry> 
    <entry key="Reference_bVariableDescription" note="">Reference b values.</entry> 
    <entry key="Delta_EVariableDescription" note="">Euclidean color distance between measured and reference color values as outlined in CIE76.</entry> 
    <entry key="NoiseTableDescription" note="">Noise measurement table. The rows of the noiseTable correspond to individual gray ROIs sequentially numbered as displayed when using the displayChart function.</entry> 
    <entry key="MeanIntensity_RVariableDescription" note="">Mean of R channel pixels in a ROI</entry>   
    <entry key="MeanIntensity_GVariableDescription" note="">Mean of G channel pixels in a ROI</entry>     
    <entry key="MeanIntensity_BVariableDescription" note="">Mean of B channel pixels in a ROI</entry>   
    <entry key="RMSNoise_RVariableDescription" note="">Root mean square (RMS) noise of R pixels</entry>
    <entry key="RMSNoise_GVariableDescription" note="">Root mean square (RMS) noise of G pixels</entry>
    <entry key="RMSNoise_BVariableDescription" note="">Root mean square (RMS) noise of B pixels</entry>
    <entry key="PercentNoise_RVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise of R expressed as a percentage of the maximum of the original chart image datatype</entry>
    <entry key="PercentNoise_GVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise of G expressed as a percentage of the maximum of the original chart image datatype</entry>
    <entry key="PercentNoise_BVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise of B expressed as a percentage of the maximum of the original chart image datatype</entry>
    <entry key="SignalToNoiseRatio_RVariableDescription" note="">Ratio of signal to noise in R</entry>
    <entry key="SignalToNoiseRatio_GVariableDescription" note="">Ratio of signal to noise in G</entry>
    <entry key="SignalToNoiseRatio_BVariableDescription" note="">Ratio of signal to noise in B</entry>
    <entry key="SNR_RVariableDescription" note="">Signal to noise ratio in dB (20*log(Signal/Noise)) for R</entry>
    <entry key="SNR_GVariableDescription" note="">Signal to noise ratio in dB (20*log(Signal/Noise)) for G</entry>
    <entry key="SNR_BVariableDescription" note="">Signal to noise ratio in dB (20*log(Signal/Noise)) for B</entry>
    <entry key="PSNR_RVariableDescription" note="">Peak signal to noise ratio in dB for R</entry>
    <entry key="PSNR_GVariableDescription" note="">Peak signal to noise ratio in dB for G</entry>
    <entry key="PSNR_BVariableDescription" note="">Peak signal to noise ratio in dB for B</entry>
    <entry key="RMSNoise_YVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise for Y channel in YCbCr color space</entry>
    <entry key="RMSNoise_CbVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise for Cb channel in YCbCr color space</entry>
    <entry key="RMSNoise_CrVariableDescription" note="">RMS noise for Cr channel in YCbCr color space</entry>
    <entry key="esfrChartFigureName" note="">eSFR test chart</entry>
    <entry key="noInstallCVT" note="">Support for distorted charts requires Computer Vision Toolbox.</entry>
    <entry key="noDetectStyle" note="">Unable to detect chart style automatically. Please specify chart style as argument.</entry>
    <entry key="grayChartColorMetrics" note="">Grayscale chart detected. Color metrics may not be useful.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidArgumentPair" note="">Invalid input arguments. Only one argument among RegistrationPoints and Sensitivity can be provided.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->
