<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
    <message>
        <entry key="InvalidEXRFile" note="">Input file must be an EXR file.</entry>
        <entry key="FileReadError" note="">Unable to read file ''{0}''. The OpenEXR library failed with the following error: \n''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="FileWriteError" note="">Unable to write file ''{0}''. The OpenEXR library failed with the following error: \n''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="StringAttrValIncorrectType" note="">''{0}'' attribute value must be a string scalar or character vector.</entry>
        <entry key="NumericScalarAttrValIncorrectType" note="">Invalid data type. ''{0}'' attribute value must be a double scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedAttrValType" note="">Invalid value type ''{0}'' specified for attribute ''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedAttrForWrite" note="">The attribute ''{0}'' is not supported for writing. See documentation for a list of supported attributes.</entry>
        <entry key="EnvMapUnsupportedValue" note="">''EnvironmentMap'' attribute value must be ''LatLon'' or ''Cube''</entry>
        <entry key="ChromaticitiesIncorrectType" note="">''Chromaticities'' attribute value must be a scalar structure.</entry>
        <entry key="ChromaticitiesInvalidFields" note="">Missing or invalid fields. ''Chromaticities'' attribute value must be a scalar structure that contains the fields ''Red'', ''Green'', ''Blue'' and ''White''.</entry>
        <entry key="ChromaticiesInvalidXYValues" note="">''{0}'' value must be a 2-element row vector of data type double.</entry>
        <entry key="NumericAttrInvalidSize" note="">''{0}'' attribute value must be a {1, number, integer}-by-{2, number, integer} numeric matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="AlphaChannelIncorrectDimensions" note="">''Alpha'' value must be the same size as the first two dimensions of the image data.</entry>
        <entry key="DataWindowIncorrectSize" note="">''DataWindow'' value must specify start and end values corresponding to a window the same size as the image data.</entry>
        <entry key="TileDimensionsIncorrect" note="">''TileDimensions'' value must specify tile dimensions smaller than the dimensions of the image data.</entry>
        <entry key="PartIDInvalid" note="">''PartIdentifier'' value must be less than or equal to the number of parts in the file, {0,number,integer}.</entry>
        <entry key="PartNameNotFound" note="">Unable to find the specified ''PartIdentifier'' value,''{0}'', in the input file.</entry>
        <entry key="PartNameNotUnique" note="">Multiple parts in the input file have the name ''{0}''. Specify ''PartIdentifier'' using the numeric index of the desired part in the structure returned by exrinfo.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelNameNotFound" note="">Unable to find one or more names specified by ''Channels'' in part {0, number, integer} of the input file.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelNamesCellStr" note="">When ''Channels'' value is a cell array, each cell must contain a character vector.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelsTypeMismatch" note="">''Channels'' value must specify image data channels that are of the same data type.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelsXYSubsamplingMismatch" note="">''Channels'' value must specify image data channels that have the same subsampling rate along the X- and Y-directions.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidImageInPart" note="">Part {0, number, integer} of the input file does not contain a valid RGB, YUV, or grayscale image.</entry>
        <entry key="YUV2RGBUnsupported" note="">Automatic conversion from YUV to RGB is not supported when reading from parts other than part 0. Read the Y, RY and BY channels individually and perform the conversion manually.</entry>
        <entry key="NoAlphaIfChanListContainsA" note="">''Alpha'' name-value argument is not supported when ''Channels'' value specifies an ''A'' channel.</entry>
        <entry key="XYSubSamplingNonIntegral" note="">To write multiresolution image data, the size of the highest resolution data must be an integer multiple of the size of subsampled data.</entry>
        <entry key="FileNameEmpty" note="">File name must be nonempty.</entry>
        <entry key="FileNameUnsupportedExtn" note="">File name must have file extension ''.exr''.</entry>
        <entry key="DefaultImageMustBeRGBOrGray" note="">Invalid number of channels in image data. To write images other than Grayscale or RGB, specify the ''Channels'' name-value argument.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelNamesNonEmpty" note="">''Channels'' value must specify nonempty channel names.</entry>
        <entry key="ChannelNamesMustBeUnique" note="">''Channels'' value must specify unique channel names.</entry>
        <entry key="NumChannelsMismatchWithData" note="">''Channels'' value must specify the same number of channels as the image data.</entry>
        <entry key="NumChannelTypesMismatch" note="">Number of channels specified by ''Channels'' and ''OutputType'' must match.</entry>
        <entry key="NumericInputsAllChannelTypesNotSame" note="">When the image data is a numeric array, the ''OutputType'' value must be the same for all channels.</entry>
        <entry key="CellInputsMustBeVectorOfNumericNonEmptyMatrix" note="">When the image data is a cell array, each cell must contain a nonempty 2-D numeric matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="HalfTypeInputsNotSupported" note="">Data type half is not supported. Use exrHalfAsSingle to store half precision values as data type single before writing.</entry>
		<entry key="InvalidWindowLimits" note="">Invalid ''{0}'' value in the {1}-direction. Start value must be less than the end value.</entry>
		<entry key="AppendFailedInvalidPartType" note="">Unable to append to specified file because one or more existing parts are invalid or not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="AppendFailedDisplayWindowMismatch" note="">Unable to append to specified file because ''DisplayWindow'' must be the same for all parts. Specify an image data array the same size as the existing parts or use the ''DisplayWindow'' name-value argument to set the display window size.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->