<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2012-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>
    <entry key="outputViewTformDimsMismatch" note="">Dimensionality of specified geometric transformation must match dimensionality of {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="spatialRefDimsDisagreeWithInputImage" note="">{0} property of spatial referencing object {1} does not agree with size of input image {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="tformDoesNotAgreeWithSizeOfA" note="">The number of dimensions of the input image {0} must be 3 when the specified geometric transformation is 3-D.</entry>
    <entry key="scalarFillValueRequired" note="">{0} must be scalar except when a 2-D geometric transform is applied to a stack of 2-D images.</entry>
    <entry key="fillValueDimMismatch" note="">When {0} is an N dimensional array, the size of {1} must match dimensions 3 to N of the input {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="badFillValueForCategorical" note="">Invalid FillValue. Categorical inputs only support the default FillValue of '0', corresponding to the 'undefined' label.</entry>
    <entry key="gpuUnderlyingClassTypeImage" note="">gpuArray image must be uint8, uint16, uint32, int8, int16, int32, single, double, or logical.</entry>
    <entry key="gpu3DSpatialRefNotAllowed" note="">You specified a 3-D spatial referencing object. Only 2-D image warping is supported for gpuArray image. </entry>
    <entry key="gpu3DGeoTransNotAllowed" note="">You specified a 3-D geometric transformation. Only 2-D image warping is supported for gpuArray image. </entry>
    <entry key="gpuProjective2dNotAllowed" note="">You specified a projective2d geometric transformation. Only affine2d geometric transformations are supported for gpuArray image. </entry>
    <entry key="outputImageTooSmall" note="">You called IMWARP such that the number of rows or columns in the output image is less than 3. For gpuArray input image, IMWARP requires the number of rows and columns in the output image to be greater than or equal to 3. Consider changing the size of the input image or specifying a spatial referencing object for the 'OutputView' parameter to change the output image size.</entry>
    <entry key="gpu3DOutputViewNotAllowed" note="">You specified a 3-D spatial referencing object for 'OutputView'. Only 2-D spatial referencing objects can be specified for 'OutputView' for gpuArray image. </entry>
    <entry key="gpuOutputViewMustBeSpatialRef" note="">Value for 'OutputView' must be a valid spatial referencing object. </entry>
    <entry key="coderInterpStringNotConst" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Interpolation method must be a string or a character vector constant.</entry>
    <entry key="coderOutputViewMustBeSpatialRef" note="">Value for 'OutputView' must be a valid spatial referencing object. </entry>
    <entry key="coderOutputViewMustBeSpecifiedWithNoDMA" note="">Value for 'OutputView' must be specified if dynamic memory allocation is turned off. </entry>
    <entry key="displacementField3dData2d" note="">When D is 3-D displacement field of size MxNxPx3, input image A must be 3-D.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDSize" note="">Displacement field D must be of size MxNx2 or MxNxPx3.</entry>
    <entry key="spatialRefNotAllowedWithDField" note="">Spatial referencing arguments not supported when warping with displacement field.</entry> 
    <entry key="badMethodForCategorical">Invalid METHOD. METHOD must be 'nearest' for categorical inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="gpuSmoothEdgesNotSupported">The 'SmoothEdges' Name/Value is not supported for gpuArray inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="gpuCubicInterpolationNotSupported">Cubic interpolation is not supported for gpuArray inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="gpuUnsupportedTransformationType">For gpuArray inputs only translation, rigid, similarity, affine, projective, and displacement field geometric transformations are supported.</entry>
</message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->
