<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018-2019 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="images">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidPatchSize">PatchSize is expected to be a two element or three element integer vector.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidIndex">Specified indices into datastore must be in the range [1,NumObservations].</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPatchSizeDimsImageDims">The number of dimensions specified in PatchSize cannot be greater than the number of dimensions in the image {0} of size {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidPatchSizeDimsLabelDims">The number of dimensions specified in PatchSize cannot be greater than the number of dimensions in the pixel label image {0} of size {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="expectPatchSmallerThanImage">Patch size ({0}) must be smaller than image size ({1}) of the file {2}</entry>
    <entry key="expect3DImagesWith3DLabels">The number of dimensions in the image, {0} cannot be less than the number of dimensions in the pixel label image {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="expectMinimum3Dimensions">The input image {0} must have at least 3 dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="outOfData">No more data to read. Use reset method to reset to start of data. Use the hasdata method to check if data is available to read.</entry>
    <entry key="unexpectedInputDatastore">Unexpected input datastore. Only imageDatastore and datastores that are subclasses of matlab.io.datastore.MiniBatchable are allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="expectSameSizeImages">The output of read() on the input datastores must return images of the same size for input files {0} {1}</entry>
    <entry key="ignoreMiniBatchesPerImage">'MiniBatchesPerImage' name-value pair is ignored because the input datastore doesn't implement readByIndex() method.</entry>
    <entry key="notPartitionable">The input datastore cannot be partitioned because it has not implemented matlab.io.datastore.Partitionable mixin.</entry>
    <entry key="notBackgroundDispatchable">DispatchInBackground name-value pair cannot be set to true when the input datastore has not implemented matlab.io.datastore.BackgroundDispatchable mixin.</entry>
    <entry key="noDataAugmentationIn3D">DataAugmentation name-value pair cannot be set to an imageDataAugmenter object for 3-D patch sizes. Use transform method on the output of randomPatchExtractionDatastore to perform data augmentation.</entry>
    <entry key="noDataAugmentationForCombinedDatastore">DataAugmentation name-value pair cannot be set for these input datastores. Use transform method on the output of randomPatchExtractionDatastore to perform data augmentation.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedMethod">The {0} method is not supported for these input datastores.</entry>
    <entry key="unequalNumPartitions">Input datastores must be of equal length.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputDatastore">Unexpected input datastore.</entry>
    <entry key="unexpectedReadFromInputDatastores">Unsupported input datastores. The output of read() on ds1 and ds2 must contain one column each representing the training input and the desired network response respectively.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
