<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="vision" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidBoxesInTable">境界ボックス データのサイズは M 行 4 列、M 行 5 列または M 行 9 列でなければなりません。ここで M は各 table 要素内のボックス数です。境界ボックスを含む学習データ table の列は cell 配列でなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelsInTable">ラベル データは M 行 1 列の categorical 配列でなければなりません。ここで、M は 1 行内のラベル数を指定します。ラベルを含む学習データ table の列は cell 配列でなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNumLabelsInTable">The number of bounding boxes does not equal the number of labels in row {0,number,integer} of the training data table. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')"&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidMixOfTables">Multiple tables must be in the same format. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')"&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataInTableColumn">入力 table {0} の列 {1} のデータが無効です。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataInTableRow">入力 table {0} の行 {1} のデータが無効です。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataInTable">入力 table {0} で無効な境界ボックスが見つかりました。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidMixOfBoxesInTable">The size of all bounding box matrices contained in the input tables must be the same. The size of each matrix must be M-by-4, M-by-5, or M-by-9, where M is the number of boxes in each table element. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')"&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidImageNumberInBlockSet">The maximum image number in the BlockLocations property must not exceed the number of rows ({0}) in the boxLabels table input. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')"&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBoxFormatForBlockSet">The bounding boxes must be M-by-4 or M-by-5 when blockLocationSet is provided as an input. See &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('vision','boxlabeldatastore')"&gt;boxLabelDatastore&lt;/a&gt; for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNDBlockOrigin">Invalid BlockOrigin in the blockLocationSet input. n-D BlockOrigin values in the blockLocationSet are not supported in boxLabelDatastore.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
