<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="vision" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidSize">{0} は 2 要素ベクトルでなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="minSizeGTMaxSize">MaxSize の値は MinSize の値より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="modelMinSizeGTMaxSize">MaxSize value must be greater than [{0} {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="minSizeLTTrainingSize">MinSize value must be greater than or equal to [{0} {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="modelNotFound">モデル {0} が見つかりません。</entry>
    <entry key="modelNotFoundOnLoad">モデル {0} が見つかりません。既定の分類モデル {1} が読み込まれます。</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataTableWidthLessThanTwo">Width of the training data table must be greater than or equal to 2.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataFirstColumnNotFilename">First column of the training data must contain image filenames.</entry>
    <entry key="detectionResultsTableWidthLessThanTwo">Width of the detection results table must be greater than or equal to 2.</entry>
    <entry key="detectionResultsMustHaveLabels">Detections results table must contain labels in the third column when there are multiple classes in the ground truth data.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInTrainingDataTable">グラウンド トゥルース データ table の {0} 行 {1} 列目の境界ボックスが無効: {2}。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInDetectionTable">検出結果テーブルの行 {0} の境界ボックスが無効です: {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidScoreInDetectionTable">検出結果テーブルの行 {0} のスコア値が無効です: {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelInDetectionTable">検出結果テーブルの行 {0} のラベル値が無効です: {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedLabelInDetectionTable">Label value in row {0} of the detection results table must be one of the following categorical values: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="ROILessThanMinSize">入力 ROI のサイズ {0} は ''MinSize'' {1} より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="ROILessThanModelSize">入力 ROI のサイズ {0} は分類モデルのサイズ {1} より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="ImageLessThanMinSize">入力イメージのサイズ {0} は ''MinSize'' {1} より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="ImageLessThanModelSize">入力イメージのサイズ {0} は分類モデルのサイズ {1} より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidObjectSize">Size of the object is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="classHasNoBoxes">クラス {0} の学習データには、少なくとも 1 つの境界ボックスが含まれていなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataHasNoBoxes">学習データには少なくとも 1 つの境界ボックスが含まれている必要があります。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBboxInBboxTable">境界ボックス table の {0} 行目の境界ボックスが無効: {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLabelInBboxTable">境界ボックス table の {0} 行目のラベル値が無効: {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="undefinedLabelInBboxTable">Label value in row {0} of the bounding box table is undefined. It must be one of the following categorical values: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputImageChannelSize">入力イメージのチャネル サイズが無効です。入力イメージのチャネル サイズ {0,number,integer} は、ネットワークの入力チャネル サイズ {1,number,integer} と同じでなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="imageSmallerThanNetwork">入力イメージのサイズは {0} より大きくなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="unSupportedInputClass">入力データ型は、uint8、uint16、int16、double または single である必要があります。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidEvaluationDatastoreInput">Evaluation ground truth data input must be a table or a datastore.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidBboxNotInCell">Bounding box from the read method output of the datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidBbox">データストアの read メソッドからの境界ボックス データが無効です:\n{0} </entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalidLabel">Label from the read method output of the datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-1 categorical, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.</entry>
    <entry key="evaluationReadOutputInvalid">Output of the read method of the input datastore must be an M-by-3 or M-by-2 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTrainingInput">Training data input must be a table or a datastore.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputNotCellTable">Read method of the training input datastore must return an M-by-3 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputNotCellTwoOrThreeColTable">Read method of the training input datastore must return an M-by-3 or M-by-2 cell or table.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidBbox">Bounding box column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array, containing elements of N-by-4 double matrix, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidLabel">Labels column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-1 categorical, where N equals the number of bounding boxes.\n\nThe categories of the categorical must contain all the label names for all of the training data.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidImage">Images column from the read method output of the training input datastore must be an M-by-1 cell array containing elements of N-by-P-by-Q images or N-by-P grayscale images.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBoxesInTrainingData">入力データ ストアの読み取りからの学習データに無効な境界ボックスが含まれています。境界ボックスは、空でなく、関連付けられているイメージ内に完全に含まれていなければならず、正の幅と高さをもたなければなりません。データ ストア変換メソッドを使用して無効な境界ボックスを削除してください。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidValidationData">学習データがデータ ストアである場合、検証データはデータ ストアでなければなりません。検証データ ストアの read メソッドは、M 行 3 列の cell または table を返さなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="validationDataMustBeDatastore">Validation data not supported when training data input is a table. Use a datstore as both validation data and the training data input.</entry>
    <entry key="backgroundUnsupportedWithDatastore">Training option DispatchInBackground is not supported with datastore training data input. The value of ''options.DispatchInBackground'' must be 'false'.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidReadDataFromFile">次のファイルに関連付けられている学習データは無効です。\n\n{0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="tooManyClasses">Number of classes in the training data must be 1.</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidBboxFileInfo">入力データストアの read メソッドにより返される境界ボックスは、N 個のボックスの [x y width height] 値を定義する N 行 4 列の数値行列を含む M 行 1 列の cell 配列でなければなりません。また、すべてのボックスの幅と高さは正でなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidImageClass">入力データストアの read メソッドにより返されるイメージ データのクラスは、double、single、uint8、int16、uint16、または logical である必要があります。また、このイメージ データは空でない非スパースの実数である必要があります。</entry>
    <entry key="readOutputInvalidRGBOrGrayscaleImage">入力データストアの read メソッドにより返されるイメージは、RGB またはグレースケールである必要があり、また M 行 1 列の cell 配列に格納する必要があります。ここで M はイメージの数です。</entry>
    <entry key="trainingDataBboxOutsideBounds">Bounding boxes associated with the following image were not all located within the image: {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDetectionInput">入力データはデータストアでなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDetectionDatastoreReadOutput">Read method of the input datastore must return a numeric array or an M-by-N cell or table containing elements of N-by-P-by-Q or N-by-P numeric arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="unableToBatchImagesForDetect">Images must have the same size when the MiniBatchSize value is greater than 1. To detect objects in images of varying size, set the MiniBatchSize value to 1.</entry>
    <entry key="noDataFromDatastore">Datastore input does not have any data. Every call to the read method returns empty.</entry>
    <entry key="genericBaseMessageWithFilename">入力データストアの以下のファイルの処理中にエラーが発生しました。\n\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="genericBaseMessageWithoutFilename">入力データストアのデータの処理中にエラーが発生しました。</entry>
    <entry key="nonEmptyMetricsInfoInExperimentMonitor">Metrics property of the Experiment Monitor input must be empty.</entry>
    <entry key="unexpectedTypeForExperimentMonitor">Specified Experiment Monitor must be of type experiments.Monitor.</entry>
    <entry key="trainingPlotWithExperimentMonitor">Training option "Plots" must be "none" when specifying the Experiment Monitor option.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
