<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd" decorate_cxx_names="true">
  <message>
    <entry key="notAvailable">Simulation through code generation is not available. See <![CDATA[<a href="matlab:disp('doc missing')">matlab.system.simulateUsing</a>]]> for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedSystem">Encountered code not supported by simulation using code generation. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="loadingTflFailed">Failed to simulate the System object using code generation because the target function library is not available. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedDataType">Encountered code not supported by simulation using code generation. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unknownFixptType">Encountered fixed-point data types for which simulate using code-generation is not supported. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedInputType">Simulation using code generation is not supported for input argument number {0}. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="failedExecution">Simulation using code generation mode failed. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="failedConstruction">System object construction in simulation using code generation mode failed. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedMethod">System object method {0} is not supported in simulation using code generation mode. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedMethodLocked">System object method {0} is not supported in simulation using code generation mode after the System object starts running. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedTunable">Tuning for the property {0} is not supported in simulation using code generation mode after the System object starts running. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="inputSpecChanged">Changing input specifications (i.e., size, type, and number) is not supported in simulation using code generation mode. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="paramSpecChanged">Changing parameter specifications (i.e., size, type, and number) is not supported in simulation using code generation mode. Run the System object in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unknownNumOutputs">Simulation using code generation requires a fixed number of outputs. Implement getNumOutputsImpl method for the System object {0} or simulate in interpreted mode. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedSystemWithMessage">Compilation in simulate using code generation mode failed with the message: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="simulateUsingInvalidValue">Invalid argument ''{0}'' to simulateUsing. You must specify &quot;Code generation&quot; or &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;. Use no argument to retrieve current simulation mode.</entry>
    <entry key="simulateUsingInvalidType">Invalid argument type to simulateUsing. You must specify &quot;Code generation&quot; or &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;. Use no argument to retrieve current simulation mode.</entry>
    <entry key="simulateUsing">Simulation mode is set to ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeError">Error occurred while running System object using simulation in code generation mode. Run the System object in interpreted mode to debug. To enable interpreted mode, run simulateUsing(&lt;yourObj&gt;, &quot;Interpreted execution&quot;).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeSizeCheck">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Matrix dimensions must agree. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeIndexOutOfBounds">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Index exceeds the number of array elements. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeIndexNotInteger">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Array indices must be positive integers or logical values. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeSubsAssignSizeMismatch">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Left and right sides of assignment have a different number of elements. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeForLoopZeroStride">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Vector expression with zero stride is not supported. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeSizeMismatch">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Size mismatch error. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
    <entry key="runTimeSizeOverflow">Error occurred while running System object using acceleration: Size overflow error. Run the System object without acceleration to debug. To disable acceleration, run accelerate(&lt;yourObj&gt;, false).</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
