<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <!-- sysobjupdate -->
    <entry key="MissingTargetInput">Missing target argument. Specify a System object name, package, or directory on the path.</entry>
    <entry key="UnrecognizedOption">Unknown option: ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="Option">option</entry>
    <entry key="ExpectedAnotherArgument">The ''{0}'' option requires an additional argument.</entry>
    <entry key="NotTextArray">The ''{0}'' option requires a string or cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="DiffRequiresBackup">Running ''-diff'' option cannot be used with the ''-nobackup'' option. Displaying updated file differences requires creating a backup.</entry>
    <entry key="DiffInPlaceTogether">sysobjupdate does not support using the ''-inplace'' and ''-diff'' options together.</entry>
    <entry key="PostWithoutSave">The ''-post'' option must be used with ''-inplace'' or ''-diff''</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidActionOption">''{0}'' is not a recognized action. Run ''sysobjupdate -listactions'' for a list of actions.</entry>
    <entry key="TargetNotFound">The specified input ''{0}'' was not recognized as a System object class, package, or directory on the path.</entry>
    <entry key="DirectoryNotOnPath">The specified directory ''{0}'' does not appear to be on the MATLAB path. Ensure System object directories are on the search path. </entry>
    <entry key="DiffMultipleClasses">The ''{0}'' input resolved to multiple System objects. The ''-diff'' option does not support usage with multiple System objects.</entry>
    <entry key="StaleMetaClass">Unable to update meta data after saving a file. This may occur when instances of the classes exist or only property validation is updated in System object. Clear classes and update System object again or restart MATLAB if the problem persists.</entry>
    <entry key="BackupFileExists">The backup file destination ''{0}'' already exists. Remove the file if it is safe to do so and update System object again.</entry>
    <entry key="CommandReturnedNonzero">The specified {0} command, ''{1}'', returned non-zero for the file ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToOpenFile">Unable to open ''{0}'' for writing.</entry>
    <entry key="ActionListHeader">Actions for sysobjupdate:</entry>
    <entry key="ResultsHeader">Following System objects have been modified:</entry>
    <entry key="UpdateNotes">Note:</entry>
    <entry key="SummaryHeader">Summary:</entry>
    <entry key="SummaryStatement">{0} out of {1} System objects were modified using sysobjupdate.</entry>
    <entry key="NoUpdatedSystemObjects">No System object has been modified.</entry>

    <!-- system object code analyzer (soca) errors -->
    <entry key="CodeAnalyzerError">An error occurred analyzing ''{0}''. Only valid System objects can be updated. Use the MATLAB Editor to address syntax problems.</entry>
    <entry key="PFileExists">The ''{0}'' file is shadowed by a P-file. Delete the P-file and refresh MATLAB's toolbox cache before updating System objects.</entry>
    <entry key="SyntaxError">An error occurred analyzing ''{0}''. Only valid System objects can be updated. Use the MATLAB Editor to address syntax problems.</entry>
    <entry key="NotASystemObject">The ''{0}'' file is not recognized to be a System object. Make sure System object is on MATLAB's path.</entry>
    <entry key="NoFileForClass">Unable to load the class definition for ''{0}''. Ensure the file still exists.</entry>
    <entry key="OverlappingExtent">Unable to update classes that define multiple properties on the same line. Split property definitions in ''{0}'' over multiple lines and update System object again or manually update the file.</entry>

    <!-- system object code analyzer (soca) update messages -->
    <entry key="CustomAttributeAbstractBaseClass">Unable to convert the ''{0}'' property and other properties in the same block to use property validation, because it declared as an abstract property in a superclass. Apply property validation to the abstract property manually, verify it produces the intended behavior, and then update System object again.</entry>
    <entry key="AssociatedStringSetHasGetter">Unable to convert the ''{0}'' property to use property validation, because the associated matlab.system.StringSet property ''{1}'' has a get method. Update the ''{0}'' property manually or remove the get method and update System object again.</entry>
    <entry key="StringSetIndirectInstantiation">Unable to convert the ''{0}'' property to use property validation, because the associated matlab.system.StringSet property ''{1}'' is assigned its default value indirectly. MATLAB only supports updating default values that involve a direct instantiation of a matlab.system.StringSet with a string or cell array of character vectors literal.</entry>
    <entry key="AssociatedStringSetUsedInSourceCode">Unable to convert the ''{0}'' property to use property validation, because the associated matlab.system.StringSet property ''{1}'' may be used in a statement or an expression inside a method. Update the ''{0}'' property manually, and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyHasEmptyDefault">Unable to convert the ''{0}'' property and other properties in the same block to use property validation, because it does not have a default value. Update the ''{0}'' property manually, and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="ImplNameConflictAfterConversion">Unable to convert the obsolete ''{0}'' method to ''{1}'' method, because the ''{1}'' method is already defined in this class. Remove the ''{0}'' method manually, and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="ImplSignatureMismatch">Unable to convert the obsolete ''{0}'' method to ''{1}'' method, because number of input, output arguments or method attribute does not match matlab.System ''{0}'' interface. Update or remove ''{0}'' method manually and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="ImplSignatureMismatchForDeletion">Unable to remove the obsolete ''{0}'' method, because number of input, output arguments or method attribute does not match matlab.System ''{0}'' interface. Remove ''{0}'' method manually and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="ImplSignatureMismatchForDeletionStrictDefaultsRedundantNonObsolete">Unable to remove the redundant ''{0}'' method for StrictDefaults system object because number of input arguments, output arguments or method attributes does not match matlab.System ''{0}'' interface. Remove ''{0}'' method manually and update System objects again.</entry>
    <entry key="LegacyImplReferenced">System object contains references to the obsolete ''{0}'' method. Manually review the code and update ''{0}'' references to ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="LegacyImplReferencedStrictDefaultsRedundantNonObsolete">StrictDefaults system object contains references to the redundant ''{0}'' method. Manually review the code and remove ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedImplReferenced">System object contains references to the obsolete ''{0}'' method. Manually review the code and rename ''{0}'' references or replace it with inline method implementation if necessary.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
