<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd" decorate_cxx_names="true">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageWithHoles">Invalid return from the messageIdentifiers method of the {0} enumeration. Enumeration display requires messages without holes. The specified message identifier, {1}, contains at least one hole.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageCatalogIdentifier">Invalid return from the messageIdentifiers method of the {0} enumeration. The {1} message identifier was not found in the Message Catalog.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageIdentifiers">Invalid return from the messageIdentifiers method of the {0} enumeration. The messageIdentifiers method must return a string vector with the same number of elements as enumeration members.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDuplicateCatalogStrings">Invalid return from the messageIdentifiers method of the {0} enumeration. The Message Catalog strings associated with the message identifiers returned by the messageIdentifiers method must be case-insensitive unique.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDisplayStrings">Invalid return from the displayStrings method of the {0} enumeration. The displayStrings method must return a string vector with the same number of elements as enumeration members.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDuplicateDisplayStrings">Invalid return from the displayStrings method of the {0} enumeration. The strings returned by the displayStrings method must be case-insensitive unique.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDefaultEnumerationValue">Unexpected default value for the {0} property of the {1} System object. Enumerations with dynamic member visibility must specify a default value that is valid in the default configuration for the System object.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPropertiesAffectingVisibility">Unexpected return value from the propertiesAffectingVisibility method of the {0} enumeration class associated with the {1} property of the {2} System object. The propertiesAffectingVisibility method must return a non-empty string vector naming Nontunable public scalar enumeration or logical properties on the {3} class.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidActiveMembers">Unexpected return value from the activeMembers method of the {0} enumeration class associated with the {1} property of the {2} System object. The activeMembers method must return a non-empty vector without duplicates of members from the {3} enumeration.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEnumerationSet">{0} is not valid value for the {1} property for the current configuration of the {2} System object. Valid values are: {3}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEnumerationSetCodegen">{0} is not valid value for the {1} property for the current configuration of the {2} System object.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEnumerationValueSetupCodegen">{0} is not valid value for the {1} property for the current configuration of the {2} System object. In code generation, enumerations with dynamic member visibility must be explicitly set to values that are valid based on the properties listed in propertiesAffectingVisibility.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCallEnumerationMethod">Unable to call the {0} method on the {1} enumeration class. If the enumeration was edited, clear classes to refresh enumeration and property relationships.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedsBothMethods">The {0} enumeration class only implements the {1} method. Both the propertiesAffectingVisibility and the activeMembers methods must be implemented to control enumeration member visibility.</entry>
    <entry key="CyclicDependencies">The enumeration classes associated with the properties of the ''{0}'' System object have a cyclic dependency. Remove the cyclic dependency. {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="ViewDependencies">View dependencies</entry>
    <entry key="UseDependencyViewer">Use matlab.system.internal.showDynamicDependencyGraph to view dependencies</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
