<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="EventTableInput">Creating an event filter from an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then create the event filter from the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="EventFilterOnEventTable">Using an event filter as a subscript on an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then subscript into the timetable using the event filter.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsAttached">Creating an event filter for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To create an event filter from this timetable, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsForSubscripting">Using an event filter as a subscript for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To subscript this timetable with an event filter, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventLabelsForSubscripting">To subscript into a timetable using an event filter created using an event label value, the event table attached to the timetable must have the EventLabelsVariable property set.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEventFilterInput">eventfilter への入力が無効です。入力は次のいずれかである必要があります。\n - string ベクトル、文字ベクトル、または文字ベクトルの cell 配列\n - timetable\n - スカラーの欠損値。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">eventfilter の二項演算子の入力が無効です。いずれのオペランドも eventfilter オブジェクトでなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="EventTimeTypeFilterError">''{0}'' 個の行時間をもつ timetable に対して、1 個のイベント フィルターと ''{1}'' 個のイベント時間を使用して添字を指定することはサポートされていません。</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelFilterError">Comparison between the event labels variable ''{0}'' and the event filter value failed.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelTypeMismatch">イベント変数 ''{0}'' の型は ''{1}'' ですが、イベント フィルター値の型は ''{2}'' です。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTime">イベント ラベル変数は datetime、duration、または calendarDuration 変数であってはなりません。割り当てられたイベント テーブルの rowtimes に基づき timetable のイベントをフィルター処理するには、まず timetable を eventfilter への入力として使用してください。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableChar">char 行列からイベント フィルターを作成することはサポートされていません。代わりに string 配列を使用してください。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableSize">複数のイベント ラベル値用のイベント フィルターを作成するには、値が空でない列ベクトルでなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTabular">イベント ラベル変数は table 変数であってはなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="NegationUnsupported">イベント フィルターでは否定演算子 (~) はサポートされません。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">イベント フィルターを使用した添字は、イベント テーブルが割り当てられた timetable の行の選択でのみサポートされています。</entry>
    <entry key="UIStringDispEventLabelsVariable">&lt;イベント ラベル変数&gt;</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
