<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2021 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="half" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="complexNotSupported">This function only supports real inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="dimagree">Matrix dimensions must agree.</entry>
    <entry key="dimensionMustBePositiveInteger">Dimension argument must be a positive integer scalar within indexing range.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionNotDefinedForHalf">Function is not defined for half inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="HalfPrecisionNotAvailable">Use of half-precision data type requires Fixed-Point Designer or MATLAB Coder to be installed.</entry>
    <entry key="ignoredImagPart">Imaginary part is ignored.</entry>
    <entry key="innerdim">Incorrect dimensions for matrix multiplication. Check that the number of columns in the first matrix matches the number of rows in the second matrix. To perform elementwise multiplication, use '.*'.</entry>
    <entry key="inputMustBeScalar">Expected input {0} to be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="inputsMustBe2D">Arguments must be 2-D, or at least one argument must be scalar. Use TIMES (.*) for elementwise multiplication, use PAGEMTIMES to apply matrix multiplication to the pages of N-D arrays, or use TENSORPROD to find a product between two N-D arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidImagPartInput" context="error">Input for imaginary part must be a real, full numeric value.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInputNotNumericOrLogical">Value must be numeric or logical.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRealPartInput" context="error">Input for real part must be a real, full numeric value.</entry>
    <entry key="Log2TwoOutCplxDiscardsImag">Imaginary part of complex argument is ignored.</entry>
    <entry key="mixedNonDoubleOperands">Colon operands must be all the same type, or mixed with real scalar doubles.</entry>
    <entry key="nologicalcomplex">Complex values cannot be converted to logicals.</entry>
    <entry key="nologicalnan">NaN values cannot be converted to logicals.</entry>
    <entry key="nonDoubleOperandsNotRealScalar">Colon operands must be real scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="OutOfRange">Colon operands must be in the range of the data type.</entry>
    <entry key="PropInvalidDataType">Invalid data type.</entry>
    <entry key="sparseInput">Input arguments must not be sparse.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFixedCast">Fixed point value cannot be cast to half.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedBfloat16">bfloat16 is currently an unsupported data type.</entry>
    <entry key="vecDimsMustBeUniquePositiveIntegers">Elements of a dimension vector must be unique.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  bfloat
-->
