<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2025 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="BackgroundRemedyForDisallowed">{0} Use alternatives supported on the background pool.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotPreallocatePoolArray">Creating arrays of parallel pools is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="DisallowedPathAlteration" context="error">基于线程的工作进程不支持更改 MATLAB 路径。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAttachFilesArgument">Files must be specified as a character vector or a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidParallelPoolFallBack" context="warning">无法创建并行池，您的代码将改为串行运行。要使用并行池，请更改您的默认集群配置文件或在集群配置文件管理器中验证它。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionMethod" context="error">Invalid partition method argument. Partition method argument must be one of {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionNumWorkersPerGPU" context="error">Invalid value for "MaxNumWorkersPerGPU" partition method argument. Value must be a numeric scalar integer equal to the maximum number of workers per unique GPU to use.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionNumWorkersPerHost" context="error">Invalid value for "MaxNumWorkersPerHost" partition method argument. Value must be a numeric scalar integer equal to the maximum number of workers per unique host to use.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPartitionWorkersArgument" context="error">Invalid value for "Workers" partition method argument. Value must be an array of parallel.Worker instances, all of which must be members of the input parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPool" context="error">并行池已关闭。请使用 parpool 启动新池。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidUseParallel" context="error">无效值。UseParallel 必须为 "on"、"off"、"auto"、true 或 false。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidUseParallelForApp" context="error">无效值。UseParallel 必须为 "on"、"off"、true 或 false。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSerializedPool">Use of a loaded parallel pool object is not supported. Avoid storing parallel pool objects in MAT files or sending them between MATLAB Sessions.</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoAttachedFiles" context="uistring">没有文件自动添加到并行池。</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoCreate" context="error">No parallel pool is available for parallel execution and AutoCreate is disabled. Either create a parallel pool using parpool, set UseParallel to "auto", or modify your Parallel Settings to enable AutoCreate.</entry>
    <entry key="NoAutoCreateOnWorker" context="error">没有可用于并行执行的并行池。请使用 parpool 创建一个并行池，或将 UseParallel 设置为 "auto"。</entry>
    <entry key="NoParallelPoolAvailableInApp" context="error">No parallel pool is available for parallel execution and AutoCreate is disabled. Either create a parallel pool using parpool or modify your Parallel Settings to enable AutoCreate.</entry>
    <entry key="PCTNotLicensed" context="error">并行池的并行功能需要 Parallel Computing Toolbox。</entry>
    <entry key="PCTNotInstalled" context="error">并行池的并行功能需要 Parallel Computing Toolbox 许可证。</entry>
    <entry key="ParpoolRemedyForDisallowed" context="error">{0} Use a PARPOOL('Processes') process-based pool or a different process-based pool instead.</entry>
    <entry key="PartitionErrorNumWorkersPerGPU" context="error">Failed to partition pool using "NumWorkersPerGPU" method. Caused by:\n{0}.</entry>
    <entry key="ScalarPoolRequired">A scalar parallel pool is required as the first argument to ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SerialFallbackOnAutoCreateFailure" context="warning">无法使用默认并行环境自动创建并行池。将改为在客户端上串行运行。在以后的版本中将删除回退到串行执行。错误详细信息:\n\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="SerializedPool">Parallel pool is unavailable because it was created in a different MATLAB session or it has been loaded from a file.</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownPool" context="uistring">关闭并行池。</entry>
    <entry key="SlowToGatherGPUDevice" context="warning">等待收集每个并行池工作进程的 gpuDevice 信息。一个或多个必需的并行池工作进程正忙于执行 PARFEVAL。如果这是预期行为，请使用 {0} 禁用此警告。</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesDifferentPool">tocBytes must be called with the same connected pool object that was used for ticBytes.</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesNotCalled">ticBytes must be called without an output argument before calling tocBytes with only a single input argument.</entry>
    <entry key="TicBytesResultRequired">Argument to tocBytes must be the argument returned from ticBytes.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeature" context="error">语法在基于线程的池上不受支持。</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureBackground">Syntax not supported on a thread-based pool. Use alternatives supported on the background pool.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureParpool">Syntax not supported on a thread-based pool. Use a process-based parallel pool instead.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureInternalPool" context="error">Syntax not supported on internal pool.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFeatureNonParpool" context="error">后台池不支持语法。请改用通过 parpool 创建的 Parallel Computing Toolbox 池。</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedTicBytesTocBytes" context="warning">基于线程的池不支持测量发送到工作进程或从工作进程接收的字节。</entry>
    <entry key="UseDelete" context="error">"close" not supported for parallel pool objects. Use "delete" instead. </entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
