<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2025 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="CloseFailure" context="error">Internal error while closing the DataQueue: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidProcess">Failed to load the DataQueue. A DataQueue can only be loaded in a MATLAB client or one of its pool workers if any of these created it.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidQueue" context="error">Invalid PollableDataQueue. PollableDataQueues become invalid when used with some features including save, load, spmdSend, spmdReceive, the ValueStore or the FileStore.</entry>
    <entry key="IsClosedFailure" context="error">Internal error while checking whether DataQueue is closed: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="NoPool" context="error">DataQueue に必要な並列プールが実行されていません。</entry>
    <entry key="NoQueue" context="error">メッセージは、キューを作成したものと同じ MATLAB クライアントまたはプール ワーカーによってのみ受け取ることができます。</entry>
    <entry key="SendFailure" context="error">データを DataQueue に送信中に内部エラーが発生しました: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="NestedProcessPool">Unable to use DataQueue in nested process pool (thread worker in a process pool).</entry>
    <entry key="PollFailedWithCause" context="error">Failed to retrieve data from the sender because: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="PollFailedWorkerLost" context="error">Failed to retrieve data because the connection to the sending worker was lost, potentially due to network problems, or a crash of that worker.</entry>
    <entry key="PollFailedUnknownWorker" context="error">Failed to retrieve data because the sender is not a part of a currently open parallel pool. Call poll on the client to retrieve all messages from the workers before closing a pool.</entry>
    <entry key="QueueClosedSend" context="error">Failed to send data because the DataQueue has been closed.</entry>
    <entry key="WrongConstructorArgs">DataQueue construction must not have additional arguments. Use D = parallel.pool.DataQueue.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
