<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="instrument">
  <message>
    <entry key="toofewargs" translate="false">The DRIVER and HWOBJ must be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDriver" translate="false">DRIVER must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidType" translate="false">HWOBJ must be an interface object.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidLength" translate="false">HWOBJ must be a 1-by-1 interface object.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidobj" translate="false">HWOBJ must be a valid interface object.</entry>
    <entry key="newerdriver" translate="false">This driver requires a newer version of Instrument Control Toolbox</entry>
    <entry key="futuredriver" translate="false">This driver was created with a newer version of the Instrument Control Toolbox</entry>
    <entry key="no64bitMATLABSupport" translate="false">IVI-COM instrument drivers are not supported in 64-bit MATLAB.  As an alternative, use an IVI-C driver or use instrument interfaces, like VISA, to configure your instrument using SCPI commands.  Click &lt;a href="http://www.mathworks.com/ivi64com"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidStateError" translate="false">The QueryInstrumentStatus is not enabled.  Errors may not be properly reported.</entry>
    <entry key="driverNotFound" translate="false">DRIVER could not be found. The DRIVER must be on the MATLAB path.</entry>
    <entry key="MATLAB32bitSupportDeprecated" translate="false">IVI-COM functionality will no longer be available starting in MATLAB R2016a. 32-bit and 64-bit IVI-C drivers are supported on both 32-bit and 64-bit MATLAB, respectively. It is recommended to use the IVI-C driver instead of the IVI-COM driver.</entry>
    <entry key="instrfindOrInstrfindall">instrfind or instrfindall</entry>
    <entry key="useIcdeviceSupportedAPI">{0} is not supported by legacy icdevice. Create the icdevice object with name-value argument LegacyMode=false.</entry>
    <entry key="expectedHardwareObjectType">Hardware interface object must be a serial, tcpip, visa, or gpib object.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
