<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2025 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<!-- Model advisor checks and messages -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Stateflow" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationTitle">Check output dimensions of MATLAB Function blocks</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationTips">Check the model for MATLAB Function blocks that have the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property enabled. If this property is enabled, the block converts output column vectors of size N-by-1 to one-dimensional signals with a signal size equal to N. Before R2021b, MATLAB Function blocks always had this property enabled.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationActionName">Fix it</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationActionDescription">Click the Fix it button to disable the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property in the listed MATLAB Function blocks that have multidimensional outputs.</entry> 
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationActionResult">Disabled the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property in the listed MATLAB Function blocks that have multidimensional outputs.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationUnorientedVectorsFailMessage">These MATLAB Function blocks produce one-dimensional outputs and have the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property enabled:</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationFailMessage">These MATLAB Function blocks have the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property enabled:</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationFailRecommendation">Disable the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property of the listed MATLAB Function blocks. You can also modify the same using &apos;VectorOutputs1D&apos; property in &apos;MATLABFunctionConfiguration&apos;.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationUnorientedVectorsFailRecommendation">Disable the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property of the listed MATLAB Function blocks. If this property is enabled, the block converts output column vectors of size N-by-1 to one-dimensional signals with a signal size equal to N. This changes the size propagation behavior of these blocks. As a result, clicking the Fix it button does not update the property of these blocks.</entry>
        <entry key="OutputInterpretationPassMessage">The model does not contain any MATLAB Function blocks with the &apos;Interpret output column vectors as one-dimensional data&apos; property enabled.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
