<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Stateflow" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="ChooseCustomPatternDir">You have not yet chosen a folder for storing custom patterns for use with the Stateflow Pattern Wizard. Please choose a folder where you want to store files for the custom patterns. This preference will be remembered for future sessions. Please make sure you have write permissions to this folder if you are going to add your own patterns.</entry>
    <entry key="SelectAndTryAgain">No Stateflow pattern selected. Select a pattern to save.</entry>
    <entry key="ErrorAddingPattern">Error while loading pattern.</entry>
    <entry key="NoChartOpen">Open a Stateflow chart before inserting a pattern.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCreatePattern">Unable to create pattern. Make sure you do not have any other models with the same name loaded.</entry>
    <entry key="FindLoadedModelsTip">TIP: Try the following command to see if any models with the same name are loaded into memory.\n\nopen_bd = find_system(''type'', ''block_diagram'')</entry>
    <entry key="UnsavedChangesError">Model has unsaved changes. Please save the model and retry.</entry>
    <entry key="ModelHasNoSFCharts">{0} model does not contain any Stateflow charts.</entry>
    <entry key="MoreThanOneSFChart"> Error while adding pattern because the model ''{0}'' contains more than one chart or an atomic subchart.</entry>
    <entry key="ModelContainsEmptyChart">Nothing to add. {0} model contains an empty Stateflow chart.</entry>
    <entry key="NoSavedPatternsFound">No saved patterns found.</entry>
    <entry key="NotAValidMATLABFile">Invalid file type. Select a MATLAB script or function file.</entry>
    <entry key="InputFileIsNotFormedCorrectly">MATLAB file contains a syntax error.</entry>
    <entry key="NestedFunctionsConversionIsNotSupported">Conversion of nested functions is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="ClassConversionIsNotSupported">Conversion of MATLAB classes is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="StandaloneStateflowChartsForExecutionInMATLAB">Conversion of MATLAB code to graphical functions is supported only in standalone Stateflow charts for execution in MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="NoDefaultTransition">Error arranging graphical function. Add missing default transition.</entry>
    <entry key="NoFunctionHandle"> Error arranging graphical function. Select a graphical function to arrange.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
