<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <entry key="BadFilename">File name must be a non-empty string or character vector.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidOption">Invalid value ''{1}'' specified for ''{0}''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidWriteVars">Input must be a cell array with {0,number,integer} elements.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidWrite">Unable to write to file: {0}\n{1}</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidVariableType">Variable "{0}" must have type ''{1}''</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidZeroVars">Second argument must have at least one variable.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedVariableAttributes">Variable "{0}" has attributes that are unsupported for writing to a Parquet file. Supported variable types include:\n\n    numeric, logical, categorical, datetime, duration, string, cellstr, char, cell, table, timetable\n\nChar variables can be matrices. Other non-tabular variables must be column vectors. Doubles and logicals must be non-sparse. All numeric variables must be real.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedCharVariableAttributes">Char variables must be char matrices to be written to a Parquet file.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedCellVariableAttributes">Cell variables must be cell arrays of character vectors to be written to a Parquet file.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedNestedTableAttributes">Nested table variables must contain at least one variable.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedDictionaryEncoding">Dictionary encoding is not supported for logical variable "{0}".\nSet the value of "VariableEncoding" to ''auto'' or ''plain'' encoding for this variable.</entry>
        <entry key="WrongOptionNumel">''{0}'' must have {1,number,integer} elements.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDirectory">Unable to find directory: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="DivByZeroRowGroupHeights">"RowGroupHeights" specified as a scalar cannot be zero when the input table has a positive height: {0} row(s).\n\nSpecify a positive scalar value for "RowGroupHeights".</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRowGroupHeightsSum">"RowGroupHeights" input: {1} sums up to the value: {2}. "RowGroupHeights" specified as a vector must sum up to the height of the input table: {0} row(s).</entry>
        <entry key="RowGroupedListOfDictionaries">''{0}'' is a LIST of DICTIONARY arrays written to multiple row groups. LIST of DICTIONARY arrays must be read using the parquetread RowGroups name-value argument.</entry>
        <entry key="NestedRowGroupedListOfDictionaries">''{0}'' contains a LIST of DICTIONARY arrays written to multiple row groups. LIST of DICTIONARY arrays must be read using the parquetread RowGroups name-value argument.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedIRI">Unable to write Parquet file "{0}". Unrecognized URL scheme.</entry>

        <!--     Internal Errors   -->
        <entry key="LeafColumnPathsEmpty">The offsets and paths vectors must be non-empty.</entry>
        <entry key="LeafColumnPathsOffsetsAcending">The offsets vector must be in ascending order.</entry>
        <entry key="LeafColumnPathsSizeMismatch">The last value in the offsets vector must be equal to the size of the paths vector.</entry>
        <entry key="LeafColumnPathsNumTopLevelCols">The number of top-level variables encoded in ColumnLeafsPath is {0,number,integer}. Expected the number of top-level variables to be {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
