<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="OperatorNotSupported">Operator is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTraverseFcn">Not enough arguments. The "traverse" method must have one or more input arguments and one or more output arguments.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidVariableName">Variable name "{0}" is not a selected variable. Filter constraints can only be applied on selected variables:\n\n    {1}\n\n</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFilterInput">Input argument must be a table or timetable.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFilterOperand">Data type of operand not supported for filtering. Supported operand data types are: numeric, string, logical, datetime, duration scalars, or character vectors.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperationOperand">Relational operators (&gt;, &lt;, &gt;=, &lt;=, ==, ~=) with multiple rowfilter or eventfilter inputs are not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperatorInputs">Relational operator must have a rowfilter or eventfilter object as input.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">Invalid binary operator input. Both operands must be rowfilter or eventfilter objects.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForRelationalOperator">Unsupported relational operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForBinaryOperator">Unsupported binary operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>

        <entry key="MissingNotSupported">Missing values are not supported as operands to RowFilter.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRowFilterInput">Invalid input to the "rowfilter" function. Input must be one of the following:\n - string vector, character vector, or cell array of character vectors\n - ParquetInfo object\n - ParquetDatastore object\n - DatabaseDatastore object\n - table or timetable.</entry>

        <entry key="InvalidIndexingOperation">Unsupported filtering operation. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingInput">Unsupported dot indexing input for filtering. Use a string scalar or a character vector to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingVariableNames">Unrecognized variable name for filtering. Select a variable for filtering using one of the following variable names: {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedDotAssignment">Unsupported filtering operation. rowfilter and eventfilter variables cannot be set using dot assignment.</entry>

        <entry key="UnsupportedClassVersion">Could not load matlab.io.RowFilter due to version incompatibility.\nConsider re-constructing the RowFilter.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFilterClass">Invalid class "{0}" for RowFilter dispatcher.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">Unable to use a row filter to subscript into the variables of a table, timetable, or event table. Specify rows using the syntax T(rf,vars), where rf specifies a row filter and vars specifies variables of T.</entry>
        <entry key="RelationalOperationFailed">Unable to apply constraint: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedType">Unexpected type returned from relational operator in the "{0}" expression. A logical vector was expected but the expression returned a value of "{1}" type.</entry>
        <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedDimensions">Logical matrix of unexpected dimensions returned from relational operator in the "{0}" expression. The result must be an empty logical array or a logical column vector. But the expression returned a {1} logical matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedHeight">Unexpected number of rows returned from relational operator in the "{0}" expression. Expected {1} row(s) but the expression returned a logical vector with {2} row(s).</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
