<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="remote_connectivity" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
	<message>
		<entry key="lockedByLocalExecutor">
			Error executing process on user's machine. Retry command execution request.
		</entry>
		<entry key="lessArguments">
			Not enough arguments provided to replace command placeholders in command. Verify all required parameters are included.
		</entry>
		<entry key="invalidPlaceholder">
			Unrecognized placeholder in command. Ensure placeholders are valid and match the expected format.
		</entry>
		<entry key="moreArguments">
			Too many arguments for placeholders. Ensure argument count matches placeholder count in the command.
		</entry>
		<entry key="notSupportedComponent">
			The requested Support Package is not enabled on the machine. Rerun the setup screens to enable it.
		</entry>
		<entry key="keyNotInRecord">
			Trigger missing in the command record. Ensure the command and its associated trigger are correctly recorded and accessible.
		</entry>
		<entry key="lockedByOnline">
			MATLAB Online is currently using the Remote Process Executor. Wait for its release and try again.
		</entry>
		<entry key="inValidArgument">
			Invalid argument. Ensure valid arguments are passed.
		</entry>
		<entry key="emptyTrigger">
			Trigger not sent from MATLAB Online. Include trigger in MATLAB Online request.
		</entry>
		<entry key="invalidTrigger">
			Invalid trigger provided. Verify the trigger with the expected format and values.
		</entry>
		<entry key="preferenceNotSet">
			Unexpected error while accessing third party tools. Rerun the setup screens.
		</entry>
		<entry key="unKnownException">
			An unknown error occurred during process execution. Retry the previous action. If the issue persists, rerun the setup screens.
		</entry>
		<entry key="userRejectedAccess">
			User rejected the command execution request.
		</entry>
		<entry key="notifyEnableSPKGHeadings">
			Permission to Enable Support Package
		</entry>
		<entry key="notifyEnableSPKGTextInitial">
			MATLAB Online is attempting to enable
		</entry>
		<entry key="notifyEnableSPKGTextEnd">
			on this machine. Do you want to continue?
		</entry>
		<entry key="rpeShowNotifyHeading">
			Permission to Execute Command
		</entry>
		<entry key="rpeNotifyFlashingHeading">
			Permission to Flash Hardware
		</entry>
	</message>
</rsccat>
