<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2015-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="sheetNumber">Sheet number must be a positive finite integer.</entry>
    <entry key="workbookEnumMode">Pass ''0'' for LibXL, ''1'' for COM, and ''2'' for Google Sheets. All other inputs are invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="filenameArg" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">The second input must be a character vector specifying the name of an existing file.</entry>
    <entry key="creation">Could not create a workbook.</entry>
    <entry key="fileOpen">Unable to open file ''{0}'' as a workbook. Check that the file exists, read access is available, and the file is a valid spreadsheet file.</entry>
    <entry key="createSheet">Could not create or initialize Worksheet.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSheetSpec" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Invalid data type. ''Sheet'' input must be a character vector specifying the sheet name or a positive finite integer specifying the sheet index.</entry>
    <entry key="openSheetName">Sheet name ''{0}'' does not exist or is not supported. To check if the sheet is supported, specify the sheet by its worksheet index.</entry>
    <entry key="openSheetIndex">Sheet index {0,number,integer} exceeds the number of sheets in the workbook.</entry>
    <entry key="saveFilenameFmt">The file name ''{0}'' is incompatible with the format ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="save">Unable to save the workbook to file ''{0}''. Check that write permissions are available, there is sufficient disk space, and the file can be written to or created.</entry>
    <entry key="sheetNames" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Sheet names must be a string array with the same number of elements as the number of sheets in the workbook.</entry>
    <entry key="sheetNameExists">The sheet named ''{0}'' already exists.</entry>
    <entry key="internalError">An internal error occurred.</entry>
    <entry key="fileTypeUnsupported">File extension ''{0}'' is not supported on computers without Excel for Windows or when ''UseExcel'' is set to false.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSheetName">Invalid sheet name. Name must be text and contain 1-31 characters, excluding :, \\, /, ?, *, [, and ].</entry>
    <entry key="invalidGoogleSheetName">Invalid sheet name. Name must be text and contain 1-100 characters.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFormat">File extension is not supported in this context. Ensure the extension is one of the following: ''XLSX'', ''XLS'', ''XLSM'', ''XLSB'', ''XLTX'', ''XLTM'', or ''ODS''.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFormatUnix">File extension is not supported in this context. Ensure the extension is one of the following: ''XLSX'', ''XLS'', ''XLSM'', ''XLTX'', or ''XLTM''.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedFormat">The ''{0}'' format is not supported in this context. Set the ''UseExcel'' parameter to true on Windows with Excel installed to read and write ''XLSB'' or ''ODS'' files and spreadsheets with interactive features, such as formulas and macros.</entry>
    <entry key="chartsheetError">Chart sheets are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="interrupt">Unable to write file.</entry>
    <entry key="noExcel">Using Excel for reading and writing spreadsheet files is only supported on Windows. Switching ''UseExcel'' to false.</entry>
    <entry key="webserviceExcelWarn">Using Excel is not recommended for web apps. Switch ''UseExcel'' to false.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
