<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2021 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
      <!-- blelist -->
      <entry key="unsupportedPlatform">Scanning and connecting to Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices are not supported on Linux.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedMacOS">Scanning and connecting to Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices are not supported on macOS 10.12 Sierra or earlier.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedWindows">Scanning and connecting to Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices are not supported on Windows 8 or earlier.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidMacBluetoothState">Bluetooth Low Energy is not supported on this computer or Bluetooth is not turned on.</entry>
      <entry key="macBluetoothPoweredOff">Bluetooth is not turned on or your computer was in sleep mode. Make sure Bluetooth is turned on before proceeding.</entry>
      <entry key="macBluetoothNotAuthorized">Bluetooth permission is not enabled for MATLAB. Allow MATLAB or Terminal to use Bluetooth from the Security &amp; Privacy settings.</entry>
      <entry key="noDeviceFound">No nearby Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices detected. Try a larger ''timeout'' value.</entry>
      <entry key="noDeviceWithNameFound">No nearby Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices with a name starting with this string detected. Try calling blelist with a larger ''timeout'' value.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidUUIDType" note="Keep 'Service'(domain-specific term) in English">Invalid data type for UUID. Service value must be a string or hexadecimal.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidServiceUUIDValue" note="Keep 'service'(domain-specific term) and 'services'(domain-specific term) in English">Invalid value for service. See &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bluetooth.com/specifications/gatt/services&quot;&gt;Bluetooth SIG webpage&lt;/a&gt; for a list of valid services.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidCharacteristicUUIDValue" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Invalid value for characteristic. See ble object for list of valid characteristic values.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDescriptorUUIDValue"  note="Keep 'descriptor'(domain-specific term) and 'characteristic'(object) in English">Invalid value for descriptor. See characteristic object for list of valid descriptor values.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNVPair">Unrecognized parameter. Parameter name must be one of the following: {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidTimeoutValue">Invalid ''timeout'' value specified. Value must be a numeric between {0} and {1}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNameValue">Invalid ''name'' value specified. Value must be a string or character vector.</entry>
      <entry key="failToScan">Failed to detect nearby Bluetooth Low Energy peripheral devices. Contact Technical Support if issue persists.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothlistReference">Run &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:bluetoothlist&quot;&gt;bluetoothlist&lt;/a&gt; to search for nearby Bluetooth classic devices.</entry>
      
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationRadioNotAvailable">Bluetooth radio is not available or turned off.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationConsentRequired">Operation requires consent.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationDeviceNotConnected">Operation cannot be completed because the remote device is not connected.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationDisabledByUser">Operation is disabled by the user.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationDisabledByPolicy">Operation is disabled by policy.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationNotSupported">Operation is not supported on the current Bluetooth radio hardware.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationResourceInUse">Operation cannot be serviced because the necessary resources are currently in use.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationTransportNotSupported">Transport is not supported.</entry>
      <entry key="bluetoothOperationOtherError">Unexpected error has occurred.</entry>
      
      <!-- ble -->
      <entry key="nosave">Saving object of type {0} to a MAT file is not supported.</entry>
      <entry key="bleCalledWithoutInput">Not enough input arguments. Specify device address or device name as a string or character vector.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidIdentifier">Invalid device identifier. Device name or address must be specified as a string or character vector.</entry>
      <entry key="ambiguousDeviceName">Multiple devices found with device name {0}. Specify one of the following addresses to connect: {1}.</entry>
      <entry key="undiscoveredDevice">Unable to find device with specified name or address. Check device status and run blelist to find device.</entry>
      <entry key="unconnectableDevice">This device does not support connections or it is currently not connectable. If device is connected elsewhere, disconnect from it and run blelist first.</entry>
      <entry key="connectionExists">Connection to this device already exists in the workspace.</entry>
      <entry key="deviceDisconnected">Device is disconnected.</entry>
      <entry key="failToConnect">Failed to connect to device. Make sure device is within proper range and not connected elsewhere. For more information, see Troubleshooting section in Documentation.</entry>
      <entry key="failToDisconnect">Failed to disconnect from device.</entry>
      <entry key="failToGetStatus">Failed to get device status.</entry>
      <entry key="failToDiscoverServices" note="Keep 'services'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to discover services. If issue persists, see Troubleshooting section in Documentation for more information.</entry>
      <entry key="failToDiscoverCharacteristics" note="Keep 'characteristics'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to discover characteristics.</entry>
      <entry key="serviceAccessDenied" note="Keep 'service'(domain-specific term) in English">Access to {0} service with UUID {1} was denied.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationAccessDenied">Operation failed because access was denied.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorLikelyInvalidPermissionMac">Operation failed likely because authentication was insufficient. Try pairing device to the computer.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorInsufficientAuthentication">Operation failed because authentication was insufficient. Try pairing device and recreate ble object.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorInsufficientEncryption">Operation failed because encryption was insufficient.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorInsufficientAuthorization">Operation failed because authorization was insufficient.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorReadNotPermitted">Operation failed because read is not permitted.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorWriteNotPermitted">Operation failed because write is not permitted.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorOthersMac">Operation failed because there was an unexpected error.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationProtocolErrorUnknown">Operation failed because there was an unknown error.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationUnreachable">Operation failed because device is unreachable. Check if device is within proper range.</entry>
      <entry key="gattCommunicationUnknown">Operation failed with unknown error.</entry>

      <!-- characteristic -->
      <entry key="unsupportedService" note="Keep 'service'(domain-specific term) in English">Unsupported service. See ble object properties for a list of supported service UUIDs and names.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedCharacteristic" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Unsupported characteristic. See ble object properties for a list of supported characteristic UUIDs and names.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidUUIDNameCustom" note="Keep 'service'(domain-specific term) and 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Specify UUID for custom service or characteristic.</entry>
      <entry key="failToDiscoverDescriptors"  note="Keep 'descriptors'(domain-specific term)">Failed to discover descriptors. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedOperation">Operation is not supported on this object.</entry>
      <entry key="noDataAvailableFcnAccess"  note="Keep 'characteristic'(object) in English">DataAvailableFcn is not supported on this characteristic object because it does not support Notify or Indicate.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedWriteType" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term and object) in English">This characteristic does not support this type of write. See characteristic object Attributes for supported types.</entry>
      <entry key="duplicateWriteOptions">Invalid input combination. Specify type, precision or both.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDataType">Invalid data type. Data must be a scalar or an array of integers.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDataRanged">Data must be between {0} and {1}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDataAvailableFcn">Invalid value for DataAvailableFcn. Specify [] or a function handle that accepts two inputs.</entry>
      <entry key="callbackError">Error in {0}(line {1})\n{2}\n\n</entry>
      <entry key="failToReadCharacteristic" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to read characteristic. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="failToWriteCharacteristic" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to write characteristic. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="failToSubscribeCharacteristic" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to subscribe to characteristic. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="failToUnsubscribeCharacteristic" note="Keep 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to unsubscribe to characteristic. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="noDataAvailable">Device has not sent new data. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidSubscriptionType">Invalid subscription type value. Value must be one of the following: {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidModeReadOnly">Invalid mode value. Value must be {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidModeNotifyOnly">Invalid mode value. Value must be one of the following: {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidModeReadNotify">Subscribe to notification or indication before reading oldest data.</entry>
      <entry key="deviceProfileChanged">Device profile has changed. Clear existing ble object with address {0} and recreate it.</entry>
      
      <!-- descriptor -->
      <entry key="unsupportedDescriptor" note="Keep 'descriptor'(domain-specific term) and 'characteristic'(object) in English">Unsupported descriptor. See characteristic object properties for a list of supported descriptor UUIDs and names.</entry>
      <entry key="noDescriptors" note="Keep 'descriptor'(domain-specific term) and 'characteristic'(domain-specific term) in English">No descriptors found for this characteristic.</entry>
      <entry key="failToReadDescriptor" note="Keep 'descriptor'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to read descriptor. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      <entry key="failToWriteDescriptor" note="Keep 'descriptor'(domain-specific term) in English">Failed to write descriptor. If device is disconnected, then clear existing ble object and recreate it.</entry>
      
      <entry key="invalidAsyncioChannel">Invalid type of asyncio channel.</entry>
      <entry key="unknownExecuteCommand">Internal error - Unrecognized execute command. Contact Technical Support for assistance.</entry>
      <entry key="executeTimeout">Failed to get a response from device.</entry>
      <entry key="failToExecuteDeviceDisconnected">Device is disconnected to the computer. Clear and recreate ble object.</entry>
      <entry key="failToExecute">Failed to execute the command.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidSubscriptionStatus">Internal error - Invalid subscription status {0}.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>