<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013-2025 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Spcuilib" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidNumPortsArrayFormat">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'' format for logging multiport data.
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset'', ''Structure'', or ''Structure with time''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNumDimensionsArrayFormat">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'' format for logging matrix signals.
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset'', ''Structure'', or ''Structure with time''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="StructureNoSupportForMultiRate">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'', ''Structure'' and ''Structure with time'' formats for multi-rate systems. 
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidVarDimensionsArrayFormat">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'' format for logging variable-size signals. 
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Structure'' or ''Structure with time''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDataStructureWithTimeFormat">
        Simulink does not support ''Structure with time'' format for logging frame-based data. 
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset'' or ''Structure''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDataArrayFormat">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'' format for logging frame-based data.
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset'' or ''Structure''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ScopeNoRTWSupportForDataset">The Scope block ''{0}'' has the ''SaveFormat'' parameter set to ''{1}''. This format is supported only for normal and accelerator mode simulations.
    No data will be logged for this block.  To log this signal in other simulation modes, consider using a To File block or changing the ''SaveFormat'' parameter to ''Structure With Time''. To log this signal in
    code generation targets, consider using output logging.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ArrayNoSupportForComplex">
        Simulink does not support ''Array'' format for logging Complex data.
        Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset'',''Structure'' or ''Structure with time''.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ScopeNoArchivingSupportForDataset">
        The Scope block has the ''SaveFormat'' parameter set to ''Dataset''. This format is supported only for normal and accelerator mode simulations.
        Data will be archived in ''Structure with time'' format for this block.
    </entry>
	<entry key="ScopeNoSupportParsim">
		Unable to open ''{0}'' because you are simulating the model using parsim.
		Clear the ''Open at Simulation Start'' parameter or simulate the model without using parsim.
	</entry>
    <entry key="NoSupportEnumSysObj">
        System objects do not support ''Enumeration'' type or ''Objects'' as inputs. 
        Pass a valid ''Numeric'' type to the Step function.
    </entry>
    <entry key="busSignalNotSupported">
        Scope cannot accept a bus as its input signal. Insert a Bus to Vector conversion block in the signal path or 
        extract signals using a Bus Selector block. To view the options associated with this message, in the Configuration Parameters 
        dialog box, select Diagnostics > Connectivity; under Buses, see Bus signal treated as vector.
    </entry>    
    <entry key="invalidNumberOfInputPortsFrameBased">
        Invalid number of input ports for frame-based input data archiving. Turn external mode data archiving off, 
        modify the Scope block to have a single input port or process data as samples.
    </entry>    
    <entry key="InvalidDimensionsModeDatasetFormat">
        Dataset logging is not supported for variable-size signals. Consider using Structure or Structure with Time format. 
    </entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedDataType">
        The input data type must be double precision, single precision, or fixed point.
    </entry>
    <entry key="invalidNumberOfInputPorts">
        The ''Number of Input Ports'' parameter must be a finite integer scalar between 1 and 96.
    </entry>
    <entry key="BlockDescription">
        Displays input signals with respect to simulation time
    </entry>
    <entry key="NumInputPorts">
        Number of input ports:
    </entry>   
     <entry key="DimsOrPropertyMismatch">
         Bus (multiplexed) signals with matrices or non-matching properties cannot be viewed with a Floating Scope.
         Unselect the signal and select the individual signals instead.
     </entry>
     <entry key="OutOfMemoryErrorLowerBufferLength">
         Out of memory.  Try reducing the buffer length of the Scope ''{0}''.
     </entry>
     <entry key="InvalidScopeBlockConstruction">
         A ScopeBlock object cannot be constructed for ''{0}''.
     </entry>
     <entry key="sigLicenseFailed">
         A DSP System Toolbox license is required in ''{0}'' when the 'Input processing' parameter is set to 'Columns as channels (frame based)'.
     </entry>
     <entry key="LoggingOutOfMemory">
         Scope out of memory. Consider limiting data points using "Limit data points to last" in the Configuration Properties - Logging tab.
     </entry>
	 <entry key="ScopeBlockErrorPreamble">
		 Error in ''{0}'':
	 </entry>
	 
     <entry key="LoggingFormatNotSupportedNonvirtualBus">
         The Scope block ''{0}'' has the logging format set to ''{1}''. Simulink does not support ''Array'', ''Structure'', and ''Structure with time'' formats for nonvirtual bus signal. 
         Change the logging format of the Scope to ''Dataset''.
     </entry>
     <entry key="SimulationModeNotSupportedNonvirtualBus">
         The Scope block ''{0}'' does not support nonvirtual bus signal in rapid accelerator and external mode simulation. Either run the model in normal or accelerator mode, or
         separate the nonvirtual bus elements using a Bus Selector block and connect them to different ports of the Scope.
     </entry>
     <entry key="FramesNotSupportedNonvirtualBus">
         The Scope block ''{0}'' does not support nonvirtual bus signal with elements having different number of rows when processing columns as frames. Either switch to processing elements as channels, or
         separate these elements using a Bus Selector block and connect them to different ports of the Scope.
     </entry>
     <entry key="VarSizeNotSupportedNonvirtualBus">
         The Scope block ''{0}'' does not support nonvirtual bus containing variable-size elements. Separate the
         variable-size elements from the nonvirtual bus using a Bus Selector block and connect them to different ports of the Scope.
     </entry>
     <entry key="InvalidBusElementDataType">
        The Scope block ''{0}'' does not support nonvirtual bus containing elements of data type ''{1}''. 
     </entry>
     <entry key="InvInputBooleanComplexSignal"><![CDATA[
         <sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}">Input port {0,number,integer}</sldiag> of ''{1}'' is a nonvirtual bus containing elements
         of data type ''boolean''. Boolean signals cannot be complex.
     ]]></entry>
     <entry key="InvInputFixptComplexSignal"><![CDATA[
         <sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}">Input port {0,number,integer}</sldiag> of ''{1}'' is a nonvirtual bus containing elements of fixed-point data type ''{2}'' with non-zero bias or slope that is not a power of 2. This signal cannot be complex.
     ]]></entry>
     <entry key="InvInputEnumTypeComplexSignal"><![CDATA[
         <sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}">Input port {0,number,integer}</sldiag> of ''{1}'' is a nonvirtual bus containing elements of enumerated data type ''{2}''. Enumerated signals cannot be complex.
     ]]></entry>
	 <entry key="SaveToWorkspaceNotSupportedWithRowMajorAndMatFileLogging">
         Scope block ''{0}'' does not support saving a signal to workspace for row-major array layout with MAT file logging.
     </entry>
	 <entry key="OutOfMemoryErrorInputData">
		 Out of memory. Reduce the size of input signal for ''{0}'' block.
     </entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
