<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2009-2011 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Spcuilib" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidMaxNumTimeStepsValue" translate="false">
      Invalid value for MaxNumTimeSteps. The value must be an integer greater than 0.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMaxNumTimeStepsSize" translate="false">
      Invalid size for MaxNumTimeSteps. The number of values cannot change, but a scalar will be expanded to match the original number of values.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMaxNumTimeStepsChange" translate="false">
      Invalid values for MaxNumTimeSteps. The values must be unique. To change to non-unique values, construct a new TimeBuffer object.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMaxDimensionsSinglePort" translate="false">
      Invalid value for MaxDimensions. The value for a single port TimeBuffer should be either a 1D vector.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMaxDimensions" translate="false">
      Invalid value for MaxDimensions. The value should be a 2D matrix or a cell array.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNPorts" translate="false">
      Invalid value for NPorts. The value should be a positive integer.
    </entry>  
    <entry key="InvalidMaxDimensionsForNPorts" translate="false">
      Invalid size for MaxDimensions. For 2D matrix, the number of rows should be equal to the number of ports.
      For a cell array, the number of cell elements should be equal to the number of ports.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBufferType" translate="false">
      Invalid BufferType. The value should be either "SingleRate" or "MultipleRate".
    </entry>
    <entry key="InitializeError" translate="false">
      Error during TimeBuffer construction.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ClearError" translate="false">
      Error in TimeBuffer.clear.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ClearBackToDataTypeError" translate="false">
      Invalid value for cutoff time in TimeBuffer.clearBackTo. The value should be a numeric scalar.
    </entry>
    <entry key="ClearBackToError" translate="false">
      Error in TimeBuffer.clearBackTo.
    </entry>
    <entry key="AddValueDataTypeError" translate="false">
      Invalid input value in TimeBuffer.addValue. The value should be a numeric matrix.
    </entry>
    <entry key="AddValueError" translate="false">
      Error in TimeBuffer.addValue. The dimension of Value should match with that of the last call to TimeBuffer.addTime.
    </entry>
    <entry key="AddTimeError" translate="false">
      Error in TimeBuffer.addTime. The input value should be a 1D vector or a scalar.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortID" translate="false">
      Invalid value for portID. It should be less than or equal to the number of ports.
    </entry>
    <entry key="GetTimeAndValueError" translate="false">
      Error in TimeBuffer.getTimeAndValue. The number of values added in the TimeBuffer should match the number of time steps added.
    </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInput" translate="false">
      Invalid value for the input argument. The input argument should not be empty.
    </entry>
    <entry key="AddValueInputFormatError" translate="false">
      Invalid value for TimeBuffer.addValue. The dimensions of the input should match MaxDimensions and the number of time steps in the last call to TimeBuffer.addTime.
    </entry>
    <entry key="AddComplexDataError" translate="false">
      The port specified doesn't support complex data.
    </entry>
    <entry key="GetComplexDataError" translate="false">
     Complex Part of the data for the specified port is corrupted.  
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidComplexityDimension" translate="false">
      The size of the complexity array should be the same as the number of ports
    </entry>
    <entry key="Assertion" translate="false">
        Internal Error: Assertion.
    </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNumTimeSteps" translate="false">
        Invalid size for MaxNumTimeSteps. The number of values should be equal to the Number of Ports.
    </entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
