<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="parallel">
  <message>
    <!-- Please keep entries in sorted order -->
    <entry key="CUDADeviceStaticMethod" context="error">Method must be called using 'parallel.gpu.GPUDevice.{0}'.</entry>
    <entry key="CouldNotLoadAGpuModule" context="error">Failed to load library ''{0}''. The error was:\n{1}\n</entry>
    <entry key="CouldNotLoadDriver" context="error">Failed to load graphics driver. Unable to load library ''{0}''. The error was:\n{1}\nUpdate or reinstall your graphics driver.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceCountMode" context="error">Device count mode must be "all", "available", or "supported".</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceDeprecated" context="warning">Support for GPU devices with compute capability {0,number,integer}.{1,number,integer} will be removed in a future MATLAB release. For more information on GPU support, see &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:web('http://www.mathworks.com/help/parallel-computing/gpu-computing-requirements.html','-browser')&quot;&gt;GPU Computing Requirements&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceIndexDisplay" context="uistring">{0} (of {1})</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceInvalidated" context="error">Execution on the GPU was interrupted. To continue, reset the GPU using 'gpuDevice({0,number,integer})', or restart MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceLibsForcedRecompiling" context="warning">Recompiling GPU libraries because CUDA_FORCE_PTX_JIT is set to ''1''. Compilation can take several minutes. </entry>
    <entry key="DeviceLibsForcedRecompilingHot" context="warning">Recompiling GPU libraries because CUDA_FORCE_PTX_JIT is set to ''1''. Compilation can take several minutes. &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('parallel-computing','cuda_jitting')"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;. </entry>
    <entry key="DeviceLibsNeedRecompiling" context="warning">Recompiling GPU libraries because your device is more recent than the libraries. Compilation can take several minutes. </entry>
    <entry key="DeviceLibsNeedRecompilingHot" context="warning">Recompiling GPU libraries because your device is more recent than the libraries. Compilation can take several minutes. &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('parallel-computing','cuda_jitting')"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;. </entry>
    <entry key="DeviceMismatch" context="error">Encountered an internal error on the selected GPU device. To continue, reset the GPU using 'gpuDevice({0,number,integer})', or restart MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceNotSelected" context="error">Property can only be set for the selected GPU device. To set the property, first select the GPU using 'gpuDevice({0,number,integer})'.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceObjectLoaded" context="warning">Loaded CUDADevice object does not indicate properties of a CUDA device on this machine. Use the gpuDevice function to access CUDA devices on this computer. &lt;a href="matlab:helpview('parallel-computing','GPUDEVICE')"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceTooNew" context="error">GPU device is not supported because it has a higher compute capability ({0,number,integer}.{1,number,integer}) than is natively supported by the CUDA libraries. Use parallel.gpu.enableCUDAForwardCompatibility(true) to enable forward compatibility for GPU devices. If you enable forward compatibility, you might see unexpected behavior in GPU computations.</entry>
    <entry key="DeviceTooOld" context="error">GPU device is not supported because its compute capability is too low. The device compute capability is {0,number,integer}.{1,number,integer} but the minimum required is {2,number,integer}.{3,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverInitFailed" context="error">Failed to initialize graphics driver for computation. The CUDA error was: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="DriverLoadFailed" context="error">Failed to load graphics driver. Unable to load library ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverMissingEntryPoints" context="error">Unable to load all CUDA functions from graphics driver. Update or reinstall your graphics driver.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverRedirect" context="error">There is a problem with the graphics driver or with this GPU device.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverVersionInvalidVersionFile" context="error">Could not extract version information from ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverVersionNoDriver" context="error">Could not find graphics driver named ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverVersionNoVersionFile" context="error">Could not read version information from ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverVersionUnknownComputer" context="error">Could not calculate driver version for computer type {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="DriverVersionXMLReadFailed" context="error">Could not read version information from ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToQueryVersion" context="error">Unable to use graphics driver because ''cuDriverGetVersion'' failed. The error was:\n{0}\nUpdate or reinstall your graphics driver.</entry>
    <entry key="ForciblyInvalidated" context="error">Execution on the GPU was interrupted. To continue using this GPU device, restart MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_connect" context="error">Unable to connect to the network. Check your internet connection.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_corrupt" context="error">MATLAB installation is corrupted. If this problem persists, contact MathWorks Technical Support.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_credentials" context="error">Installer credentials are not valid. If this problem persists, contact MathWorks Technical Support.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_dest" context="error">Unable to create install destination. Check folder permissions for ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_release" context="error">The specified MATLAB release is unavailable. If this problem persists, contact MathWorks Technical Support.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFail_unknown" context="error">Installation of the Parallel Computing Toolbox GPU libraries failed. If this problem persists, contact MathWorks Technical Support.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsDownloadFailed" context="error">Installation of the Parallel Computing Toolbox GPU libraries failed. The error was: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsNotPresent" context="warning">Downloading and installing the Parallel Computing Toolbox GPU libraries (several GB) because they are not present in your system. This process can take several minutes.</entry>
    <entry key="GpuLibsNotPresentWorker" context="error">Failed to load Parallel Computing Toolbox GPU libraries. GPU functionality might not be enabled on your system. To check whether the GPU libraries are installed on your local machine, call gpuDevice. Installing the GPU libraries on parallel workers is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="InitDevProps" context="error">Encountered error when retrieving CUDA device properties. The CUDA error was:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCachePolicy" context="error">Invalid cache policy. Valid options are "maximum", "balanced", "minimum" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDeviceID" context="error">Invalid CUDA device id: {0}. Select a device id from the range 1:{1}.</entry>
    <entry key="IsAvailableNonIndexInput" context="error">Indices must be positive integers.</entry>
    <entry key="LazyEvaluationBadCap" context="error">Invalid value for the lazy evaluation cap.</entry>
    <entry key="LazyEvaluationBadPolicy" context="error">Lazy evaluation policy ''{0}'' was not recognized.</entry>
    <entry key="MacOSGPUNotSupported" context="error">GPU acceleration with Parallel Computing Toolbox is not supported on macOS.</entry>
    <entry key="MacOSGPUSupportToBeRemoved" context="warning">Support for GPU acceleration with Parallel Computing Toolbox on macOS will be removed in a future MATLAB release.</entry>
    <entry key="MacOSMojaveGPUSupportRemoved" context="error">GPU acceleration with Parallel Computing Toolbox is not supported on macOS versions 10.14 (Mojave) and above. Support for earlier macOS versions will be removed in a future MATLAB release.</entry>
    <entry key="MustBeScalarLogical" context="error">New value must be true (1) or false (0).</entry>
    <entry key="NoCUDADevice" context="error">Unable to find a supported GPU device.</entry>
    <entry key="NoDriver" context="error">Unable to load graphics driver.</entry>
    <entry key="NoLongerCurrent" context="error">Selected GPU device is in an invalid state. Try reselecting the device using the gpuDevice function.</entry>
    <entry key="OldDriver" context="error">Graphics driver is out of date. Download and install the latest graphics driver for your GPU from NVIDIA.</entry>
    <entry key="PlatformGPUNotSupported" context="error">GPU acceleration with Parallel Computing Toolbox is not supported on this platform.</entry>
    <entry key="ResetCurrent" context="error">Unable to reset CUDADevice because it is not selected. To select a CUDADevice use the gpuDevice function.</entry>
    <entry key="ResetMultipleSelection" context="warning">GPU device {0} is selected by multiple thread workers. Data for gpuArray and CUDAKernel on the other thread-workers will not be cleared. To clear all GPU memory across all thread workers, deselect this device from all workers using parfevalOnAll(@gpuDevice,0,[]).</entry>
    <entry key="RuntimeInitFailed" context="error">CUDA runtime failed to initialize correctly. This can occur with some older graphics drivers.</entry>
    <entry key="SelectDevice" context="error">Argument must be a positive integer or [].</entry>
    <entry key="SelectDeviceNotInteger" context="error">Argument must be a positive integer.</entry>
    <entry key="SelectedUnavailable" context="error">Failed to use GPU device {0}. Device is busy or unavailable.</entry>
    <entry key="SelectedUnsupported" context="error">Selected GPU device is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="ShowAllDeviceProperties" context="uistring">Show &lt;a href="matlab:disp(urldecode(''{0}''));"&gt;all properties&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="UnavailableDevice" context="error">Unable to find an available GPU device. All supported devices are in exclusive use or in prohibited compute mode.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownCUDAError" context="error">Encountered unexpected error during CUDA execution. The CUDA error was:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownOldDriver" context="error">Unable to use graphics driver because ''cuDriverGetVersion'' was not found. This can occur with old versions of the graphics drivers. The library name used was ''{0}''. Update or reinstall your graphics driver.</entry>
    <entry key="WorkerUnavailableDevice" context="error">Worker {0} failed to use GPU device {1}. Device is already in use.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
