<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--Copyright 2009-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="SimulinkFixedPoint" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="sharedGroupWarningPropagation">This result belongs to DTGroup {0}. The data types of one or more elements of this group may result in update diagram errors. View the DTGroup by adding the DTGroup column to the spreadsheet.</entry>
    <entry key="GetAutoscalerConstraint">''{0}'' of ''{1}'' accepts {2}.</entry>
	<entry key="GetMonotonicityConstraint">''{0}'' of ''{1}'' accepts only fixed-point types that allow values to be strictly monotonically increasing. This restriction can lead to a scenario where the proposed word length and fraction length do not match the default settings.</entry>
	<entry key="clashWithMonotonicityConstraint">Results that must share the same data type have conflicting restrictions on the fixed-point types they can accept.</entry>
    <entry key="HardwareSettings">Hardware settings</entry>
    <entry key="GetHardwareConstraint" translate="false">{0} of {1} allow the following word lengths: {2}.</entry>
	<entry key="SumHardwareConstraint" translate="false">Cannot add two hardware constraints.</entry>
	<entry key="WordlengthOutOfBounds" translate="false">Wordlength must be between 1 and 128.</entry>
    <entry key="ExplicitValuesNotEvenlySpaced">Breakpoint values must be perfectly evenly spaced to be represented by a fixed-point data type.</entry>
	<entry key="isSpacingPerfectlyEvenInputValidation" translate="false">Input values must be a vector with 2 or more elements.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownBusObjectName">Unknown bus object ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="UndefinedPixelControlBus">Undefined bus object ''pixelcontrol''. Please enter ''pixelcontrolbus'' at the command prompt and propose again.</entry>
    <entry key="CodeGenMacroConstraint">This parameter object appears in the generated code as a macro due to its custom storage class.  The Fixed-Point Tool does not autoscale parameter objects which appear as a macro in the generated code. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidClassName">Invalid class name. </entry>
    <entry key="mustBeString" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">{0} must be a character vector. </entry>
    <entry key="conflictingConstraints">Results that must share the same data type have conflicting restrictions on the {0} of the fixed-point type.</entry>
    <entry key="incompatibleConstraints">Incompatible datatype requirements: {0} cannot be restricted to both ''{1}'' and ''{2}''. </entry>
    <entry key="NoFxptSupportForTrigFunction">sin, cos, sincos, cos + jsin and atan2 functions using a CORDIC approximation method accept only fixed-point types. This block is configured for ''{0}'' function with ''{1}'' approximation method.</entry>
    <entry key="blockOutsideSubSystem">Result is outside subsystem to be scaled.</entry>
    <entry key="overflowCount">Overflow occurred {0,number,integer} time(s).</entry>
    <entry key="saturationCount">Saturation occurred {0,number,integer} time(s).</entry>
    <entry key="paramSatCount">Parameter saturation occurred {0,number,integer} time(s).</entry>
    <entry key="divByZeroCount">Division by zero occurred {0,number,integer} time(s).</entry>
    <entry key="blockDTCantAutoscale">Data type parameter on this block cannot be autoscaled.</entry>
    <entry key="lockedDTFromMask">Data type in this block is locked from parent mask.</entry>
    <entry key="dtFieldNotExist">Parameter ''''{0}'''' does not exist in the block.</entry>
    <entry key="BusNotSupported">The data type is specified via a bus object and cannot be autoscaled.</entry>
    <entry key="evalToEnumDT">The data type of ''''{0}'''' resolves to an enumerated data type and cannot be autoscaled.</entry>
    <entry key="aliasDTShared">The alias data type may not match the proposed data type of its DTGroup. This may cause data type propagation errors. View the DTGroup by adding the DTGroup column to the spreadsheet.</entry>
    <entry key="engineInterfaceFail">Update diagram on model failed. Please check the model before propose scaling. </entry>
    <entry key="autoscaleProposeFail">Autoscaling proposal failed. Cannot handle certain signals. </entry>
    <entry key="loggedSubsystem">Logged subsystem results only. Cannot be autoscaled.  </entry>
    <entry key="noContainerType">The Fixed-Point Tool cannot propose a data type for this result because the specified data type is ''''{0}''''. To get a data type proposal, the specified data type of the result must be either floating-point, fixed-point or use an inheritance rule.</entry>
    <entry key="notValidRange">The collected range is not valid. Unable to propose a valid data type.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSFData">Invalid Stateflow data object result.</entry>
    <entry key="topLinkNotMask">This item can''t be autoscaled.  This item is located under a library link, and the link does not provide a mask parameter that maps to the data type specification of this item.</entry>
    <entry key="underMaskNotSupportAutoscaling">This item is under a masked block that does not support autoscaling.</entry>
    <entry key="maskSupportsAutoscalingButUnknownItem">This item is under a masked block.  The mask does not support autoscaling for this item.</entry>
    <entry key="notNormalMode">You can only propose fraction lengths if the model's Simulation mode is set to Normal. To prevent this error, go to the model's Simulation menu and change the mode to Normal.</entry>
    <entry key="commandNotFound" translate="false">Command cannot be found. Use "Collect", "Propose" or "Apply" to specify actions.</entry>
    <entry key="topSubsysNotValid">System to scale cannot be found. Use block diagram object or subsystem object to specify.</entry>
    <entry key="unspecifiedSign">The data type cannot have an unspecified sign.</entry>
    <entry key="actionNotSupport">Action is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="dataInMATLABBlk">Autoscale is not supported for data used in MATLAB Function block.</entry>
    <entry key="inheritFromBusObj">Specify via bus object</entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedbuiltinIntegerOnly">built-in integers only</entry>
    <entry key="limitedDblBoolUFix1">only double, Boolean and ufix1 </entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedintegerOnly">integers only</entry>
    <entry key="ConstraintFromInport">Input port </entry>
    <entry key="ConstraintFromOutport">Output port </entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedbooleanOnly">boolean only  </entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedFunctionCall">function call signal only  </entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedfloatingpointOnly">floating point only  </entry>
    <entry key="NoChangeAtMdlRefBoundary"> only existing data types  </entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedwordlengthOnly">only word lengths between {0} and {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedFloatPointOnlyWhenComplex">The constraint applies only when input is complex.</entry>
    <entry key="modelTerminationFailed">Cannot close and restore model. Unfortunately you must quit MATLAB now using "exit force".</entry>
    <entry key="RACheckSolverVariableStep"> If you want to perform range derivation on this model, you must first change its Solver configuration parameter setting to specify a fixed-step, discrete solver.</entry>
    <entry key="configParamNotMatch">System parameter ''''{0}'''' is expected to be set to ''''{1}'''' but remains ''''{2}''''</entry>
    <entry key="multiwordWLMicro">The word length selection exceeds the size for long specified on the Hardware Implementation pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box. Multi-word representation is proposed.</entry>
    <entry key="licenseCheck">Range collection and automatic data type selection requires Fixed-Point Designer product license.</entry>
    <entry key="RangeAnalysisBadDesignRange">Potential conflict of design min/max specification detected when deriving min/max values for the model.\n\n <![CDATA[See more examples and tips to diagnose the potential conflict on a model in Fixed-Point Designer documentation. <a href="matlab:helpview([docroot '/toolbox/fixedpoint/fixedpoint.map'], 'RangeAnalysisBadDesignRange')">More help...</a>]]> </entry>
    <entry key="derivedFailNotAtomic">Deriving min/max can only be performed on a model or atomic subsystems or atomic subcharts. Select model in the hierarchy or enable the subsystem parameter "treat as atomic unit".</entry>
    <entry key="InValidBusElementName">Invalid bus element name ''''{0}''''. </entry>
    <entry key="noAutoscaler">No autoscalers are mapped</entry>
    <entry key="objectInvalidAfterEval">Autoscaling proposal failed. Some blocks might be added or deleted in a self-modifying mask. To prevent this error, update the mask initialization callbacks.</entry>
    <entry key="OnlySingleSharedDTListExpected">There should be only one sharedDT list for this block. </entry>
	<entry key="UnRecognizedSigNameInVirBusSource">Signal ''''{0}'''' was not found in virtual bus source. </entry>
    <entry key="UnRecognizedSigNameInSigHier">Signal ''''{0}'''' was not found in signal hierarchy. </entry>
    <entry key="BusObjectHandleNotFoundInMap">Handle for bus Object ''''{0}'''' was not found. </entry>
	<entry key="StructForLeafElementNotAllowed">Invalid bus initial condition : a structure cannot be assigned to a leaf element of a bus.</entry>
	<entry key="DSMNotFound">Target data store memory for ''''{0}'''' not found.</entry>
	<entry key="UnresolvedBusName">Unresolved Bus Name : ''''{0}'''' in ''''{1}''''. Bus object specification using variable expression or mask initialization is not supported. Please use bus object name defined in base workspace or data dictionary.</entry>
    <entry key="UnRecognizedBusEleName"> Unrecognized bus element ''''{0}''''.</entry>
    <entry key="SIMBackwardsCompatibleSyntax">The "simulateSystem" method of the "DataTypeWorkflow.Converter" class does not support signal logging using the backwards compatible syntax of the "sim" command.</entry>
    <entry key="DefaultWorkflowReportName" translate="false" note="TranslateFalseBatch;">results_report.html</entry>
    <entry key="NoRangeTunableParamObj">No design range is specified for this tunable parameter object. The data type proposal is based on the current value of the parameter object.</entry>
    <entry key="ConflictingRangeTunableParamObj">No design range is specified for this tunable parameter object and design ranges specified for block parameters using this parameter object are not consistent. The data type proposal is based on the current value of the parameter object.</entry>
    <entry key="NamedShortcutDoesNotExist">Model {0} does not contain a shortcut named {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="DataTypeWorkflowDefaultRunName">Run 1</entry>
    <entry key="ModelNotLoaded">The model {0} is not loaded. Please load the model before calling this function.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionShouldReturnLogical">The specified filter function returns a value of type ''{0}'', when it should be returning a value of type ''logical''.</entry>
    <entry key="reloadExistingRun">The specified MAT-file, ''''{0}'''', contains runs with the same names as existing runs.
        \n {1} \n
    If you do not want to preserve the existing runs, specify ''''merge'''' or ''''overwrite'''' instead of ''''keepExisting''''.</entry>
    <entry key="runSettingsDoNotExist">There are no settings saved for run ''''{0}'''', so no settings can be applied.</entry>
    <entry key="cellArrayOfStringsExpected" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">The value of ''{0}'' is invalid. Expected a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="noReportBecauseNoRunsExist">Unable to generate report because no runs exist</entry>
    <entry key="noRunsExist">The action cannot be completed because there are no runs in the specified Converter object.</entry>
    <entry key="noShortcuts">No shortcuts exist for the system. Use the Fixed-Point Tool to create shortcuts for the system that can be applied with this method.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidType" translate="false" note="TranslateFalseBatch;">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="unrecognizedStringChoice" translate="false" note="TranslateFalseBatch;">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="shortcutStringMismatch">The input ''{0}'' is not a valid shortcut name. Access the ''ShortcutsForSelectedSystem'' property of the converter object to list available shortcuts.</entry>
    <entry key="noSDIRuns">Unable to compare results. This may be because the system has not yet been simulated, or because no signals in the system are being logged.</entry>
    <entry key="signalIDNotMatch">Unable to compare runs. Both runs must contain the same set of signals with signal logging enabled.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSystemToScale">Invalid system to scale. To continue, verify that the top model with the specified subsystem can be compiled.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTopModel">Invalid top model. To continue, verify that the model can be compiled.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCLIHandle">Invalid handle specified. This may be because the model was closed or the converter object was deleted.</entry>
    <entry key="msgNoProposedFL">There are no proposed fraction lengths or word lengths to apply. Please see individual results for more information, or use the proposalIssues property to find possible causes.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidMATFile">Unable to load from MAT-file, since the file was not created using the DataTypeWorkflow.Converter.saveRuns function.</entry>
    <entry key="defaultTypeSettingNonChar" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Expression for default data type must be a non-empty character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="defaultTypeSettingMessySlopeBias">A non-zero bias or a slope adjustment factor other than one cannot be accepted as a default data type.</entry>
    <entry key="defaultTypeSettingLongWL">Word length greater than 128 is not supported. </entry>
    <entry key="defaultTypeSettingInvalid">The specified data type does not resolve to a valid data type that can be used as the default data type.</entry>
    <entry key="derivedFailSLFunction">Deriving min/max cannot be performed on a Simulink Function. Select model or a higher level subsystem in the hierarchy.</entry>
    <entry key="futureFunctionality">This method is not available.</entry>
    <entry key="runNameNotFound">The run ''''{0}'''' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="modelNameMismatch">The Converter's model name does not match the one to be imported, ''''{0}''''.</entry>
    <entry key="badInputArgument">The data to be imported is bad.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSpecificConstraintType" translate="false">Invalid specific type. Specific type has to be of type SimulinkFixedPoint.AutoscalerConstraints.SpecificConstraintTypes</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSpecificWL" translate="false">Invalid word length for specific type constraint. Word length should be real, finite and less than 128. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidSpecificFL" translate="false">Invalid fraction length for specific type constraint. Fraction length should be real and finite. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidSpecificSigned" translate="false">Invalid signedness for specific type constraint. Signedness should be signed or unsigned. </entry>
    <entry key="limitedBoolOnly">only Boolean</entry>
    <entry key="limitedMLFBExprOnly">Data types cannot be proposed for expressions in MATLAB function blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="limitedFloatingPointOnly">only double</entry>
    <entry key="signedOnly">only signed types</entry>
    <entry key="unsignedOnly">only unsigned types</entry>
    <entry key="sinwaveConstraint">Fixed-point and user-defined data types are only supported when the 'Sample mode' parameter is set to 'Discrete' and the 'Computation method' parameter is set to 'Table lookup'.</entry>
    <entry key="mlfbCompatibilityError">Errors were detected in this variable or the MATLAB function this variable belongs to.</entry>
    <entry key="mlfbCompatibilityWarning">Warnings were detected in this variable or the MATLAB function this variable belongs to.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRanges" translate="false">Invalid range. The lower bound of a range cannot be larger than the upper bound.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRangeType" translate="false">Invalid range type.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataTypeSpecification" translate="false">Invalid data type specification.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDerivedRangeState" translate="false">Invalid derived range state.</entry>
    <entry key="unregisteredResult" translate="false">Unregistered result found.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidMemberDeletion" translate="false">Group member deletion failed. Result does not belong to the group.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidObjectForNamedTypeHandle" translate="false">NamedTypeHandle does not exist for the provided object.</entry>
    <entry key="sudNotUnderTop">The top model ({0}) does not reference the system under design ({1}).</entry>
    <entry key="insufficientAttributesForWrapperBuilder" translate="false">All {0} attributes of object must be set.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTableForDecoupledSubsystemDisplay" translate="false">The object tableData must be a table with compatible format.</entry>
    <entry key="issueWhenConstructingInterfacePortPairs" translate="false">Port handle pair creation triggered an error.</entry>
    <entry key="signalHierarchyIssue" translate="false">Signal hierarchy for port handle {0} could not be read. Try compiling the model.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidProgressTrackingValue">SimulationScenarios cannot be empty to set this property.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFunctionName">Input function name must be a non-empty string or char.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  autoscaled subcharts autoscalers sincos jcos Autoscaler jsin
     LocalWords:  pixelcontrol pixelcontrolbus
-->
