<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--Copyright 2016-2020 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="SimulinkFixedPoint" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="DTUnknown">An output data type cannot be specified on this result. The output type is the same as the input type.</entry>
        <entry key="DTFloatingPoint">The data type of this result is floating point.</entry>
        <entry key="DTInherited">The data type of this result is inherited or derived. The Fixed-Point Tool cannot remove data type inheritance from all results. To get a proposal for this result, refer to the "Get Proposals for Results With Inherited Types" topic in the Fixed-Point Designer documentation.   </entry>
        <entry key="DTAliasType">The data type of this result resolves to a Simulink.AliasType object.</entry>
        <entry key="DTEnum">The data type of this result is an enumerated data type.</entry>
        <entry key="DTBoolean">The data type of this result is boolean.  The Fixed-Point Tool does not generate a proposal for results that are boolean because boolean types can be represented efficiently in an embedded design.</entry>
        <entry key="DTBus">The data type of this result is specified using a bus object. The bus leaf elements were autoscaled separately.</entry>
        <entry key="NamedDTResolution">The specified data type of this result resolves to {0} ({1}).</entry>
        <entry key="NamedDTParent">To change the data type of this result, edit the data type of ''''{0}''''.</entry>
        <entry key="AbstractSimulinkObjectResultClassAndWorkspace">This is a {0} object defined in the {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="AbstractSimulinkObjectResultUsedIn">This data object is used in {0}.</entry>
		<entry key="ResultLocked">The Fixed-Point Tool does not generate a proposal for results whose output data type is locked against changes by the fixed-point tools.</entry>
		<entry key="DTCStoredInteger">The Fixed-Point Tool cannot propose a valid data type because the block parameter 'ConvertRealWorld' is set to 'Stored Integer (SI)'.</entry>
		<entry key="DTFROMSIMULINKSIGNALOBJECT">The data type of this result is inherited from the Simulink.Signal object.</entry>
        <entry key="NamedDTHierarchy">The data type of this result is {0}. The type belongs in the following hierarchy: {1}.</entry>
		<entry key="NamedDTControl">The data type of this result is controlled by ''{0}''.</entry>
		<entry key="SeeDataObjectsPane"> To view the result for ''{0}'', select ''Data Objects'' in the ''Model Hierarchy'' pane.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords: autoscaled autoscaling -->
