<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="instrument">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidSerialPort">The serial port selected in the block ''{0}'' is invalid. Please select a valid port.</entry>
    <entry key="multipleSCBlocks">The model contains more than one ''Serial Configuration'' block configured to the same serial port {0}. You must have only one ''Serial Configuration'' block for {1} in a model.</entry>
    <entry key="invaliddatatype">The data type at the input port is not supported by the block {0}. The valid data types are ''single'', ''double'', ''int8'', ''uint8'', ''int16'', ''uint16'', ''int32'' and ''uint32''.\n</entry>
    <entry key="invalidinheritedsampletime">The block ''{0}'' cannot be assigned a continuous sample time.\n</entry>
    <entry key="hostinvalid">The remote address could not be detected. Specify a different remote address.\n</entry>
    <entry key="localhostinvalid">The local address could not be detected. Specify a different local address.\n</entry>
    <entry key="portinvalid">The block {0} could not connect to the specified port. Please specify a different port or wait for the current port to become available.\n</entry>
    <entry key="noSCBlocks">The model contains no serial configuration block for the port {0}. Please use the ''Serial Configuration'' block from the Instrument Control Toolbox block library to configure {1}</entry>
    <entry key="multipleSSBlocks">The model contains more than one ''Serial Send'' block configured to the same serial port {0}. You must have only one ''Serial Send'' block for {1} in a model.</entry>
    <entry key="ddgApply">Return arguments have switched order.</entry>
    <entry key="argcheck">INSTRUMENTSLGATE is a gateway routine to the Instrument Control Toolbox Simulink\nprivate functions and should not be directly called by users.</entry>
    <entry key="bufferError">The data size specified in the block {0} is greater than the largest buffer size that can be set.</entry>
    <entry key="timeouterror">The specified amount of data was not returned within the Timeout period.\nPlease ensure that data is being sent to the specified port or specify a greater timeout value.\n</entry>
    <entry key="multipleSRBlocks">The model contains more than one ''Serial Receive'' block configured to the same serial port {0}. You must have only one ''Serial Receive'' block for {1} in a model.</entry>
    <entry key="outputSizeMismatch">The dimensions of field ''Custom value'' and ''Data size'' do not match.</entry>
    <entry key="unappliedChanges">Block has unapplied changes.  Please apply or cancel these changes before running the simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownCallback">{0} is not a recognized icbgate command.</entry>
    <entry key="multipleBlocksSamePortError">Multiple {0} blocks cannot connect to the same remote address and port.\n</entry>
    <entry key="conflictingbyteordererror">The blocks ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' have different byte order settings. You must have same byte order setting for both these blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidRemoteHost">''Remote host'' parameter must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="remotePortNonScalar">''Remote port'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="remotePortNegative">''Remote port'' parameter must be positive.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidManufacturerID">''Manufacturer ID'' parameter must be either a positive numeric scalar or a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidModelCode">''Model code'' parameter must be either a positive numeric scalar or a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSerialNumber">''Serial number'' parameter must be either a positive numeric scalar or a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="sampleTimeNonScalar">Sample time must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="sampleTimeNegative">Sample time must be positive.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSampleTime">Sample time must be non-negative or -1.</entry>
    <entry key="timeoutNonScalar">Timeout parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="timeoutNegative">Timeout parameter must be positive.</entry>
    <entry key="inputBufferSizeNonScalar">''Input buffer size'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="inputBufferSizeLessThanMin">''Input buffer size'' parameter must be greater than 1.</entry>
    <entry key="baudRateNonScalar">Baud rate parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="baudRateNegative">Baud rate parameter must be greater than zero.</entry>
    <entry key="boardIndexNonScalar">''Board index'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="boardIndexNegative">''Board index'' parameter must be positive.</entry>    
    <entry key="primaryAddressNonScalar">''Primary address'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="primaryAddressNegative">''Primary address'' parameter must be positive.</entry>    
    <entry key="secondaryAddressNonScalar">''Secondary address'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="secondaryAddressNegative">''Secondary address'' parameter must be positive.</entry>
    <entry key="portNonScalar">''Port'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="portNegative">''Port'' parameter must be positive.</entry>    
    <entry key="chassisIndexNonScalar">''Chassis index'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="chassisIndexNegative">''Chassis index'' parameter must be positive.</entry>        
    <entry key="logicalAddressNonScalar">''Logical address'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="logicalAddressNegative">''Logical address'' parameter must be positive.</entry>        
    <entry key="emptyWSObject">''Workspace object'' parameter is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidWSObject">''Workspace object'' parameter does not exist in the MATLAB workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="binaryValuesNonScalar">''Binary values to read'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="binaryValuesNegative">''Binary values to read'' parameter must be positive.</entry>    
    <entry key="frameSizeNonScalar">''Frame size'' parameter must be a numeric scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="frameSizeNegative">''Frame size'' parameter must be positive.</entry>    
    <entry key="invalidInitCommand">Initialization command must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidQueryCommand">Query command must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCommand">''Command'' must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidASCIIFormat">ASCII format must be a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="queryDataUnknown">Error locating QueryInstrument block data.</entry>
    <entry key="sendDataUnknown">Error locating SendInstrument block data.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNumElements">Size of the specified workspace variable could not be obtained.</entry>
    <entry key="wsObjNonScalar">''Workspace object'' parameter  must be a scalar instrument interface object.</entry>
    <entry key="wsVarInvalid">Instrument interface object specified as workspace object parameter is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="wsObjNotIntObj">Instrument interface object specified as workspace object parameter is not supported by the block.</entry>
    <entry key="createFailed">An error occurred during the creation of the required object.</entry>
    <entry key="openFailed">An error occurred while opening the required object.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedVISA">Unsupported VISA vendor specified.</entry>
    <entry key="objNotUnique">Found multiple instrument objects with the same block specific name.</entry>
    <entry key="initFailed">An error occurred during the instrument initialization action.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInstrumentObj">The instrument interface is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedGPIB">Unsupported GPIB vendor specified.</entry>
    <entry key="responseEmpty">Response from instrument was empty.</entry>
    <entry key="responseNonNumeric">Response from instrument was non-numeric.</entry>
    <entry key="acquisitionFailed">Could not acquire samples from the instrument.</entry>
    <entry key="errorMexCallMATLAB">Error using Toolbox.  View the MATLAB command line for details.</entry>
    <entry key="outputDatagramPacketSize">The UDP packet size entry must be a valid integer between 1 and 65535.</entry>
    <entry key="udpInvalidLocalPort">The local port entry must be a valid integer between 1 and 65535.</entry>
    <entry key="udpInvalidRemotePort">The remote port entry must be a valid integer between 1 and 65535.</entry>
    <entry key="conflictPortSharingSettings">Unable to set "Enable local port sharing" parameter for this block. UDP blocks with the same local address and local port must have the same "Enable local port sharing" setting. Please check the 'Enable local port sharing' setting of your UDP blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="localHostDoesNotResolve">The local address could not be detected. Specify a different local address.</entry>
    <entry key="localHostResolves">The local address ''{0}'' has been found.</entry>
    <entry key="localHostResolvesWithIP">The local address ''{0}'' ({1}) has been found.</entry>
    <entry key="localHostAndPortCorrect">The local address ''{0}'' and port number {1} are valid and available.</entry>
    <entry key="localHostAndPortCorrectWithIP">The local address ''{0}'' ({1}) and port number {2} are valid and available.</entry>
    <entry key="remoteHostAndPortCorrect">The remote address ''{0}'' and port number {1} are valid and available.</entry>
    <entry key="remoteHostAndPortCorrectWithIP">The remote address ''{0}'' ({1}) and port number {2} are valid and available.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidASCIIFormatString">The ASCII format string entry must be a valid numeric conversion specifier in the form of a character vector or string.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTerminator">Terminator must be an integer between 0 and 127 (ASCII decimal value), 'CR/LF' or 'LF/CR'.</entry>
    <entry key="outputlatestdataunavailable">Outputting the latest data is not supported with the data type ASCII. Change to a data type that supports the output.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectASCIIRead">Data was read incorrectly. Check the Data size option and the ASCII format string option.</entry>
    <entry key="localPortAutoAssignment">(-1 for automatic local port assignment)</entry>
    <entry key="noteUDPReceiveBlk">Note: Remote address and Remote port only need to be modified for specific workflows.</entry>
    <entry key="noteUDPSendBlk"> Note: Local address and Local port only need to be modified for specific workflows.</entry>
    <entry key="noteClkHelpText">         Click Help for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidStopbitsDatabits1">Stop bits value should be 1 or 2 for the selected Data bits.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidStopbitsDatabits2">Stop bits value should be 1 or 1.5 for the selected Data bits.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidReceiveSampleTime">Block sample time must be either specified as a positive number or -1 to inherit sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="noPortsSelected">No ports selected. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataType">The selected data type is not supported. </entry>
    <entry key="errorConfiguringPort">Cannot configure the selected serial port as the port selected was configured by another Serial object. </entry>
    <entry key="portNotConfigured"> The selected port is not configured. Use Serial Configuration block to configure the port. </entry>
    <entry key="emptyDatasize"> Data size field should not be empty. </entry>
    <entry key="emptyCustomValue"> Custom value field should not be empty. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidCustomValue"> Custom value must be specified as a real numeric value. Custom value must be either a scalar value or equal to size of data specified in the 'Data size' field. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidCustomValueType"> Custom value cannot be represented in output data's type. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidParity"> Parity value as ''{0}'' is not supported in this version of MATLAB. Parity must be set to 'none', 'even' or 'odd'.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidASCIIFormatStringForCodegen">Block support only one ASCII format string entry while simulating model in codegen mode.</entry>
    <entry key="incorrectSscanfOutput">Data cannot be outputted correctly. Check the ASCII format string value.</entry>
    <entry key="nonscalarTerminator"> TCP/IP Receive block in exported version support only scalar Terminator values. Update the Terminator value before simulating the exported model.</entry>
    <entry key="warnfor64bitDatatype"> 'Source Data type' value of ''{0}'' in block ''{1}'' is not supported in exported version. Changing 'Source Data type' to default value of 'uint8'</entry>
    <entry key="blockParam">Block Parameters: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="invalidWidgetTag">Invalid widget tag</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBlock">Invalid block</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBlockRef">Invalid block reference</entry>
    <entry key="errorString">Error</entry>
    <entry key="successString">Success</entry>
    <entry key="tcpipReceive">TCP/IP Client Receive</entry>
    <entry key="tcpipSend">TCP/IP Client Send</entry>
    <entry key="noPortSelected">No ports\n selected</entry>
    <entry key="nonPositiveTimeout">Timeout must be specified as a positive number.</entry>
    <entry key="portNumericRange">The port entry must be a valid integer between 1 and 65535.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataSize">The data size must be a valid scalar or row vector containing positive integers.</entry>
    <entry key="portUnavailable">\nHowever, we are unable to connect to the server at the specified port.\n\nSpecify a different port or wait for the current port to become available.</entry>
    <entry key="configError">Configuration Error</entry>
    <entry key="serialportUnavailable">No serial ports are available.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidBaudRate">Baud rate must be specified as a valid positive integer.</entry>
    <entry key="remoteAddressFound">The remote address ''{0}''{1} has been found.</entry>
    <entry key="specifiedSerialportUnavailable">Serial port ''{0}'' is unavailable.\nPlease select another serial port.</entry>
    <entry key="inquirySerialConfigurationBlock">You have successfully set the parameters for the 'Serial {0}' block. This block requires a 'Serial Configuration' block to configure the serial port properties.\n\nWould you like to add a 'Serial Configuration' block for ''{1}'' from the Instrument Control Toolbox block library at this time?</entry>
    <entry key="mismatchedSingleQuotes">The entry for {0} field consists of mismatched single quotes.\nIf single quote is required as a part of the {1}, two single quotes must be used.</entry>
    <entry key="selectPort">&lt;Please select a port...&gt;</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidReadTerminator"> Read terminator value must be "LF", "CR", "CR/LF", or an integer from 0 to 255, inclusive. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidWriteTerminator"> Write terminator value must be "LF", "CR", "CR/LF", or an integer from 0 to 255, inclusive. </entry>
    <entry key="invalidHeader"> Unable to find specified header in instrument response. </entry>
    <entry key="instrumentReadError"> Error returned during read operation indicating: \n ''{0}''  </entry>
    <entry key="sendCommandFailedWithInstrError"> Failed to send command to instrument. Error returned during send operation indicating: \n ''{0}'' \n Instrument returned error indicating: \n ''{1}'' </entry>
    <entry key="sendCommandFailed"> Failed to send command to instrument. Error returned during send operation indicating: \n ''{0}'' </entry>
    <entry key="readAndInstrumentError"> Error during read operation cause instrument to go into an error state. Error returned during read operation indicating: \n ''{0}'. Instrument returned error indicating: \n ''{1}''  </entry>
    <entry key="warnBlockDeprecation"> ''{0}'' ''{1}'' will be removed in a future release. Use one of the interface-specific Instrument Control Toolbox blocks instead. </entry>
    <entry key="noResourceSelected"> No resource selected. </entry>
</message>
</rsccat>
