<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="instrument">
    <message>
        <!-- Instrument Transport Classes -->
        <entry key="BluetoothWarning">Bluetooth will be removed in a future release. Use bluetooth (case-sensitive) instead.</entry>
        <entry key="BluetoothError">Bluetooth has been removed. Use bluetooth (case-sensitive) instead.</entry>

        <entry key="gpibWarning">gpib will be removed in a future release. Use visadev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="gpibError">gpib has been removed. Use visadev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="serialWarning">serial will be removed in a future release. Use serialport instead.</entry>
        <entry key="serialError">serial has been removed. Use serialport instead.</entry>

        <entry key="tcpipWarning">tcpip with the NetworkRole property set to "client" will be removed in a future release. Use tcpclient instead.\n
            tcpip with the NetworkRole property set to "server" will be removed in a future release. Use tcpserver instead.</entry>
        <entry key="tcpipError">tcpip with the NetworkRole property set to "client" has been removed. Use tcpclient instead.\n
            tcpip with the NetworkRole property set to "server" has been removed. Use tcpserver instead.</entry>

        <entry key="udpWarning">udp will be removed in a future release. Use udpport instead.</entry>
        <entry key="udpError">udp has been removed. Use udpport instead.</entry>

        <entry key="visaWarning">visa will be removed in a future release. Use visadev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="visaError">visa has been removed. Use visadev instead.</entry>
		
        <entry key="i2cWarning">i2c will be removed in a future release. Use the device function with an ni845x or aardvark object instead.</entry>
        <entry key="i2cError">i2c has been removed. Use the device function with an ni845x or aardvark object instead.</entry>

        <!-- icdevice exception -->
        <entry key="icdeviceNotSupported">\nNote: To use {0} with icdevice, create an icdevice object with name-value argument LegacyMode=false.</entry>

        <!-- Discovery Functions- instrhwinfo and seriallist -->
        <entry key="instrhwinfobluetoothWarning">instrhwinfo('Bluetooth') will be removed in a future release. Use bluetoothlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfobluetoothError">instrhwinfo('Bluetooth') has been removed. Use bluetoothlist instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfogpibWarning">instrhwinfo('gpib') will be removed in a future release. Use visadevlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfogpibError">instrhwinfo('gpib') has been removed. Use visadevlist instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfoserialWarning">instrhwinfo('serial') will be removed in a future release. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfoserialError">instrhwinfo('serial') has been removed. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfoserialportWarning">instrhwinfo('serialport') will be removed in a future release. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfoserialportError">instrhwinfo('serialport') has been removed. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfotcpipWarning">instrhwinfo('tcpip') will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfotcpipError">instrhwinfo('tcpip') has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfoudpWarning">instrhwinfo('udp') will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfoudpError">instrhwinfo('udp') has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhwinfovisaWarning">instrhwinfo('visa') will be removed in a future release. Use visadevlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfovisaError">instrhwinfo('visa') has been removed. Use visadevlist instead.</entry>
		
        <entry key="instrhwinfoi2cWarning">instrhwinfo('i2c') will be removed in a future release. Use ni845xlist or aardvarklist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhwinfoi2cError">instrhwinfo('i2c') has been removed. Use ni845xlist or aardvarklist instead.</entry>

        <entry key="seriallistWarning">seriallist will be removed in a future release. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>
        <entry key="seriallistError">seriallist has been removed. Use serialportlist instead.</entry>

        <!-- Legacy ICT Helper Functions -->
        <entry key="instrfindWarning">instrfind will be removed in a future release. For objects of type\n - serialport use serialportfind\n - tcpclient use tcpclientfind\n - tcpserver use tcpserverfind\n - udpport use udpportfind\n - visadev use visadevfind\n - aardvark use aardvarkfind\n - ni845x use ni845xfind\n - icdevice with LegacyMode=false use icdevicefind</entry>
        <entry key="instrfindError">instrfind has been removed. For serialport, tcpclient, tcpserver, udpport, visadev, aardvark, and ni845x objects, use serialportfind, tcpclientfind, tcpserverfind, udpportfind, visadevfind, aardvarkfind, and ni845xfind instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrfindallWarning">instrfindall will be removed in a future release. For objects of type\n - serialport use serialportfind\n - tcpclient use tcpclientfind\n - tcpserver use tcpserverfind\n - udpport use udpportfind\n - visadev use visadevfind\n - aardvark use aardvarkfind\n - ni845x use ni845xfind\n - icdevice with LegacyMode=false use icdevicefind</entry>
        <entry key="instrfindallError">instrfindall has been removed. For serialport, tcpclient, tcpserver, udpport, visadev, aardvark, and ni845x objects, use serialportfind, tcpclientfind, tcpserverfind, udpportfind, visadevfind, aardvarkfind, and ni845xfind instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrresetWarning">instrreset will be removed in a future release. For objects of type\n - serialport use delete(serialportfind)\n - tcpclient use delete(tcpclientfind)\n - tcpserver use delete(tcpserverfind)\n - udpport use delete(udpportfind)\n - visadev use delete(visadevfind)\n - aardvark use delete(aardvarkfind)\n - ni845x use delete(ni845xfind)\n - icdevice with LegacyMode=false use delete(icdevicefind)</entry>
        <entry key="instrresetError">instrreset has been removed. For serialport, tcpclient, tcpserver, udpport, visadev, aardvark, and ni845x objects, use delete(serialportfind), delete(tcpclientfind), delete(tcpserverfind), delete(udpportfind), delete(visadevfind), delete(aardvarkfind), and delete(ni845xfind) instead.</entry>

        <entry key="instrcallbackWarning">instrcallback will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="instrcallbackError">instrcallback has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="instrnotifyWarning">instrnotify will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="instrnotifyError">instrnotify has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="instrhelpWarning">instrhelp will be removed in a future release. For serialport, tcpclient, tcpserver, udpport, visadev, bluetooth, aardvark/device, and ni845x/device objects, use help instead.</entry>
        <entry key="instrhelpError">instrhelp has been removed. For serialport, tcpclient, tcpserver, udpport, visadev, bluetooth, aardvark/device, and ni845x/device objects, use help instead.</entry>

        <!-- DRIVER API -->
        <entry key="makemidWarning">makemid will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="makemidError">makemid has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="midtestWarning">midtest will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="midtestError">midtest has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <entry key="mideditWarning">midedit will be removed in a future release. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>
        <entry key="mideditError">midedit has been removed. There is no simple replacement for this.</entry>

        <!-- Class Compliant IVI-C Drivers -->
        <entry key="IviDCPwrWarning">instrument.ivic.IviDCPwr will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviDCPwrError">instrument.ivic.IviDCPwr has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviDmmWarning">instrument.ivic.IviDmm will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviDmmError">instrument.ivic.IviDmm has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviFgenWarning">instrument.ivic.IviFgen will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviFgenError">instrument.ivic.IviFgen has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviSwtchWarning">instrument.ivic.IviSwtch will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviSwtchError">instrument.ivic.IviSwtch has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviSpecAnWarning">instrument.ivic.IviSpecAn will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviSpecAnError">instrument.ivic.IviSpecAn has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviScopeWarning">instrument.ivic.IviScope will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviScopeError">instrument.ivic.IviScope has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviRFSigGenWarning">instrument.ivic.IviRFSigGen will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviRFSigGenError">instrument.ivic.IviRFSigGen has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <entry key="IviPwrMeterWarning">instrument.ivic.IviPwrMeter will be removed in a future release. Use ividev instead.</entry>
        <entry key="IviPwrMeterError">instrument.ivic.IviPwrMeter has been removed. Use ividev instead.</entry>

        <!-- Apps -->
        <entry key="tmtoolWarning">The Test and Measurement Tool app (tmtool) will be removed in a future release. Use the TCP/IP Explorer (tcpipExplorer), UDP Explorer (udpExplorer), Serial Explorer (serialExplorer), VISA Explorer (visaExplorer), or Instrument Explorer (instrumentExplorer) app instead.</entry>
        <entry key="tmtoolError">The Test and Measurement Tool app (tmtool) has been removed. Use the TCP/IP Explorer (tcpipExplorer), UDP Explorer (udpExplorer), Serial Explorer (serialExplorer), VISA Explorer (visaExplorer), or Instrument Explorer (instrumentExplorer) app instead.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>