<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <entry key="allNonstandardExtensions">Input folders or files contain non-standard file extensions.\n\nUse FileExtensions Name-Value pair to include the non-standard file extensions.</entry>
        <entry key="ambiguousAlternateFileSystemRoots">Root paths ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' specified in ''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' are non-unique or are subfolders of each other.</entry>
        <entry key="fileExtensionsNotPresent">Input folders or files do not contain specified file extensions: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="invalidAlternateFileSystemRoots">''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' must either be an empty cell or specify multiple root paths in a string vector or a cell array of character vectors.\n Each root path must contain at least 2 characters.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidMaxFailures">MaxFailures must be a positive numeric scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="maxErrorsExceeded">Number of read failures exceeded MaxFailures. To get the list of all the files with read failures, use the ReadFailures property.</entry>
        <entry key="noAlternateFileSystemRootsExist">Root paths ''{0}'' do not exist.\n''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' must either be an empty cell or contain at least one root path that exists.</entry>
        <entry key="noEntryMatchesFiles">Root paths ''{0}'' specified in ''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' must have at least one entry that points to the location of files. For more information, see documentation for ''AlternateFileSystemRoots''.</entry>
        <entry key="nonFilePaths">''{0}'' does not appear to be a file.\nFiles property assignment cannot accept folder names or wildcard (*) operations.\n\nSpecify full file and path names instead.</entry>
        <entry key="partialPathNonexistent">Invalid cloud path entries in AlternateFileSystemRoots: ''{0}''.\nTo specify cloud paths correctly, see the "Read Remote Data" topic in the &lt;a href="matlab:doc(''datastore'')"&gt;datastore&lt;/a&gt; documentation.</entry>
        <entry key="relativePathsUnsupported">Invalid ''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' entries: ''{0}''.\n''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' must not contain file names or relative paths.</entry>
        <entry key="setReadFailureRule">To skip files that cannot be read, set the value of ReadFailureRule to 'skipfile'.\nFor more information, see Handling Read Failures in Datastores.</entry>
        <entry key="warnFirstFailure">Unable to read ''{0}''.\nRead failures found in one or more files. To look up all the files that have read failures, use the ReadFailures property.\nFurther read failures will not display a warning message. For more information, see Handling Read Failures in Datastores.</entry>
        <entry key="warnReadall">Unable to read one or more files from the datastore. To look up all the files that have read failures, use the ReadFailures property.\nIf you update the files with read failures, you must reset the datastore.\nFor more information, see Handling Read Failures in Datastores.</entry>
        <entry key="warnReadFailures">Unable to read one or more files from the datastore. To look up all the files that have read failures, use the ReadFailures property.\nIf you update the files with read failures, you must reset the datastore.\nFor more information, see Handling Read Failures in Datastores.</entry>
        <entry key="nonEmptyAlternateFileSystemRoots">When input location or ''Files'' is empty, ''AlternateFileSystemRoots'' must be set to an empty cell.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
