<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 1994-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Coder" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="fileOpenError">Unable to open file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="tflControlMissing">Expected a TflControl argument.</entry>
    <entry key="compilationErrorStatus">{0} compiler produced errors.</entry>
    <entry key="compilationFailed">Compilation failed: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="compilationSuppressed">Compilation suppressed: generating code only.</entry>
    <entry key="targetCompilerWarnings">{0} Compiler produced warnings. See the build log for further details.</entry>
    <entry key="unrecognizedTarget">Unrecognized compilation target.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedExternalDependency">The library ''{0}'' is not supported by the current target, language or compiler.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidExternalDependency">The library method ''{0}'' failed.</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedCompiler">Unsupported compiler.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownCompiler">Unknown compiler ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="unknownMexCompiler">Unable to determine MEX compiler: use {0} to configure your system.</entry>
    <entry key="MEXLCCDeprecationError">Unable to determine MEX compiler: use &lt;a href="matlab: mex -setup"&gt;mex -setup&lt;/a&gt; to configure your system. Note that the LCC compiler is deprecated and no longer available. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="ToolchainLCCDeprecationError">You selected the LCC toolchain which has been deprecated and is no longer available. To generate and build code, select an alternative toolchain. To generate source code only, enable the Generate Code Only ('GenCodeOnly') configuration setting and set the Toolchain setting to 'Automatically locate an installed toolchain'. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="NoToolchainInstalledLCCDeprecationError">Your system does not have an installed toolchain. To generate source code only and skip the compilation, enable the Generate Code Only ('GenCodeOnly') configuration setting. Note that the LCC compiler has been deprecated and is no longer available. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="NoToolchainInstalled">Your system does not have an installed toolchain. To generate source code only and skip the compilation, enable the Generate Code Only ('GenCodeOnly') configuration setting. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="SelectedToolchainNotInstalled">The selected toolchain ''{0}'' is not installed. To generate source code only and skip the compilation, enable the Generate Code Only ('GenCodeOnly') configuration setting.</entry>
    <entry key="mexFileLocked">The MEX-file is locked and must be unlocked before recompiling.</entry>
    <entry key="mexStillInMemory">The MEX file ''{0}'' is still loaded in memory. To clear the MEX file from memory, close the MATLAB session.</entry>
    <entry key="fileNotFound">{0} specified in {1} does not exist in any of the following search directories: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="missingBuildInfoOrTflControl">Project, BuildInfo and TflControl arguments required.</entry>
    <entry key="expectedProjectArgument">Expected a Project argument.</entry>
    <entry key="expectedBuildInfoArgument">Expected a BuildInfo argument.</entry>
    <entry key="expectedTflControlArgument">Expected a TflControl argument.</entry>
    <entry key="nothingToBuild">Nothing to build.</entry>
    <entry key="directoryNotSpecified">Build directory not specified.</entry>
    <entry key="tmfUnspecified">No TMF specified.</entry>
    <entry key="tmfUnavailable">Specified TMF ''{0}'' cannot be accessed.</entry>
    <entry key="RtwsfcnTMFNeedsMexCompiler"><![CDATA[Cannot create S-Function Target without a mex compiler. The template makefile, ''{0}'', must specify a TOOLCHAIN_NAME that corresponds to an available mex compiler. For an example, see the <a href="matlab:edit(fullfile(tmffolder, grt_default_tmf))">default template makefile for GRT targets</a>. 
                                            For more information, see <a href="matlab:helpview('rtw','associate_tmf_with_toolchain')">Associate the Template Makefile with a Toolchain</a>.]]></entry>
    <entry key="RtwsfcnNeedsMexToolchain">Cannot create S-Function Target without a mex compiler. The specified toolchain, ''{0}'', does not support the building mex functions. </entry>
    <entry key="tmfSyntaxErrorMissingToken">TMF SYNTAX ERROR: missing {0} token for make-rule expansion.</entry>
    <entry key="tmfSyntaxErrorDuplicateToken">TMF SYNTAX ERROR: found {0} before related {1} token.</entry>
    <entry key="cancelledByUser">Build cancelled.</entry>
    <entry key="specifiedProjectFileNotFound">Project file ''{0}'' not found.</entry>
    <entry key="specifiedProjectFileExists">Project file ''{0}'' already exists.</entry>
    <entry key="badBrojectFileExtension">Project file extension ''{1}'' is not supported. Use ''{0}'' instead.</entry>
    <entry key="incompleteProjectCreationArgs">Incomplete arguments specified. Expecting: ''coder -target -new project_name''</entry>
    <entry key="invalidGpuProjectCreationArgs">Argument ''{0}'' not supported with ''gpucoder -new'' or ''coder -gpu -new''.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecateInlineThreshold">The ''InlineThreshold'' option will be removed in a future release. Use ''InlineBetweenUserFunctions'', ''InlineBetweenMathWorksFunctions'', and ''InlineBetweenUserAndMathWorksFunctions'' options instead.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecateInlineThresholdMax">The ''InlineThresholdMax'' option will be removed in a future release. Use ''InlineBetweenUserFunctions'', ''InlineBetweenMathWorksFunctions'', and ''InlineBetweenUserAndMathWorksFunctions'' options instead.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecateInlineStackLimit">The ''InlineStackLimit'' option will be removed in a future release. Use ''InlineBetweenUserFunctions'', ''InlineBetweenMathWorksFunctions'', and ''InlineBetweenUserAndMathWorksFunctions'' options instead.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecateDynamicMemoryAllocation">The ''DynamicMemoryAllocation'' config option is deprecated. Use ''EnableDynamicMemoryAllocation'' and ''DynamicMemoryAllocationThreshold'' options instead. Alternatively, in the MATLAB Coder app select "Enable dynamic memory allocation" and set a value for "Dynamic memory allocation threshold".</entry>
    <entry key="TerminateFunctionNecessaryRequiredOff">A terminate function is
    necessary, however the code generation process did not generate a terminate
    function because the 'Terminate function required' check box is
    cleared.</entry>

    <entry key="TerminateFunctionNecessaryExportFcnModel">A terminate function
    is necessary, however the code generation process did not generate a
    terminate function because the model is set up to export function-call
    subsystems.</entry>
    <entry key="PWSUnsupportedUnsizedArgInhouse">Data type of argument {0,number,integer} of function ''{1}'' generated from ''{2}'' maps to type with different word length on host computer. Portable word sizes is not supported for ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="PWSUnsupportedUnsizedRetArgInhouse">Data type of return argument of function ''{0}'' generated from ''{1}'' maps to type with different word length on host computer. Portable word sizes is not supported for ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="PWSUnsupportedUnsizedArgInhouseTlc">Argument(s) {0} of function ''{1}'' use data type(s) that map to different wordlength(s) on the host. Portable word sizes is not supported for this function in TLC.</entry>
    <entry key="PWSWarnAboutUnsizedArgs">Argument(s) {0} of function ''{1}'' generated from ''{2}'' use data types that map to different wordlengths on the host. Your custom implementation function argument data types should match wordlengths on the production hardware to avoid/ minimize possible numerical differences or runtime errors.</entry>
    <entry key="PWSWarnAboutUnsizedReturnArg">The return argument for implementation function ''{0}'' generated from ''{1}'' uses a data type that maps to a different wordlength on the host. Your custom implementation function''s return type should match wordlengths on the production hardware to avoid/ minimize possible numerical differences or runtime errors.</entry>
    <entry key="OpenSupportFileError">Unable to open support file ''{0}'' because of ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="CopyfileError">Unable to copy file from ''{0}'' to ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="C99IncompatibleCompiler">Selected C compiler is incompatible with C99 (ISO) language standard. Code generation will switch to C89/90 (ANSI) instead. Consider changing C compiler or target language setting to suppress this warning.</entry>
    <entry key="C99IncompatibleTFL">Selected code replacement library is incompatible with C99 (ISO) language standard. Code generation will switch to C89/90 (ANSI) instead. Consider changing the target language setting to suppress this warning.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSourceExtension">{0} does not have a valid extension, build may fail.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedMultiSourceFile">Using whitespace or pathsep to delimit files for CustomSource, CustomInclude, and CustomLibrary is deprecated. To delimit files, make each file name a separate element of a cell array or array of strings. If specifying a single file with a space in the path, use a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedQuote">CustomSource, CustomInclude, or CustomLibrary configuration property contains quote characters for grouping file names. In a future release, these quotes will be included literally in the file name and not removed. Instead of quotes, specify multiple file names using a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedArgPathsep">Using pathsep to delimit multiple paths with "-I" will be deprecated in a future release. Instead, pass the "-I" flag multiple times, each with a single file.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedReplacementTypesHeadersSemicolon">Using semicolon to delimit multiple header files to specify the ReplacementTypes.HeaderFiles property will be deprecated in a future release. Instead, use a string array or cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="CustomPropWrongType">CustomInclude, CustomLibrary, or CustomSource do not have the correct type. Property should be a cellstr or an empty character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="GenCodeOnlyRequired">Selected toolchain ''{0}'' requires MATLAB Coder to be configured to generate code only. Configuration setting ''GenCodeOnly'' is now enabled.</entry>
    <entry key="ToolchainLCCDeprecationWarning">Build process is using LCC compiler, which is deprecated and will be removed in a future release. Consider selecting a different compiler toolchain. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="MEXLCCDeprecationWarning">MEX or SIL/PIL build is using LCC compiler, which is deprecated and will be removed in a future release. Consider configuring a MEX compiler via 'mex -setup'. For information about supported compilers, see &lt;a href="https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers"&gt;https://www.mathworks.com/support/compilers&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
