<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="fixed" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
      <entry key="angleOutOfDomainOfConvergence">In {0}, input angle {1} is out of the domain of convergence.  Input must be in the range [{2}, {3}] for maximum shift value {4} and quantized to {5}.</entry>
      <entry key="cart2pol_YXDataTypesMustMatch">The Y and X arguments must be of the same data type.</entry>
      <entry key="cart2pol_YXMustBeReal">The Y and X arguments must be real-valued.</entry>
      <entry key="cart2pol_invalidDataValue">The input argument values must be numeric, finite, and non-empty.</entry>
      <entry key="cart2pol_invalidDims">The Y and X arguments must be the same size (or either can be scalar).</entry>
      <entry key="cart2pol_invalidMixedDataTypes">The Y and X arguments must be of the same data type class (mixing floating-point and non-floating point types or double and single types is not supported).</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDataType">The datatype ''{0}'' is unsupported for the function {1}</entry>
      <entry key="invalidInputDataTypeAcos">The input ''cosVal'' must be a single, double, or fi object with the property ''DataTypeMode'' equal to ''Fixed-point: binary point scaling'', ''Scaled double: binary point scaling'', ''double'', or ''single''.</entry>
	  <entry key="invalidInputDataTypeAsin">The input ''sinVal'' must be a single, double, or fi object with the property ''DataTypeMode'' equal to ''Fixed-point: binary point scaling'', ''Scaled double: binary point scaling'', ''double'', or ''single''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNiters">The number of iterations (niters) argument of function {0} must be a positive integer-valued scalar.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNitersCodeGen">The number of iterations argument must be a positive integer-valued scalar.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParameter">Argument did not match any valid parameter of the parser.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidScaleOutputArg">Argument ''ScaleOutput'' failed validation.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidSinCosInput">The input value of function {0} must be a real, finite value in the range [-1, 1].</entry>
      <entry key="invalidThetaValue">The angle (theta) argument values of function {0} must be real, numeric, non-empty, and in the range [-2*pi, 2*pi).</entry>
      <entry key="inputWordLengthNotGTOne">CORDIC input arguments must have word lengths greater than one.</entry>
      <entry key="nitersConstCodeGen">The input indicating the number of iterations of the CORDIC kernel must be constant.</entry>
      <entry key="pol2cart_invalidR">The magnitude (r) argument values must be real (consider using CORDICROTATE for complex vector rotation).</entry>
      <entry key="rotate_invalidDims">The u and theta arguments must be the same size (or either can be scalar).</entry>
      <entry key="rotate_invalidMixedDataTypes">The u and theta arguments must be of the same data type class (mixing floating-point and non-floating point types or double and single types is not supported).</entry>
      <entry key="rotate_invalidU">The u argument values must be numeric and non-empty.</entry>
      <entry key="thetaValueOutOfRange">The angle (theta) argument values of function {0} must be in the range [-2*pi, 2*pi).</entry>
      <entry key="invalidHyperbolicArgument">The angle (theta) argument value of function {0} must be real, numeric, non-empty and finite.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidHyperbolicArgumentHDL">The angle (theta) argument value of function {0} must be real, numeric, scalar and finite.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  niters CORDICROTATE
-->
<!-- Copyright 2011-2023 The MathWorks, Inc.
                                      -->
