<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="fixed" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
   <message>
      <entry key="invalidType">Second input argument must be a numerictype object with a fixed-point DataTypeMode</entry>
      <entry key="invalidValues">Invalid data. Data must be finite values. </entry>
      <entry key="invalidWordlength">Invalid wordlength. WordLength should be a discrete value in range [1, 128]</entry>
      <entry key="invalidSafetyMarginConstraint">Invalid SafetyMargin constraint. SafetyMargin constraint should be real and finite. </entry>
      <entry key="invalidAbsTolConstraint">Invalid absTol constraint. AbsTol constraint must be non-negative, real and finite. </entry>
      <entry key="invalidRelTolConstraint">Invalid RelTol constraint. RelTol constraint must be non-negative, real and finite. </entry>
      <entry key="invalidSignednessConstraint">Invalid Signedness constraint. Signedness constraint must be 'Auto' or 'Lock'</entry>
      <entry key="invalidWordLengthConstraint">Invalid WordLength constraint. WordLength constraint must 'Auto' or 'Lock'</entry>
      <entry key="invalidScalingConstraint">Invalid FractionLength constraint. Scaling constraint must 'Auto' or 'Lock'</entry>
      <entry key="noTolerancesMet">Proposed output numerictype does not meet the tolerance constraints with input data. Consider setting WordLength to 'Auto' and Scaling to 'Auto' to get a new datatype that meets the specified constraints</entry>
      <entry key="switchModeOnUnspecifiedScaling">Unable to propose datatype with given constraints. Input numerictype is of unspecified scaling. Switching WordLength constraint to Auto.</entry>
      <entry key="switchModeOnUnspecifiedConstraints">Unable to propose datatype with given constraints. AbsTol, RelTol is undefined. Switching Scaling constraint to Auto, WordLength constraint to Lock.</entry>
      <entry key="noScalingConstraints">Only signedness is proposed with given WordLength and Scaling constraint. Both WordLength and Scaling cannot be locked to propose WordSize and Scaling attributes of output numerictype.</entry>
      <entry key="unableToConstructSBScaling">Unable to propose data type of slope bias scaling with given constraints.</entry>
   </message>
</rsccat>
