<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="NoPackage">Unable to find packages with ''.msg'' files, or ''.srv'' files, or ''.action'' files in {0}. Each message package must contain ''.msg'' files in a directory named ''msg'', or ''.srv'' files in a directory named ''srv'', or ''.action'' files in a directory named ''action'', or a combination of any of these directories.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageName">Invalid message name ''{0}''. Message name must start with an upper case character followed by alphanumerical characters.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCustomMessagesError">Invalid message format, package, or structure found during validation.</entry>
    <entry key="ParserValidationError" translate="false" note="translate=false set due no translatable content">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="CreateColconIgnore">Error creating ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="CreateCatkinIgnore">Error creating ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="MsgFieldNameError">Invalid message field names in message definition {0}. Message field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the message definition file: {1}}</entry>
    <entry key="SrvFieldNameError">Invalid service field names in service definition {0}. Service field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the service definition file: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="ActionFieldNameError">Invalid action field names in action definition {0}. Action field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the action definition file: {1}</entry> 
    <entry key="NoZipFileExists">The input folder is empty. The folder must contain a zip file named {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="FolderExists">The input folder contains {0} folder. To avoid overwriting existing generated messages, copy the zip file to a different location and then execute the registration.</entry>
    <entry key="PlatformNotSupported">Registering these custom messages is not supported for {0}. Sharing custom messages is only supported between systems using the same architecture. You can <![CDATA[<a href="matlab:{1}(''{2}'')">regenerate your custom messages here</a>]]></entry>
    <entry key="ReleaseNotSupported">Registering these custom messages is not supported for {0}. This zip file was created on a {1} release. Sharing custom messages is only supported between systems using the same release. You can <![CDATA[<a href="matlab:{2}(''{3}'')">regenerate your custom messages here</a>]]></entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
