<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Slvnv" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="DDEntry">Data Dictionary Entry</entry>
    <entry key="fix">Fix</entry>
    <entry key="fixAll">Fix All</entry>
    <entry key="fixInLib">In Library</entry>
    <entry key="block">Block</entry>
    <entry key="requirements">Requirements</entry>
    <entry key="update">Update</entry>
    <entry key="currentDescription">Current description</entry>
    <entry key="externalDescription">External description</entry>
    <entry key="currentPath">Current path</entry>
    <entry key="validPath">Valid path</entry>
    <entry key="groupEntry">Requirements Consistency</entry>
    <entry key="taskTitle">Requirements Consistency Checking</entry>
    <entry key="taskTips">Checks consistency of requirements</entry>
    <entry key="checkDocumentTitle">Identify requirement links with missing documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkDocumentTips">Ensure that requirement link to existing documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkDocumentResults">The document {0} could not be found. The following links point to this missing document. Click {1} to locate the missing document or select an appropriate substitute.</entry>
    <entry key="checkDocumentDocBlock">The DocBlock corresponding to {0} could not be found. The following links point to this missing DocBlock. Open the substitute DocBlock and click {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="checkDoorsTitle">Identify IBM DOORS objects linked from Simulink that do not link to Simulink</entry>
    <entry key="checkDoorsTips">Ensure that IBM DOORS objects that are targets of Simulink-to-DOORS requirement links, have corresponding DOORS-to-Requirements Toolbox links.</entry>
    <entry key="checkDoorsResults">The following links point to valid objects in DOORS database, but there are no matching links from DOORS to Simulink. If you prefer to keep the links on both sides in sync, click {0} to insert matching links in DOORS, or remove the link on Simulink side.</entry>
    <entry key="checkIdTitle">Identify requirement links that specify invalid locations within documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkIdTips">Ensure that requirements link to valid locations (e.g., bookmarks, line numbers, anchors) within documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkIdResults">The following requirements link to invalid locations within their documents. The specified location (e.g., bookmark, line number, anchor) within the requirements document could not be found. To resolve this issue, edit each requirement and specify a valid location within its requirements document.</entry>
    <entry key="checkLabelTitle">Identify selection-based links having description fields that do not match their requirements document text</entry>
    <entry key="checkLabelTips">Ensure that description fields of selection-based links use the same text found in their requirements documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkLabelResults">The following selection-based links have descriptions that differ from their corresponding selections in the requirements documents. If this reflects a change in the requirements document, click {0} to replace the current description in the selection-based link with the text from the requirements document (the external description).</entry>
    <entry key="checkResultsLib">You cannot modify requirement links on objects in libraries unless you disable the library link.</entry>
    <entry key="checkPathTitle">Identify requirement links with path type inconsistent with preferences</entry>
    <entry key="checkPathTitleNonPC">Identify requirement links with absolute path type</entry>
    <entry key="checkPathTips">Check that requirements paths are of the type selected in the preferences (absolute, model relative, path relative)</entry>
    <entry key="checkPathTipsNonPC">Check that requirements links are not using absolute path, which is less reliable when models are moved together with requirements documents</entry>
    <entry key="checkPathResults"><![CDATA[For the following requirements, the paths to the requirements use a different path type than the preferred type. The preferred type is set to: {0}. To resolve the inconsistency, do one of the following:<ul><li>To change the preferred type, click <b>Link Settings</b> in <b>REQUIREMENTS VIEWER</b> toolstrip to open the Settings dialog, then adjust <b>Document file reference</b> setting in <b>Selection Linking</b> tab.<br /></li><li>Click <b>Fix</b> to change the current path to the valid path.<br /></li></ul>]]></entry>
    <entry key="checkPathResultsNonPC"><![CDATA[For the following requirements, absolute paths are used. It is recommended that you use paths relative to either the current working directory or the model location. To resolve the inconsistency, do one of the following:<ul><li>Open <b>Outgoing Links</b> dialog for each linked object and edit the <b>Document</b> fields to avoid absolute paths.<br /></li><li>Click <b>Fix</b> to change from absolute to local file path.<br /></li></ul>]]></entry>    
    <entry key="errorInvalidLinkAtObject">Invalid link at object {0}</entry>
    <entry key="errorUnableToResolveType">Unable to resolve requirement link type for {0}</entry>
    <entry key="errorDocCouldNotBeFound">Document {0} could not be found</entry>
    <entry key="errorDocWasNotFound">Document {0} was not found</entry>
    <entry key="errorFailedToLocateItem">Failed to locate item {0} in {1}</entry>
    <entry key="errorUnableToLocateDoc">Unable to locate document {0}</entry>
    <entry key="pathAbsolute">absolute path</entry>
    <entry key="pathPwdRelative">path relative to current folder</entry>
    <entry key="pathRelative">path relative to model folder</entry>
    <entry key="pathNone">filename only</entry>
    <entry key="pathInvalid">Invalid path type</entry>
    <entry key="DocNotFound">The document {0} could not be found.</entry>
    <entry key="EncounteredErrors">Encountered Errors:</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToCheck">Failed to check some items:</entry>
    <entry key="IdNotFound">The following referenced items in document {0} could not be found</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistenciesInMatlab">Inconsistencies in links associated with MATLAB Function code lines</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistenciesInMatlabCodeLinks">Inconsistencies for MATLAB code in {0}</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistenciesInSLDDLinks">Inconsistencies for Data Dictionary {0}</entry>
    <entry key="IssueCount">{0} issue(s)</entry>
    <entry key="LabelNoMatch">The following links have labels that do not match the text in external document</entry>
    <entry key="MCodeLocation">MATLAB code location</entry>
    <entry key="NoLinksToCheck">\n{0} has no links, or the configured User Tag filter does not match any links.</entry>
    <entry key="NotLoaded">Traceability data for {0} is not loaded.</entry>
    <entry key="PathInconsistent">Document {0} has inconsistent path setting</entry>
    <entry key="Requirement">Requirement</entry>
    <entry key="RptSrcLocation">Source Location: </entry>
    <entry key="RptSrcLastSaved">Source last saved: </entry>
    <entry key="RptReqLastSaved">Traceability data last saved: </entry>
    <entry key="RptHasUnsavedChanges">WARNING: unsaved changes detected when generating report</entry>
    <entry key="RptCheckDoc">Requirements associations with missing documents</entry>
    <entry key="RptCheckId">Requirements associations that specify invalid locations within documents</entry>
    <entry key="RptCheckLabel">Requirements associations that have description fields not matching requirements document text</entry>
    <entry key="RptCheckPath">Requirements associations with path type inconsistent with preferences</entry>
    <entry key="RptCountIssues">{0} issues</entry>
    <entry key="RptGeneratedOn">Generated On: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RptGeneratedBy">Generated By: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RptMissingDoc">Missing Documents: </entry>
    <entry key="RptMissingDoorsLink">Missing Links from DOORS: </entry>
    <entry key="RptMissingId">Missing Items: </entry>
    <entry key="RptMismatchedLabel">Mismatched Descriptions: </entry>
    <entry key="RptMismatchedPath">Inconsistent Paths: </entry>
    <entry key="RptOneIssue">1 issue</entry>
    <entry key="RptNoIssues">No issues</entry>
    <entry key="RptRerun">Rerun</entry>
    <entry key="RptTotalItems">Total linked items: </entry>
    <entry key="RptTotalLinks">Total links checked: </entry>
    <entry key="RptTotalFiltered">{0} out of {1}</entry>
    <entry key="SeeReport">See Report</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCheckMissingDoc">Unable to check:</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCheckReferencedItem">Links to outdated imported references detected, see below for the list of imported documents.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToCheckUpdateReferences">Please perform Update in Requirements Editor and use Change Information to identify stale links.</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToSetupMS">Failed to set up Microsoft {0} for Consistency Checking</entry>
    
      <!-- labels above are used by legacy Consistency Checks in Model Advisor. Labels below are used for extension hookup in Requirements Toolbox. -->

      <entry key="ExternalItemChecking">External link destination checking</entry>
      <entry key="PromptToEnableDocChecker">Open and analyze {0} to validate stored identifiers of linked items?</entry>
      <entry key="PressNotNowToSkip">Press "Not now" to skip and assume valid.</entry>
      <entry key="CheckBtn">Validate</entry>
      <entry key="SkipBtn">Not now</entry>
      <entry key="CheckError">Error checking link destination</entry>

  </message>
</rsccat>
