<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="mlreportgen" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="mustBeBlock">Value must be string, DOM element object, hole reporter object with HoleID: "{0}" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeEquation">Value must be LaTeX equation string, DOM Image object, Image Reporter, hole reporter object with HoleID: "{0}" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeImage">Value must be image filepath string, DOM Image object, hole reporter object with HoleID: "{0}" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeImageOrSnapshotMaker">Value must be image filepath string, DOM object, SnapshotMaker reporter object, hole reporter object with HoleID: "{0}" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeInline">Value must be string, DOM inline object or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeInstanceOf">Value must be an instance of {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeInstanceOfMultiClass">Value must be an instance of one of the following classes: ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeLinkTarget">Value must be string, DOM LinkTarget object, or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeList">Must be an N-element array whose size is 1xN or Nx1.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeLogical">Value must be logical true or false.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeSingleValue">Value must be single value.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeString">Value must be MATLAB string or char array.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeTabular">Value must be DOM Table, Formal Table, MATLAB Table, content to create a DOM Table or hole reporter object with HoleID: "{0}" or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeValidTemplateSrc">Value must be a non empty Template path, DOM Document object, DOM DocumentPart object, Report or Reporter object or [] empty matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeVectorOf">Value must be a one-dimensional array whose elements are objects of the following classes: ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeWatermark">Value must be watermark filepath string, DOM Watermark object, or [].</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeScalar">值必须为标量。</entry>
    <entry key="unsupportedNumberOfDimensions">不支持的维数。</entry>
    <entry key="mustBeDimension">Invalid Dimension value.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
