<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2025 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="BusTypePropBlockHasUnsetInputInfo">''{0}'' has unset signal bus type information for input port {1,number,integer}. Currently there is not enough information to solve the model. Please consider adding a Signal Specification block with a bus object before the input port. To set the bus type to nonvirtual, check the ''Require nonvirtual bus'' checkbox in the Signal Specification block parameters dialog. </entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropBlockHasUnsetOutputInfo">''{0}'' has unset signal bus type information for output port {1,number,integer}. Currently there is not enough information to solve the model. Please consider adding a Signal Specification block with a bus object after the output port. To set the bus type to nonvirtual, check the ''Require nonvirtual bus'' checkbox in the Signal Specification block parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropBusConfiguredForNVB"> ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输出端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 必须连接到非虚拟总线或非总线信号。要将虚拟总线转换为非虚拟总线或向量，请使用 Signal Conversion 或 Bus to Vector 模块。</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropBusConfiguredForNVBIn"> &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;Input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of ''{1}'' must connect to a nonvirtual bus or nonbus signal. To convert a virtual bus to a nonvirtual bus or vector, use a Signal Conversion or Bus to Vector block.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropSrcDstMismatchBusSrc">''{3}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{3}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 需要非总线信号，但接收到来自 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输出端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 的总线。要将虚拟总线转换为向量，请使用 Bus to Vector 模块。要选择总线的元素，请使用 Bus Selector 模块。</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropSrcDstMismatchBusSrcStateflow">Cannot propagate bus signal to &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of ''{1}'' because this input port requires a non-bus signal. \n\nIf the destination block is a bus-capable block, ensure that the block configuration and its input signal(s) meet the requirements for bus support. Please see Simulink documentation for further information on composite (i.e. bus) signals and their proper usage. Alternately, if the input bus signal is virtual; consists only of scalar elements, 1-D elements, or either row or column vectors; and all elements have the same data type, signal type, and sampling mode, consider inserting a Bus to Vector conversion block in the signal path. Otherwise, consider using a Bus Selector block in the signal path.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropSrcDstMismatchVB">All input signals to the block ''{0}'' must be of the same type (bus or non-bus). The signal at input port {1,number,integer}  is a virtual bus while the signal at input port {2,number,integer} is not a bus signal. If the input bus signal consists only of scalar elements, 1-D elements, or either row or column vectors; and all elements have the same data type, signal type, and sampling mode, consider inserting a Bus to Vector conversion block in the signal path.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropVirtualityMismatchNVToV">到模块 ''{0}'' 的所有输入总线必须具有相同的虚拟性。输入端口 {1,number,integer} 上的总线是非虚拟总线，而输入端口 {2,number,integer} 上的总线是虚拟总线。</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropVirtualityMismatchNVToVVariantMerge">All input buses from Variant Subsystem choices to the Outport block ''{0}'' must be of the same virtuality (all Virtual or all Nonvirtual). To fix this issue the output of ''{1}'' must be a nonvirtual bus which can be created by adding a Signal Conversion block which is configured to convert virtual buses to nonvirtual buses.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropVirtualityMismatchNVToVVariantMergeHier">All input buses from Variant Subsystem choices to the Outport block ''{0}'' must be of the same virtuality. One way to fix this issue, is to set all the Variant choice blocks' outport bus types to be nonvirtual.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropVirtualityMismatchNVToNB">All input buses to the block ''{0}'' must be of the same virtuality. The bus at input port {1,number,integer} is nonvirtual, while the signal at input port {2,number,integer} is not a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="BusTypePropVirtualityMismatchVToNV">到模块 ''{0}'' 的所有输入总线必须具有相同的虚拟性。输入端口 {1,number,integer} 上的总线是虚拟总线，而输入端口 {2,number,integer} 上的总线是非虚拟总线。</entry>
    <entry key="BusVectorCompilationRequired">Cannot get the list of BusAsVector ports unless the model is in compiled state.</entry>
    <entry key="EditTimeBusPropFailureInputPort">Unable to determine the signal hierarchy entering &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of ''{1}''. In order to determine the signal hierarchy, Simulink must inspect upstream blocks and propagate information about the signal hierarchy to this block. Simulink encountered an error condition during this process. The specific diagnostic message is:</entry>
    <entry key="EditTimeBusPropFailureOutputPort">Unable to determine the signal hierarchy at the &lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;output port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of ''{1}''. In order to determine the signal hierarchy, Simulink must inspect upstream blocks and propagate information about the signal hierarchy to this block. Simulink encountered an error condition during this process. The specific diagnostic message is:</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockBusSettingDoesntMatchPropInfo">模块 ''{0}'' 上输入总线的层次结构必须与该模块指定的总线对象的层次结构匹配。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockBusSettingDoesntMatchPropInfoNonBus">模块 ''{0}'' 指定总线对象，并且必须接收与指定的总线对象匹配的总线。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockBusSettingSubBusDoesntMatchPropInfo">模块 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输入端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 需要与该模块指定的总线对象 ''{2}'' 具有相同层次结构的总线，但该模块接收到的总线不包含数据类型为 ''{3}'' 的元素。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockHasUnequalBusInputs">馈入模块 ''{0}'' 的总线信号不具有相同的信号名称和层次结构。该模块的所有总线输入信号必须具有相同的名称和层次结构。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockHasUnequalInputs">The signals feeding into block ''{0}'' do not have the same signal names and hierarchies. All input signals to this block must have the same names and hierarchical structure.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockHasUnsetInputInfo">''{0}'' has unset signal name and hierarchy information for input port {1,number,integer}. If this error message references a built-in Simulink block, please contact MathWorks for assistance.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBlockHasUnsetOutputInfo">''{0}'' has unset signal name and hierarchy information for output port {1,number,integer}. If this error message references a built-in Simulink block, please contact MathWorks for assistance.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBusAssignOutputDoesNotMatchInput">在模块 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 上的输入总线中找不到所选信号 ''{0}''。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBusSelOutputDoesNotMatchInput">在模块 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 上的输入总线中找不到所选信号 ''{0}''。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBusAssignOutputDoesNotMatchInputWithVariants">Unable to find selected signal ''{0}'' in the input bus signal of block ''{1}'', &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;Input port {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt;, because there is an 'always false' condition propagating from the variant block whose variant activation time is set to 'update diagram'.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropBusSelOutputDoesNotMatchInputWithVariants">Unable to find selected signal ''{0}'' in the input bus signal of block ''{1}'', &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;Input port {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt;, because there is an 'always false' condition propagating from the variant block whose variant activation time is set to 'update diagram'.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropInputToBlockMustBeABus">&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;Input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; for ''{1}'' must be a bus signal.</entry>
    <entry key="BusToVectorBlockShouldAcceptVirtualBus">非总线信号连接到 Bus to Vector 模块 ''{0}'' 的输入端口，该端口仅在输入信号为虚拟总线时起作用。因此，请考虑删除 Bus to Vector 模块。 </entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropMaxRecursionExceeded">Hierarchical depth of a bus signal has exceeded the logical limit imposed by the Bus Creator and Out Bus Element blocks in the model.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropNoSolutionLoop">Unable to determine signal hierarchy. The output of ''{0}'' is fed back to the input port of the same block through other bus capable blocks. This loop cannot be resolved because signal hierarchy is defined by a recursive relationship. To resolve this issue, consider breaking the loop by selecting the correct signal with a Bus Selector or an In Bus Element block.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcDstMismatchBusSrc">''{3}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{3}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 需要非总线信号，但接收到来自 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输出端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 的总线。要将虚拟总线转换为向量，请使用 Bus to Vector 模块。要选择总线的元素，请使用 Bus Selector 模块。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcDstMismatch">''{3}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{3}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 需要与它从 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输出端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 接收的总线具有不同结构体的总线。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcDstMismatchNonBusSrc">''{3}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{3}"&gt;输入端口 {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 需要总线，但接收到来自 ''{1}'' 的&lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;输出端口 {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; 的非总线信号。</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcDstMismatchNonBusSrcForIVBlocks"> 无法将非总线信号从模块 ''{0}'' 的输出端口传播到目标模块 ''{1}'' 的输入端口，因为目标模块需要总线信号。 </entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcDstMismatchNonBusSrcForMessages">Cannot propagate non-bus signal to &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of ''{1}'' because the destination block requires a bus signal.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSrcsCannotHaveDynamicSetting">Source ''{0}'' cannot have dynamic signal hierarchy setting for its output port {1,number,integer}. All sources should explicitly set all their signal name and hierarchy in Block Eval params. If this error message references a built-in Simulink block, please contact MathWorks for assistance.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropTooManyOutputs">Block ''{0}'' uses the default set function in the signal hierarchy propagator but it has more than one output. This block must implement a custom set function. If this error message references a built-in Simulink block, please contact MathWorks for assistance.</entry>
    <entry key="SigHierPropSelectIntoMsg">Selected element ''{0}'' in ''{1}'' is part of message data. Use ''{1}'' to select and output the entire message.</entry>
    <entry key="VarDimsNotSupportedForUnconnectedBusSources">The bus object ''{0}'' specified by the unconnected bus source block ''{1}'' contains one or more variable-sized elements. You cannot associate unconnected bus sources with bus objects that contain variable-sized elements. </entry>
    <entry key="VarDimsNotPermittedForAoB1">The bus object ''{0}'' associated with the block ''{1}'' contains both a variable sized element and an array of sub-buses. Arrays of buses cannot be used in conjunction with bus objects that contain variable sized elements. </entry>
    <entry key="VarDimsNotPermittedForAoB2">The bus object ''{0}'' associated with the block ''{1}'' contains a variable sized element and the block specifies non-scalar dimensions. Arrays of buses cannot be used in conjunction with bus objects that contain variable sized elements. </entry>
    <entry key="VarDimsNotPermittedForAoB3">The input non-virtual bus signal to port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}'', and defined by bus object ''{2}'', contains one or more variable sized bus elements. This block cannot operate on non-virtual bus signals that contain variable sized elements. </entry>
    <entry key="VarDimsNotPermittedForAoB4">无法在模块 ''{2}'' 的输入端口 {1,number,integer} 上对由总线对象 ''{0}'' 定义的非虚拟总线信号进行操作。这是因为输入端口 {1,number,integer} 已配置为接收可变大小信号。 </entry>
    <entry key="FramesNotPermittedForAoB1">The bus object ''{0}'' associated with the block ''{1}'' contains both an element with frame based sampling mode and an array of sub-buses. Arrays of buses cannot be used in conjunction with bus objects that contain frame based elements. </entry>
    <entry key="FramesNotPermittedForAoB2">The bus object ''{0}'' associated with the block ''{1}'' contains an element with frame based sampling mode and the block specifies non-scalar dimensions. Arrays of buses cannot be used in conjunction with bus objects that contain frame based elements. </entry>
    <entry key="FramesNotPermittedForAoB3">The input non-virtual bus signal to port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}'', and defined by bus object ''{2}'', contains one or more elements with frame based sampling mode. This block cannot operate on non-virtual bus signals that contain bus elements with frame based sampling mode. </entry>
    <entry key="ExpansionNotPermittedForAoB1">Input to block ''{0}'' is an array of bus signal or contains an element which is an array of bus. The block's ''Initial condition'' parameter is a non-zero scalar or vector value. Consider using a matching MATLAB structure (see Simulink.Bus.createMATLABStruct) or a scalar zero to initialize the array of buses.</entry>
    <entry key="ExpansionNotPermittedForAoB2">Converting arrays of buses to virtual buses is not supported. Specify a nonvirtual bus output for block ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="ExpansionNotPermittedForAoB3">Input to block ''{0}'' is an array of bus signal. This {1} block's ''Output'' parameter is configured to produce a virtual bus, which is not supported with array of bus inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="NVToVConversionNotSupportAOB">&lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0,number,integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;Input port {0,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of block ''{1}'' contains an array of bus signal. This {2} block is configured to require a virtual bus. An array of bus signal is only supported in a non-virtual bus.</entry>
    <entry key="SlUpdateArraysOfBusesReason">为根 Inport 或 Outport 模块检测到不兼容的维度设置。如果为具有非标量维度的根 Inport 或 Outport 模块指定了总线数据类型，则在 R2010a 之前创建的模型无法使用这些模块。</entry>
    <entry key="VCNVDoesNotSupportAOBWithDiscontiguousIndices">Block ''{0}'' does not support the array of buses, which has discontiguous indices, from block ''{1}''. At the output port of block ''{1}'', insert a signal conversion block that uses the default ''Output'' setting (''Signal Copy'').</entry>
    <entry key="StrictBusMigrationStub2">打开升级顾问</entry>
    <entry key="ExplicitBusSetupRequiredForSfcnOutput">S-function block ''{0}'' has a bus data type ''{1}'' propagating out of &lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{2,number,integer}" objname="{0}"&gt;output port {2,number,integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt;. For S-function blocks to operate with bus signals, bus data type information must be specified in the mdlInitializeSizes method using the ssSetBusOutputObjectName and ssSetBusOutputAsStruct macros.</entry>
    <entry key="BusCC_BusCheckFailedShort">传播到模块 ''{1}'' 的输入端口的总线对象 ''{0}'' 与通过模块对话框指定的或传播到该模块的其他输入端口的总线对象 ''{2}'' 不匹配。</entry>
    <entry key="VariantReducerDoesNotSupportVCNV">The Variant Reducer does not support a virtual bus that contains a nonvirtual bus. Insert a Signal Conversion block at the &lt;sldiag objui="inport" objparam="{0, number, integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;input port {0, number, integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of block ''{1}'' to convert the input to a virtual bus.</entry>
    <entry key="VariantReducerDoesNotSupportVCNVOutput">The Variant Reducer does not support a virtual bus that contains a nonvirtual bus. Insert a Signal Conversion block at the &lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0, number, integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;output port {0, number, integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of block ''{1}'' to convert the output to a virtual bus.</entry>
    <entry key="BusRegisterShadowClassBasedBus">总线对象 ''{0}'' 已使用 Simulink.Bus.register 注册，并且未与 MATLAB 类 ''{0}'' 关联。要将该类用作总线，请使用 Simulink.Bus.deregister 注销此总线对象。</entry>
    <entry key="BusRegisterInvalidInputArgs">输入参数无效。函数 Simulink.Bus.register 需要下列输入: (1) 名称，(2) 有效总线对象，(3) 用于强制注册的可选逻辑值，(4) ''blockHandle'' 或 ''docLink'' 名称-值对组。</entry>
    <entry key="BusDeRegisterInvalidInputArgs">输入参数无效。函数 Simulink.Bus.deregister 只需要一个表示要注销的总线对象名称的输入。</entry>
    <entry key="BusRegisterCannotOverwrite">总线对象 ''{0}'' 已存在。要覆盖总线对象，请将 ''forceRegister'' 输入参数设置为 true。</entry>
    <entry key="DynamicBusNotResolvable">Cannot create a valid dynamic bus type at &lt;sldiag objui="outport" objparam="{0, number, integer}" objname="{1}"&gt;output port {0, number, integer}&lt;/sldiag&gt; of the MATLAB System block  ''{1}''. To fix the issue, please check the getOutputDataTypeImpl method of the block's system object class.</entry>
    <entry key="DynamicBusCannotUseNonBusInputs">Cannot create a valid dynamic bus type at the output of the MATLAB System block ''{0}''. The information of an input scalar signal is not allowed to be used to create a dynamic bus. To fix the issue, please check the getOutputDataTypeImpl method of the block's system object class.</entry>
    <entry key="DynamicBusMustHaveNamesAtEachLevel">Cannot create a valid dynamic bus type at the output of the MATLAB System block ''{0}''. The Simulink.SignalDescriptor object used to describe a dynamic bus type must have a valid data type name specified at each level of the bus. To fix the issue, please check the getOutputDataTypeImpl method of the block's system object class.</entry>
    <entry key="DynamicBusTopLevelCannotContainDimensions">The dynamic bus type ''{0}'' created by the MATLAB System block ''{1}'' has its ''dimensions'' property specified. Please set its ''dimensions'' to the default value 1 and use the ''getOutputSizeImpl'' method to specify the dimensions of the output signal instead.</entry>
    <entry key="DynamicBusNameLengthCheck">MATLAB System block ''{0}'' creates bus type ''{1}'' with a name that has ''{2}'' characters. Name length must be less than 64 characters.</entry>
    <entry key="RootIOPortCannotUseBusesFromBusDictionary">Specifying bus object ''{0}'' as the data type of a root Inport or Outport block (''{1}'') is not supported because the bus object is not in the base workspace or a data dictionary. To create the bus object in the base workspace or a data dictionary, use Simulink.Bus.createObject. </entry>
    <entry key="NdBusInDynamicArrayNotAllowed">无法保留总线对象 ''{0}'' 的维度，因为它用于模块 ''{1}'' 中的无界数组。请清除 ''{0}'' 的保留维度属性或将 ''{1}'' 的信号维度设置为固定值。</entry>
    <entry key="NdBusWithColumnMajorNotAllowed">The bus object ''{0}'' is set to preserve dimensions for the block diagram ''{1}'' whose array layout is Column-major. To preserve dimensions, set the array layout parameter to Row-major or clear the preserve dimension property of the bus object ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="NdBusWithUnsupportedTarget">总线对象 ''{0}'' 设置为保留具有不受支持代码生成目标的模块图 ''{1}'' 的维度。仅 ERT 目标支持保留总线对象的维度。</entry>
    <entry key="NdBusWithVarDimsNotAllowed">The bus object ''{0}'' used in the model ''{1}'' contains variable-sized elements and it is set to preserve element dimensions. Preserving dimensions for bus elements is not supported when the bus object has variable-sized elements.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
