<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2025 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="FunctionToImportMismatch">Functions ''{0}'' do not exist, are undefined, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="TypeToImportMismatch">Types ''{0}'' do not exist, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="AmbiguousTypeToImport">无法导入类型 ''{0}''，因为这些类型在不同命名空间下具有相同名称。请选择类型、函数或类方法，确保仅导入其中一个类型。</entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindOutputFolder">Unable to find the specified output folder ''{0}''. Check your output folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableOutputFolder">Output folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify an output folder that is not write-protected. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseUnsuccessful">无法解析自定义代码。 </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyParseResult">Code Importer parser returned empty result. </entry>
    <entry key="BuildUnsuccessful">Failed to build custom code executable. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceHeader">请至少指定一个要导入的接口头文件。可通过调用 ''computeInterfaceHeaders'' 方法基于指定的源文件计算接口头。</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceHeaderUI">请至少指定一个要导入的接口头文件。可通过点击 "自动填充" 按钮基于指定的源文件计算接口头。</entry>
    <entry key="EmptySourceFile">指定至少一个要导入的源文件。 </entry>
    <entry key="InferringHdrWithEmptySrc">请指定至少一个源文件来计算接口头文件。 </entry>
    <entry key="CannotLoadFile">Unable to load the specified file ''{0}''. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotReadFunctionSettings">Failed to read Code Importer settings. The specified file ''{0}'' is not a Code Importer settings file, or is corrupted. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsFilePath">Unable to load the file ''{0}'' because it does not exist on the computed file path ''{1}''. Check your full path specification ''{2}'' against output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsPath">Unable to find the directory ''{0}''. Check your directory folder specification against the output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="MetadataFileNotCompatible">Unable to load the metadata file. Code Importer only supports MAT-file and ASAP2 format metadata files. </entry>
    <entry key="ASAP2WindowsOnlyWarn">ASAP2 file can only be imported on Windows.</entry>
    <entry key="GRLWindowsOnlyWarn">GRL file can only be imported on Windows.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindMetadataFile">Unable to find the specified metadata file ''{0}''. Check the specified MetadataFile path in CustomCode property.</entry>
    <entry key="DuplicateVariableNameInMetadataFile">Variable name ''{0}'' has duplicate entries in the metadata file. </entry>
    <entry key="NonexistentProjectFile">Unable to load project file. Specified project file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="ImportRequiredBeforeAddToProject">Cannot add files to the project. Perform an import before adding to project.</entry>
    <entry key="ProjectWithinIncludeDir">Unable to add file or folder ''{0}'' to the project. File or folder must be inside of specified project root folder ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSaveFile">Failed to save Code Importer settings. </entry>
    <entry key="FilePathNotExist">The specified folder or file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotOverwrite">File ''{0}'' already exists. Specify a different file name, or to overwrite, set 'Overwrite' to 'on'. </entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotWritable">File ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a file that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="NoFileToLoad">Specify one file to load. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableFolder">Folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a folder that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToOpenSLBlocksFile">Unable to create ''slblocks.m'' in directory ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLibraryFileName">''{0}'' 不是有效的库文件名。请指定有效的 Simulink 模型文件名。</entry>
    <entry key="NothingToImport">There are no Simulink compatible functions or types to import. To import classes, specify classes by namespace qualified names.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotInferHeaderFile"> 接口头文件信息为空。请检查源文件并包括目录设定或显式指定接口头文件。 </entry>
    <entry key="InferHeadersUnsupported">接口头文件的计算不适用于单元测试工作流。 </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToLoadSLTestSavedFileToBase">无法加载由 Simulink Test 的代码导入器保存的导入设置文件。要加载该文件，请从测试管理器中打开 Simulink Test 的代码导入器。 </entry>
    <entry key="ClassSimulinkInterfaceUndefined">必须定义导入的类 ''{0}'' 的 Simulink 接口。</entry>
    <entry key="ClassTypeToImportMismatch">类型为 ''{0}'' 的类不存在，或者它与 Simulink 不兼容。 </entry>
    <entry key="OptionsCreateSLBlocks_Ignored">无法将模型 ''{0}'' 添加到 Simulink 库浏览器。该模型必须为库模型。</entry>
    <entry key="ValidateSimulinkInterfaceUnsuccessful">无法在类 ''{1}'' 的 Simulink 接口中验证 ''{0}''。 </entry>
    <entry key="ValidateSimulinkInterfaceSuccessful">已成功验证类 ''{0}'' 的 Simulink 接口。 </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInterfaceErrorResult">验证 Simulink 接口的代码导入器返回的结果为空。 </entry>
    <entry key="ValidateInterfaceErrors">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="ConflictLoadedModelPath">Specified output folder ''{0}'' is inconsistent with the path of the loaded model or library ''{1}''. The specified output folder must either match the path of the loaded model or library, or you can move the loaded model or library to output folder ''{0}''. </entry>
    <entry key="IncorrectTestTypeForSandboxCreation">Sandbox cannot be created for Integration Testing workflow. To create a sandbox change the ''TestType'' property to ''UnitTest''.</entry>
    <entry key="SandboxDoesNotExistError">Sandbox does not exist. Use createSandbox method to create a sandbox.</entry>
    <entry key="MoreThanOneSrcSingleSrcSbxError"> ''GenerateAggregatedHeader'' sandbox should contain only one source file. Custom code has {0} source files: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="SandboxUpdateError">Sandbox files have changed. Use createSandbox method to refresh the sandbox.</entry>
    <entry key="CustomCodeChangedSandboxUpdateError">Custom code files specified in the ''CustomCode'' property have changed. Use createSandbox method to refresh the sandbox.</entry>
    <entry key="SandboxCreationFailedError">Code Importer failed to create the sandbox.</entry>
    <entry key="SandboxParseFailedError">Code Importer sandbox parse was unsuccessful.</entry>
    <entry key="AutoStubGenerationFailedError">Code Importer failed to generate auto stub files.</entry>
    <entry key="GenerateSLBlocksIgnored">Code Importer option ''LibraryBrowserName'' is not applicable for testing workflow.</entry>
    <entry key="GenerateTestHarnessIgnored">Simulink Test is required to create test harness for imported library blocks. </entry>
    <entry key="MissingSymbolsInSandbox">Declarations for the following symbols are missing. These symbols cannot be automatically stubbed. Declare these symbols in the sandbox manual stub files and execute ''createSandbox'' method to update the sandbox and proceed.</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingInSandbox">缺失符号: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MissingSymbolsInSandboxUI">Declarations for the following symbols are missing. These symbols cannot be automatically stubbed. Declare these symbols in the sandbox manual stub files and click on ''Update Sandbox'' button to proceed.</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingFunction">函数:</entry>
    <entry key="SymbolsMissingType">类型:</entry>
    <entry key="ImportSpecialTypesError">代码导入器无法将所选类型导入 Simulink 数据字典。</entry>
    <entry key="ParseErrors">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="BuildErrors">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="SLTestCodeImporterFailureCause">{0}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
