<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="look1MaxAndMin">Maximum x value must be larger than minimum x value (including quantization).</entry>
    <entry key="look1NotFixPt">The input is not a fixed point data type so the power of two spacing restriction will be ignored.</entry>
    <entry key="look1InvalidLimits">Both upper limits were invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="look1ScaleNotEven">ASSERT: Scaling not even.</entry>
    <entry key="look1DTNotSupport">不支持此数据类型的类。</entry>
    <entry key="look1EvenSpacingConversionInputOutOfBounds">Input data is outside the range of its data type. Consider using the Lookup Table Optimizer to convert unevenly spaced lookup tables to use even spacing. </entry>
    <entry key="numInputArg">必须指定至少两个输入参数。</entry>
    <entry key="num2fixptNonDoubleVal">num2fixpt requires the first parameter to be double.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTNoArg">必须指定第一个输入参数。</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTInputArg">This model has not been loaded, or the provided handle or model name is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTLibrary">模型 {0} 是一个库。 </entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTResolve">无法解析模块 {3} 中数据类型 {2} 的 {0} 或 {1}。</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose0">找不到 slDataTypeAndScale() 调用。</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose1u">以下不必要的 slDataTypeAndScale() 调用已被替换。</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose1">以下 slDataTypeAndScale() 调用是不必要的，可以自动替换。</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose2">以下 slDataTypeAndScale() 调用需要用户检查以确定它们是否为不必要的。</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleNumDTWithAliasOn">slDataTypeAndScale() 的第一个参数 ''{0}'' 计算结果为完全指定的 Simulink.NumericType 对象且 IsAlias 设置为 true。不再支持 slDataTypeAndScale() 的这种用法。您可以放心地用其第一个参数替换此调用。{1}</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleAliasDT">The first argument ''{0}'' of slDataTypeAndScale() evaluates to a Simulink.AliasType object with a fully specified base type. Such usage of slDataTypeAndScale() is no longer supported. You can safely replace this call with its first argument. {1}</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleUpgrade">要针对此问题和其他已知升级问题自动更新您的模型，请点击&lt;a href="matlab:modeladvisor ''{0}''"&gt;此链接&lt;/a&gt;以启动模型顾问并运行以下任务: ''{1}''。您也可以通过运行脚本 &lt;a href="matlab:slRemoveDataTypeAndScale(''{2}'')"&gt;slRemoveDataTypeAndScale&lt;/a&gt; 来解决此问题。</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleBusDT">The first argument ''{0}'' of slDataTypeAndScale() evaluates to a Simulink.Bus object. Such usage of slDataTypeAndScale() is not valid.</entry>
    <entry key="InvWordLength">Invalid WordLength ''{0}'' specified; the WordLength must be a scalar numeric value that is greater than 0.</entry>
    <entry key="InvFractionLength">指定的 FractionLength ''{0}'' 无效；FractionLength 必须为标量整数值。</entry>
    <entry key="FxDLicenseRequired">Fixed-Point Designer license is required to run the example. Ensure that the product is installed and a license is available.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveDTOModel">Data type override is active on the model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;. This enables you to simulate floating-point behavior regardless of the data types specified on the blocks. To learn how to control this setting, refer to the &lt;a href="matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot,'fixedpoint','fixedpoint.map'), 'dtOverride')"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveMMOModel">Min, max and overflow logging is active on the model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;. To learn how to control this setting and view collected simulation data, refer to the &lt;a href="matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot,'fixedpoint','fixedpoint.map'), 'minMaxOverflow')"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveDTOModelNoLinks">Data type override is active on the model ''{0}''. This enables you to simulate floating-point behavior regardless of the data types specified on the blocks. To change this setting, open Fixed-Point Tool. To learn more, refer to the Fixed-Point Designer documentation.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveMMOModelNoLinks">Min, max and overflow logging is active on the model ''{0}''. To learn how to control this setting and view collected simulation data, refer to the Fixed-Point Designer documentation.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzTopModelSetInNormalMode">The model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt; is configured to simulate flush-to-zero (FTZ) behavior, but is using normal mode simulation. To observe FTZ behavior, simulate the model using an accelerated mode.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzRefModelSetInNormalMode">The model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt; is configured to simulate flush-to-zero (FTZ) behavior, but an instance of the model is using normal mode simulation. To observe FTZ behavior, reconfigure the required model instance to simulate using an accelerated mode.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzLicenseCheckout">The model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt; is configured to simulate flush-to-zero (FTZ) behavior, which requires the &lt;a href="matlab:web('https://www.mathworks.com/products/fixed-point-designer.html')"&gt;Fixed-Point Designer&lt;/a&gt;, but license checkout failed.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
