<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="BoundsDatatypesMismatch">Lower and upper bounds must have the same data type.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleSizes">Lower and upper bounds must have compatible sizes with the input array or the corresponding variables in the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleBounds">The size of the lower bound must be compatible with the size of the upper bound.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLowerBound">Lower bound must be less than or equal to upper bound.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBoundsForNontabularInputs">Tabular bounds are only supported when the first input is tabular.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBounds">Lower and upper bounds must be nonmissing.</entry>
    <entry key="CharInputsNotSupported">Char inputs are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="BoundsPrecisionLoss">When arguments have mixed numeric data types, bounds must be within the range of values that the type of the input data can represent.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInputTypeForNVArguments">Name-value arguments ''DataVariables'' and ''ReplaceValues'' are supported only for tabular input data.</entry>
    <entry key="ArgNameValueMismatch">Incorrect number of input arguments. Each parameter name must be followed by a corresponding value.</entry>
    <entry key="ComplexNumbersNotSupported">Input data, lower bound, and upper bound must be real.</entry>   
    <entry key="TabularBoundsRequired">Lower and upper bounds must be one-row tables if the table variables to operate on have mixed data types.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownParameter">Parameter name must be ''DataVariables'' or ''ReplaceValues''.</entry>
    <entry key="DataVariablesTableSubscript">''DataVariables'' value must be a variable name, a vector of variable names, variable indices, logical values, a pattern, a function handle, or a vartype subscript.</entry>
    <entry key="DataVariablesFunctionHandle">''DataVariables'' function handle must return a logical scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTabularBoundsWithDataVars">Variable names specified by ''DataVariables'' must match variable names in tabular bounds.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTabularBounds">Variable names in tabular lower and upper bounds must match.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTabularBoundsFirstInput">Variable names in tabular lower and upper bounds must be present in the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSizesInTabularBounds">Table variables in upper bound must have the same size as table variables in lower bound.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>