<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
      <entry key="BothLabelsandLabelsVariable">Specify either event labels or an event labels variable.</entry>
      <entry key="BothLengthsandLengthsVariable">Specify either event lengths or an event lengths variable.</entry>
      <entry key="BothEndsandEndsVariable">Specify either event ends or an event ends variable.</entry>
      <entry key="FirstInputMustBeTimetable">''{0}'' name-value pair is only supported when the first input is a timetable.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidFirstInput">First input must either be a timetable or it must be a datetime or duration vector.</entry>
      <entry key="WrongHeightArg">''{0}'' must either be a scalar or a vector with the same number of elements as the height of the first input.</entry>
      <entry key="BothLengthsandEnds">Specify either event lengths or event ends but not both.</entry>
      <entry key="CategoricalAndLabels">Event labels or an event labels variable are not supported when the second input is a categorical.</entry>
      <entry key="MustBeCategoricalOrTime">The second input must be a valid timetable row subscript or a categorical vector.</entry>
      <entry key="ConflictingEventAndDataVars">{0} must not be in the list of EventDataVariables.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLengthsVariable">Event lengths variable must be a duration or calendarDuration column vector.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLabelsCategorical">The number of elements in the labels categorical vector must be the same as the number of rows of the input timetable.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTime">Event labels variable must not be a datetime, duration, or calendarDuration variable.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableSize">Event labels variable must be a column vector.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableChar">Event labels variable must not be a char variable. Use a string array instead.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTabular">Event labels variable must not be a nested tabular variable.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidEndsVariable">Event ends variable must be a datetime or duration column vector.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleLengthsRowTimes">Event lengths variable must be a duration variable if the event table has duration rowtimes.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleEndsRowTimes">Event ends variable must be the same data type as the event table row times.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleEndsRowTimesTZ">Event ends variable and row times must both have time zones, or must both be unzoned.</entry>
      <entry key="NoAttachedEvents">Timetable must have an event table assigned to the Events property.</entry>
      <entry key="NonScalarLabel">The default label supplied to syncevents must be a scalar.</entry>
      <entry key="CannotMergeEvents">The event tables attached to the timetables cannot be automatically merged. Consider detaching the event tables and merging them separately. When the input timetables have different event tables attached to them, they are merged by outerjoin using the common variables as keys.</entry>
      <entry key="DifferentTaggedVariables">All event tables must have the same event labels variable, event lengths variable, and event ends variable.</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleLoad" note="Do NOT add period ('.') at the end - it is intentionally left out.">Unable to load the saved eventtable because it is incompatible with this version of MATLAB</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleLoadProperties" note="Do NOT add period ('.') at the end - it is intentionally left out.">Unable to load the saved EventtableProperties because it is incompatible with this version of MATLAB</entry>
      <entry key="IncompatibleEventFilterLoad" note="Do NOT add period ('.') at the end - it is intentionally left out.">Unable to load the saved eventfilter because it is incompatible with this version of MATLAB</entry>
      <entry key="NonScalarEventVars">Specify one variable in the input to be used as the ''{0}''. Use a positive integer, a variable name, or a logical vector containing a single true value.</entry>
      <entry key="ExtracteventsMissingEventVariables">In order to specify PreserveEventVariables, provide at least one of EventDataVariables, EventLabelsVariable, EventLengthsVariable, or EventEndsVariable.</entry>
      <entry key="ExtracteventsMissingSecondOutput">Using extractevents and specifying PreserveEventVariables without assigning the second output to a workspace variable does not modify the input timetable.\nUse [et,tt] = extractevents(tt,...,EventDataVariables=datavars,PreserveEventVariables=tf).</entry>
      <entry key="RelationalOperation">Operation ''{0}'' is not allowed for event tables when EventLengthsVariable or EventEndsVariable is set.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidOutputLabels">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the event labels variable ''{1}'' generated an error.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidOutputLengths">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the event lengths variable ''{1}'' generated an error.</entry>
      <entry key="InvalidOutputEnds">Applying the function ''{0}'' to the event ends variable ''{1}'' generated an error.</entry>
  <!-- ui strings -->
      <entry key="UILabelsVarUnset">&lt;unset&gt;</entry>
      <entry key="UILabelsVar">Event Labels Variable:</entry>
      <entry key="UILengthsVarInstant">&lt;instantaneous&gt;</entry>
      <entry key="UILengthsVar">Event Lengths Variable:</entry>
      <entry key="UIEndsVar">Event Ends Variable:</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
