<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="EventTableInput">Creating an event filter from an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then create the event filter from the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="EventFilterOnEventTable">Using an event filter as a subscript on an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then subscript into the timetable using the event filter.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsAttached">Creating an event filter for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To create an event filter from this timetable, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsForSubscripting">Using an event filter as a subscript for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To subscript this timetable with an event filter, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventLabelsForSubscripting">To subscript into a timetable using an event filter created using an event label value, the event table attached to the timetable must have the EventLabelsVariable property set.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEventFilterInput">Invalid input to eventfilter. Input must be one of the following:\n - string vector, character vector, or cell array of character vectors\n - timetable\n - scalar missing value.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">Invalid binary operator input for eventfilter. Both operands must be eventfilter objects.</entry>
    <entry key="EventTimeTypeFilterError">Subscripting into a timetable with ''{0}'' row times using an event filter and ''{1}'' event times is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelFilterError">Comparison between the event labels variable ''{0}'' and the event filter value failed.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelTypeMismatch">Event variable ''{0}'' has type ''{1}'' and the event filter value has type ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTime">Event labels variable must not be a datetime, duration, or calendarDuration variable. To filter timetable events based on the attached event table's rowtimes, use the timetable as the input to eventfilter first.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableChar">Creating an event filter from a char matrix is not supported. Use a string array instead.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableSize">To create an event filter for multiple event label values, the values must be a non-empty column vector.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTabular">Event labels variable must not be a table variable.</entry>
    <entry key="NegationUnsupported">Event filters do not support the negation operator (~).</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">Subscripting using an event filter is only supported for selecting rows of a timetable that has an attached event table.</entry>
<!-- ui strings -->
    <entry key="UIStringDispEventLabelsVariable">&lt;Event Labels Variable&gt;</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
