<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rsccat locale="en_US" product="MATLAB" version="1.0">
    <message>
        <entry key="InvalidArgument">Invalid argument "{0}".</entry>  
        <entry key="InvalidComponent">Unable to find "{0}". Check whether "{1}" is the correct location for "{0}" and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidExample">Unable to find "{0}". Check the example name and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidHostName">Unable to download example. Specified MATLAB web documentation location "{0}" is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableDownload">Unable to download - {0}. Check your internet connection or change your Help preferences to view the locally installed documentation.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidWorkDir">Argument must be the path to an existing folder or to the folder to create.</entry>  
        <entry key="InvalidSupportingFile">Unable to find "{0}". Make sure that the product containing the example is installed and that the specified file is not a folder, project file, or the main example file.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidWebExample">Unable to find "{0}". Verify the example name and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidInstalledExample">Unable to find "{0}". Check that the documentation for the product containing this example file is installed or change your "Documentation Location" preference to open the documentation on the web.</entry>
        <entry key="SupportingFileInSubfolder">Unable to open "{0}". Specifying a supporting file in a subfolder is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="ExampleNotFound">Example "{0}" not found in "{1}".</entry>  
        <entry key="InvalidConfiguration">openExample is not supported in this configuration.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDirectory">Folder argument must be a character vector.</entry>
        <entry key="EmptyDirectory">Folder argument must not be empty.</entry>
        <entry key="PathNotValid">Unable to create the example folder because the default folder name contains characters that are not supported. Specify a different folder to the copy the example into.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableCreateWorkDir">Unable to create a new copy of example folder "{0}". Delete "{0}" or check the write permissions of the parent folder.</entry>  
        <entry key="UnsupportedDirectoryName">Unable to create the example folder because the default folder name contains characters that are not supported. To open the example, use the openExample function and specify a different folder to copy the example into. For example, copy the example into a temporary folder on your system: openExample("{0}","workDir",tempdir)</entry>
        <entry key="FunctionInMultipleExamples">''{0}'' is used in the following examples:{1}</entry>
        <entry key="FunctionInSingleExample">''{0}'' is used in {1}.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
