<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2017-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <!-- Table only messages -->
        <entry key="GroupVariablesTableSubscript">Invalid grouping variables.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupVariablesFunctionHandle">Grouping variables function handle must return a logical scalar.</entry>
        <!-- Matrix only messages -->
        <entry key="FirstInputSize">First argument must be a vector, matrix, cell array containing column vectors, table, or timetable.</entry>
        <!-- Common messages -->
        <entry key="GroupBinsEmpty">Invalid binning scheme.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsVarsDiffSize">The number of binning schemes must be compatible with the number of grouping variables.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsNoGroupVars">Binning scheme is not supported when grouping variable is empty.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsError">Unable to apply binning method ''{0}'' to grouping variable ''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsErrorUnnamed">Unable to apply binning method to grouping variable ''{0}''.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsScalarExpand">Unable to apply binning method to all grouping variables. Use a cell array or string array to specify a binning method for each grouping variable, with 'none' to indicate no binning.</entry>
        <entry key="ParseFlags">Parameter name must be ''IncludeMissingGroups'', ''IncludeEmptyGroups'', or ''IncludedEdge''.</entry>
        <entry key="KeyWithoutValue">Incorrect number of input arguments. Parameter names and values must occur in pairs.</entry>
        <entry key="IncludedEdgeNoGroupBins">''IncludedEdge'' is only supported when binning scheme is specified.</entry>
        <!-- Code generation messages -->
        <entry key="CodegenConstGroupVariables">Grouping variables must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstGroupBins">When multiple binning methods are provided, the number of columns of the first input must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclNan">''IncludeMissingGroups'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclEmpty">''IncludeEmptyGroups'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclEdge">''IncludedEdge'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenGroupBinsNotSupported">Binning methods are not supported for datetime or duration data for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenGroupBinsMustBeConst">When the binning method is a character vector, string, or cell array of character vectors, it must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenCellstrInput">Cell arrays of character vectors are not supported as the first input argument for code generation.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
