<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2017-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <!-- Table only messages -->
        <entry key="ApplyDataVarsError">Unable to apply method ''{0}'' to data variable {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupVariablesTableSubscript">Invalid grouping variables.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupVariablesFunctionHandle">Grouping variables function handle must return a logical scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="DataVariablesTableSubscript">Invalid data variables.</entry>
        <entry key="DataVariablesFunctionHandle">Data variables function handle must return a logical scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="DataVariablesCellNumElements">Number of elements in each data variables cell must be the same or 1.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMethodOutputTable">Method must return one array whose first dimension has length 1 for each data group.</entry>
        <!-- Matrix only messages -->
        <entry key="FirstInputSize">First argument must be a vector, matrix, cell array, table, or timetable.</entry>
        <entry key="FirstInputSizeCell">When the first argument is a cell array, each cell element must contain matrices with the same number of columns or a single vector.</entry>
        <entry key="FirstInputSizeCellRows">When the first argument is a cell array, each cell element must contain matrices with the same number of rows.</entry>
        <entry key="FirstSecondMismatchSize">Grouping variables and data matrix must have same number of rows.</entry>
        <entry key="SecondInputType">Grouping variable cannot be specified as a function handle.</entry>
        <entry key="ApplyDataVecsError">Unable to apply method ''{0}'' to data column {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="MustSpecifyMethod">Must specify a method when first argument is a vector or matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="StatsCattable">Unable to concatenate results from applying specified methods to data columns.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMethodOutputArray">Method must return a scalar per group.</entry>
        <!-- Common messages -->
        <entry key="GroupBinsEmpty">Invalid binning scheme.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsVarsDiffSize">The number of binning schemes must be compatible with the number of grouping variables.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsNoGroupVars">Binning scheme is not supported when grouping variable is empty.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsError">Unable to apply binning method ''{0}'' to grouping variable ''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsErrorUnnamed">Unable to apply binning method to grouping variable ''{0}''.</entry>
        <entry key="GroupBinsScalarExpand">Unable to apply binning method to all grouping variables. Use a cell array or string array to specify a binning method for each grouping variable, with 'none' to indicate no binning.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMethodOption">Method must be a valid name, a function handle, or a cell array containing valid methods.</entry>
        <entry key="ParseFlags">Parameter name must be ''IncludeMissingGroups'', ''IncludeEmptyGroups'', or ''IncludedEdge''.</entry>
        <entry key="KeyWithoutValue">Incorrect number of input arguments. Parameter names and values must occur in pairs.</entry>
        <entry key="IncludedEdgeNoGroupBins">''IncludedEdge'' is only supported when binning scheme is specified.</entry>
        <entry key="MedianMethodWithChar">Character array data is not supported for the ''median'' method.</entry>
        <entry key="NumUniqueWithNonColumn">Data variable must be column vector for the ''numunique'' method.</entry>
        <!-- Code generation messages -->
        <entry key="CodegenConstGroupVariables">Grouping variables must be constant for code generation when the first input argument is a table.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenGroupBinsNotSupported"> Binning scheme for datetime or duration data is not supported for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclNan">''IncludeMissingGroups'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclEmpty">''IncludeEmptyGroups'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstInclEdge">''IncludedEdge'' value must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenVarsizeCell">Variable-sized cell array inputs are not supported for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenFuncHandleDataVars">Function handle data variables are not supported for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenCellstrInput">Cell arrays of characters are not supported as the first input argument for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstMethod">Computation method must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenConstDataVars">Data variables must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenGroupBinsMustBeConst">When the binning method is a character vector, string, or cell array of character vectors, it must be constant for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenMethodCantReturnND">Computation methods returning an N-dimensional output are not supported for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenMethodCantReturnSparse">Computation methods returning a sparse output are not supported for code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenMethodCantReturnCell">Computation methods returning cell arrays are not supported for code generation.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
