<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <entry key="InvalidBoundsForNontabularInputs">Tabular bounds are only supported when the first input is tabular.</entry>
        <entry key="IncompatibleSizes">Lower and upper bounds must have compatible sizes with the input array or the corresponding variables in the input table.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidInputTypeForNVArguments">Name-value argument ''DataVariables'' is supported only for tabular input data.</entry>
        <entry key="DataVariablesTableSubscript">''DataVariables'' value must be a variable name, a vector of variable names, variable indices, logical values, a pattern, a function handle, or a vartype subscript.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTabularBoundsFirstInput">Variable names in the tabular bounds must be present in the input table.</entry>
        <entry key="UnknownParameterForAllbetween" context="error">Parameter name must be ''DataVariables''.</entry>
        <entry key="UnknownParameter">Parameter name must be ''DataVariables'' or ''OutputFormat''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTabularBoundsWithDataVars">Variable names specified by ''DataVariables'' must match variable names in tabular bounds.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTabularBounds">Variable names in tabular lower and upper bounds must match.</entry>
        <entry key="TabularBoundsRequired">Lower and upper bounds must be one-row tables if the table variables to operate on have mixed data types.</entry>
        <entry key="ArgNameValueMismatch">Incorrect number of input arguments. Each parameter name must be followed by a corresponding value.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidIntervalType">Interval type must be 'open', 'closed', 'openright', 'openleft', 'closedright', or 'closedleft'.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidObjects">Input data must be an object that supports the class methods ''lt'' and ''le''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTabularOutputFormat">Specifying ''OutputFormat'' as 'tabular' is only supported for tabular input data.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidOutputFormat">''OutputFormat'' value must be ''logical'' or ''tabular''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTableVars">When the input data or bounds contain multi-column table variables or nested table variables, the value of ''OutputFormat'' must be ''tabular''.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTableVarsForAllbetween" context="error">Input data or bounds containing multi-column table variables or nested table variables are not supported.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
