<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="AssociatedHostTerminated">MATLABPyHost process with process ID ''{0}'' has been terminated because Python call was interrupted.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNumArgs">Invalid number of arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidKey">Invalid input ''{0}''. Key must be ''Version'' or ''ExecutionMode''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPyHostNamespace">Invalid input ''{0}''. Value for ''Namespace'' must be a valid MATLAB Identifier.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidExecutionMode">Invalid input ''{0}''. Value for ''ExecutionMode'' must be ''InProcess'' or ''OutOfProcess''.</entry>
    <entry key="VersionAndModeExpected">''Version'' and ''ExecutionMode'' parameters are expected.</entry>
    <entry key="TerminateNotSupported">Termination not supported for InProcess execution mode.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonLoaded">Python is loaded. The environment cannot be changed while the interpreter is running. To change the environment, call ''terminate(pyenv)'' then call ''pyenv''.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonLoadedInOOP">Python loaded in ''OutOfProcess'' mode. To change the ''ExecutionMode'' to ''InProcess'', restart MATLAB, and then call ''pyenv''.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonLoadedInProcess">Python is loaded. The environment cannot be changed in this MATLAB session. To change the environment, restart MATLAB, and then call ''pyenv''.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonTerminatedReloadNotSupported">Python process is terminated and cannot be called in this MATLAB session. To call Python functions, restart MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonTerminated">Python process terminated unexpectedly. To restart the Python interpreter, first call "terminate(pyenv)" and then call a Python function.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonEnvironmentLoadNotSupported">Unable to load PythonEnvironment object. Saving (serializing) PythonEnvironment into a MAT-file is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonSharedLibNotFound">Cannot find shared library for specified Python version. Python must be built with a shared library, and the library must be on the search path.</entry>
    <entry key="IncorrectPythonHomePath">Supported Python executable not found at PYTHONHOME set to ''{0}''.\nSet PYTHONHOME to a location of a supported Python executable, or unset it using ''unsetenv("PYTHONHOME")''.</entry>
    <entry key="ConflictingPythonHome">PYTHONHOME set to ''{0}'' does not match location set by pyenv.\nSet PYTHONHOME to same location set by pyenv, or unset it using ''unsetenv("PYTHONHOME")''.</entry>
    <entry key="PythonWindowsAppStoreInstallNotSupported">Python installation from Microsoft Store is not supported. Use a different Python installation.</entry>
    <entry key="NoValidPythonFound">No supported Python version found.\n&lt;a href="matlab: helpview(strcat(docroot, '/matlab/matlab_external/matlab_external.map'),''warning_Pyenv_NoValidPythonFound'')"&gt;Related documentation&lt;/a&gt;</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
