<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2017-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="Column">Column {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSourceTable">'SourceTable' must be a table, timetable, cell vector of tables, or cell vector of timetables.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayVariablesTablesOnly">To use 'DisplayVariables', plot input must be a table or timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDisplayVariables">''{0}'' is not a variable of the input table or timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDisplayVariablesIndices">'DisplayVariables', when specified as an array of numeric indices, must be positive integers less than or equal to {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayVariablesEmptyCells">'DisplayVariables' must not contain empty cells.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayVariablesInvalidType">'DisplayVariables' must be a string array, numeric array, logical array, cell array of character vectors, cell array of numeric arrays, or cell array of text arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="UnplottableDisplayVariables">'DisplayVariables' must specify variables that are numeric, logical, datetime, duration, or categorical arrays, or are themselves tables or timetables, with at least one column.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDisplayLabels">'DisplayLabels' value must either be a string array, or a cell array containing character vectors or numeric vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="LogicalArraySize">When specifying {0} as a logical array, its length must be equal to {1,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="XLimitsNonIncreasing">'XLimits' value must contain monotonically increasing values.</entry>
    <entry key="XVariableTablesOnly">To use 'XVariable', plot input must be a table or multiple tables.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidXVariable">To use 'XVariable', specify a variable of the input table.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLogicalXVariable">If the value of 'XVariable' is a logical array, then it must contain one true element.</entry>
    <entry key="XVariableInvalidType">'XVariable' value must be a character vector, a string scalar, a positive integer, or a logical array with one true element.</entry>
    <entry key="UnplottableXVariable">'XVariable' value must specify a table variable that is a numeric, logical, datetime, or duration column vector.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLineProperties">'LineProperties' value must have the same length as the number of axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAxesProperties">'AxesProperties' value must have the same length as the number of axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidColorMatrix">'Color' value must either be a 1-by-3 row vector or a N-by-3 matrix where N is the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMarkerFaceColorMatrix">'MarkerFaceColor' value must either be a 1-by-3 row vector or a N-by-3 matrix where N is the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMarkerEdgeColorMatrix">'MarkerEdgeColor' value must either be a 1-by-3 row vector or a N-by-3 matrix where N is the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLineStyleArray">'LineStyle' value must be either a character vector or a cell array of character vectors with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLineWidthArray">'LineWidth' value must be either a scalar or a vector with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMarkerStyleArray">'Marker' value must be either a character vector or a cell array of character vectors with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMarkerSizeArray">'MarkerSize' value must be either a scalar or a vector with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPlotTypeArray">'PlotType' value must be either a character vector or a cell array of character vectors with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleTableInput">Unable to specify 'SourceTable' value when the 'XData' and 'YData' values are nonempty.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleArrayInput">Unable to specify 'XData' and 'YData' values when the 'SourceTable' value is nonempty.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidParent">Parent container must be a figure, uipanel, or uitab.</entry>
    <entry key="DeletedParent">Parent container is a deleted graphics object.</entry>
    <entry key="LegendLabelsInvalidType">'LegendLabels' value must be a string array or cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="LegendLabelsInvalidSize">'LegendLabels' value must be a vector with length equal to the number of plots in the axes.</entry>
    <entry key="SourceTableLegendLabelsInvalidSize">'LegendLabels' value must be a vector with length less than or equal to the number of source tables.</entry>
    <entry key="OverlaidNestedTable">Unable to plot variables that are nested tables or timetables using the same axes as the other variables.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoIncompatibleOverlaidTypes">Table variables ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' cannot be plotted in the same axes because they have incompatible types.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreeIncompatibleOverlaidTypes">Table variables ''{0}'', ''{1}'', and ''{2}'' cannot be plotted in the same axes because they have incompatible types.</entry>
    <entry key="MoreIncompatibleOverlaidTypes">Table variables ''{0}'', ''{1}'', and {2,number,integer} others cannot be plotted in the same axes because they have incompatible types.</entry>
    <entry key="XDataYDataMismatch">X must have length equal to the number of rows in Y.</entry>
    <entry key="OneVariableNotShown">{0} not shown.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoVariablesNotShown">{0} and {1} not shown.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreeVariablesNotShown">{0}, {1}, and 1 more variable not shown.</entry>
    <entry key="MoreVariablesNotShown">{0}, {1}, and {2,number,integer} more variables not shown.</entry>
    <!--Multiple tables/timetables-->
    <entry key="InvalidCellData">Cell array source data must contain tables or timetables.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCellDataArray">Cell array source data must be a vector.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleTableTypes">Multiple table or timetable data must be all tables, all timetables, or all eventtables.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleTimetableRowTimeTypes">Multiple timetable data must have either all duration row times or all datetime row times.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayVariablesInvalidTypeMultiTable">When plotting multiple tables or timetables, 'DisplayVariables' must be a string array, cell array of character vectors, or cell array of text arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidXVariableMultiTable">Variable ''{0}'' does not exist in table {1}. To use 'XVariable', specify a single variable name common to all input tables or a vector of variable names, one for each input table.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidXVariableLengthMultiTable">Wrong number of x-variables: {0} provided, but expected {1}. 'XVariable' must specify a single variable name common to all input tables or a vector of variable names, one for each input table.</entry>
    <entry key="XVariableIncompatibleTypes">'XVariable' value must specify a table variable that is the same type for all tables.</entry>
    <entry key="XVariableInvalidTypeMultiTable">'XVariable' value must be a character vector, a string array, or a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="OneInvalidCombinedDisplayVariable">All ''{0}'' variables could not be plotted in the same axes because they do not have compatible types across input tables. Set CombineMatchingNames to false to plot incompatible variables on separate axes.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoInvalidCombinedDisplayVariables">All ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' variables could not be plotted in the same axes because they do not have compatible types across input tables. Set CombineMatchingNames to false to plot incompatible variables on separate axes.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreeInvalidCombinedDisplayVariables">All ''{0}'', ''{1}'', and ''{2}'' variables could not be plotted in the same axes because they do not have compatible types across input tables. Set CombineMatchingNames to false to plot incompatible variables on separate axes.</entry>
    <entry key="MoreInvalidCombinedDisplayVariables">All ''{0}'', ''{1}'', and {2,number,integer} more variables could not be plotted in the same axes because they do not have compatible types across input tables. Set CombineMatchingNames to false to plot incompatible variables on separate axes.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCombineMatchingNames">CombineMatchingNames must be a logical scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDisplayVariablesMultiTable">''{0}'' is not a variable of any input table or timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompatibleOverlaidTypesMultiTable">Table {0,number,integer} variables {1} cannot be plotted in the same axes because they have incompatible types.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidXVariableRemoved">Invalid XVariable removed. {0}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
