<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="zh_CN" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="EventTableInput">Creating an event filter from an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then create the event filter from the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="EventFilterOnEventTable">Using an event filter as a subscript on an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then subscript into the timetable using the event filter.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsAttached">Creating an event filter for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To create an event filter from this timetable, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsForSubscripting">Using an event filter as a subscript for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To subscript this timetable with an event filter, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventLabelsForSubscripting">To subscript into a timetable using an event filter created using an event label value, the event table attached to the timetable must have the EventLabelsVariable property set.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEventFilterInput">eventfilter 的输入无效。输入必须为以下各项之一:\n - 字符串向量、字符向量或字符向量元胞数组\n - 时间表\n - 标量缺失值。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">eventfilter 的二元运算符输入无效。两个操作数都必须为 eventfilter 对象。</entry>
    <entry key="EventTimeTypeFilterError">不支持使用事件过滤器和 ''{1}'' 事件时间通过下标对具有 ''{0}'' 行时间的时间表进行索引。</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelFilterError">Comparison between the event labels variable ''{0}'' and the event filter value failed.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelTypeMismatch">事件变量 ''{0}'' 的类型为 ''{1}''，事件过滤器值的类型为 ''{2}''。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTime">事件标签变量不能为 datetime、duration 或 calendarDuration 变量。要根据附加的事件表的行时间过滤时间表事件，请先将时间表用作 eventfilter 的输入。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableChar">不支持从字符矩阵创建事件过滤器。请改用字符串数组。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableSize">要为多个事件标签值创建一个事件过滤器，这些值必须为非空列向量。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTabular">事件标签变量不能为表变量。</entry>
    <entry key="NegationUnsupported">事件过滤器不支持求反运算符(~)。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">仅在选择附有事件表的时间表行时，才支持使用事件过滤器标注下标。</entry>
    <entry key="UIStringDispEventLabelsVariable">&lt;事件标签变量&gt;</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
