<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="shared_tracking" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidObjectAttributesCodegen">When generating code for a {0}, the ObjectAttributes of objectDetection must be a struct or a struct in a cell.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilter">Expected filter to be a tracking filter.\n{0} is incompatible with {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedAttributes">ObjectAttributes must be a struct.</entry>
    <entry key="NumAttributes">The ObjectAttributes of the input track passed to ''{0}'' contain more attributes than the tracker {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="PredictBeforeUpdate">You must update the tracker at least once before calling ''{0}''. Use isLocked() to check if the tracker has been updated.</entry>
    <entry key="ExpectedFilter">The tracker is configured to use a {0} filter, but no filter was provided in  the call to ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="UndefinedSampleDetection">The first call to ''step'' must have at least one detection.</entry>
    <entry key="UndefinedFilter">A tracking filter must be defined for code generation.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLogicType">The logic of the input track passed to ''{0}'' is incompatible with the logic type used by the tracker.</entry>
    <entry key="TrackIDNotFound">There is no track with a TrackID={0} in the tracks list.</entry>
    <entry key="MaxNumTracksReached">Failed to initiate a new track because {0} was reached.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDetectionSensorIndex">Detection SensorIndex is not one of the ''MaxNumSensors'' unique values already used with this tracker.</entry>
    <entry key="DetectionTimeMismatch">The detection timestamp must be greater than the previous time value in the call for {0} and less than or equal to the current time value in the call for {0}.</entry> 
    <entry key="OOSMError">When setting the ''{0}'' property to ''{1}'', the detection timestamps must be greater than the previous timestamp in the call to ''{2}'' and less than or equal to the current timestamp in the call to ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="exceedsMaxNumDetections">The number of detections in the input exceeds ''MaxNumDetections''</entry>
    <entry key="OddNameValuePairs">Expected Name-Value pairs.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSyncedTracks">Synced tracks must be of the same class.</entry>
    <entry key="VarsizeDetsWithoutVarsizedFilter">Filters of type {0} do not support variable sized detections. Check the documentation for a list of filters that support variable-sized detections in the tracker or make sure that all the detectionss are the same size.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>