<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="InvalidYData">YData must be a numeric vector.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidXYData">The positional grouping variable and sample data must be vectors of the same length, matrices of the same size, or a combination of a vector and a matrix where the length of the vector matches either the number of columns or rows of the matrix.</entry>
    <entry key="NoPDFWithData">''EvaluationPoints'' and ''DensityValues'' are not supported if sample data is specified.</entry>
    <entry key="BothPDFPartsNeeded">''EvaluationPoints'' and ''DensityValues'' must both be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="BadXData">XData must be of type numeric or categorical.</entry>
    <entry key="BadXDataYData">XData and YData must be vectors of the same length.</entry>
    <entry key="BadEvalPtsAndDensity">EvaluationPoints and DensityValues must have the same size.</entry>
    <entry key="ColGrpsNotWithTables">You cannot specify ''GroupByColor'' with table input.</entry>
    <entry key="ColGrpsNotWithPDFs">You cannot specify ''GroupByColor'' when you specify ''EvaluationPoints'' and ''DensityValues''.</entry>
    <entry key="ColGrpsOnlyWithYvec">To specify ''GroupByColor'', specify the positional grouping variable and sample data arguments as vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="BadColGroupVectorY">''GroupByColor'' value must be a vector of the same length as the sample data argument.</entry>    
    <entry key="EvalPtsModeManualBadXNumGroups">When EvaluationPointsMode is ''manual'', the number of groups in XData must match the number of columns in EvaluationPoints.</entry>
    <entry key="DensValMissingData">When EvaluationPointsMode is ''manual'' and DensityValuesMode is ''auto'', both XData and YData must be provided.</entry>
    <entry key="DensValModeManualEvalPtsAutoMissingData">When EvaluationPointsMode is ''auto'' and DensityValuesMode is ''manual'', both XData and YData must be provided.</entry>
    <entry key="OrientationYYAxis">Changing the ''Orientation'' property is not supported when the violin plot has categorical values in multiple y-axes.</entry>
    <entry key="OrientationMixedType">Changing the ''Orientation'' property is not supported when the violin plot has categorical values and the axes contains charts of different types.</entry>
    
    <!-- Datatip fields -->
    <entry key="Position" translate="false" note="this is the property name">XData</entry>
    <entry key="EvalPt">Evaluation Point</entry>
    <entry key="DensVal">Density Value</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>