<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014-2018 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
      <!--getThingSpeakURL -->
      <entry key="URLNotAString">URL must be a string.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidChannelID">Channel ID must be a  positive integer.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidFields">''Fields'' value must be a scalar or a 1-by-n numeric vector of positive integers with values between 1 and 8.</entry>
      <entry key="nonUniqueFields">''Fields'' value must be a vector of unique integers.</entry>
      
	  <!-- thingSpeakRead -->
      <entry key="invalidSecondParam">Second argument must be a string representing a valid parameter name.</entry>
      <!-- <entry key="unrecognizedParameter">{0}</entry> -->
      <entry key="missingValue">Incorrect number of input arguments. Each parameter name must be followed by a corresponding value.</entry>

      <entry key="invalidReadAPIKey">''ReadKey'' value must be a string.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidReadAPIKeySpace">''ReadKey'' value must not contain any spaces.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNumPoints">''NumPoints'' value must be a positive integer less than or equal to 8000.</entry>
	  <entry key="invalidNumDays">''NumDays'' value must be a positive integer.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidNumMinutes">''NumMinutes'' value must be a positive integer.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidDateRange">''DateRange'' value must be a 1-by-2  vector of datetime values.</entry>
      <entry key="badStartEnd">''DateRange'' value must have an end date and time later than the start date and time.</entry>
      <entry key="timeZonesDontMatch">'Time zone of start datetime and end datetime must match.'</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamDateRangeWithNumPoints">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumPoints'' or ''DateRange''</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamNumDaysWithNumPoints">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumPoints'' or ''NumDays''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamNumMinsWithNumPoints">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumPoints'' or ''NumMinutes''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamDateRangeWithNumDays">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''DateRange'' or ''NumDays''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamNumMinsWithNumDays">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumMinutes'' or ''NumDays''.</entry>
	  <entry key="invalidParamDateRangeWithNumMinutes">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumMinutes'' or ''DateRange''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamNumDaysWithNumMinutes">Invalid input combination. Specify either ''NumMinutes'' or ''NumDays''.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidLocation">''Location'' value must be either 0 (false) or 1 (true)</entry>
      <entry key="invalidTimeout">''Timeout'' value has to be a finite number greater than 0'</entry>
      <entry key="invalidOutputFormat">''OutputFormat'' value must be either ''matrix'', ''table'' or ''timetable''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidFieldBounds">Specified Field is not available on the channel. Refer to the FieldIDs in the channel information for valid field IDs.</entry>
      <entry key="improperJSON">Channel and field data missing from JSON. Ensure that the URL in the diagnostic information returns valid JSON.</entry>
      <entry key="unableToParseChannelInfo">Cannot parse channel information returned by ThingSpeak. Ensure that the server installation is working correctly.</entry>
      <entry key="incorrectKey">Specify a valid read API key, or make the channel public to avoid specifying the read API key.</entry>    
      <entry key="connectionTimeOut">Connection to the ThingSpeak server has timed out. Specify a ''Timeout'' value to increase the read timeout period.</entry>
      <entry key="unknownHost">Unable to resolve hostname or IP address {0}. Specify a valid URL.</entry>      
      <entry key="numPointsUnmet">'Unable to read {0} points as requested. Only {1} points available in the channel.</entry>      
      <entry key="nonNumericDataFound">Non-numeric data was found. This could mean that you are attempting to retrieve data from a channel or field that has non-numeric points. Set ''OutputFormat'' property to ''table'' or ''timetable'' to read non-numeric data.</entry>
      <entry key="missingValuesInput">Unable to find data. Specify data to write to fields using ''Values''.</entry>
      <entry key="missingAuthentication">Unable to write data to a channel. Specify ''WriteKey'' value as a string containing the write API Key.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidWriteAPIKey">''WriteKey'' value must be a string.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidWriteAPIKeySpace">''WriteKey'' value must not contain any spaces.</entry>       
      <entry key="timetableIncorrectTime">Values provided as ''Timetable'' must contain time as datetime value.</entry>      
	  <entry key="missingData">No data provided to write to ThingSpeak. Specify either ''Values'' or ''Locations''.</entry>      
      <entry key="unrecognizedParameter">Second input must be either a named parameter or data specified as numeric scalars or arrays or cell arrays or tables.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidParamWithValues">''Values'' must be a scalar, a 1-by-n numeric vector, or a cell array and must have the same dimensions as the ''Fields'' value.</entry>      
      <entry key="tooManyValues">''Values'' must have a maximum of 9 elements, including the timestamp.</entry>
      <entry key="tooManyValuesTimeTable">''Values'' must have a maximum of 8 elements.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidParamWithLocation">''Locations'' value must be specified as [latitude, longitude, altitude]. Specify latitude and longitude in degrees between [-90, 90] and altitude in meters.</entry>      
      <entry key="multipleTStampsLT">Timestamps have been provided through two arguments. Use either ''Location'' or ''Timestamps'' to specify timestamps.</entry>
      <entry key="multipleTStampsLV">Timestamps have been provided through two arguments. Use either ''Location'' or ''Values'' to specify timestamps.</entry>      
      <entry key="multipleTStamps">Timestamps have been provided through two arguments. Use either ''Values'' or ''Timestamps'' to specify timestamps.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidTimeFormat">''Timestamps'' value must contain Year, Day, Month, Hour, Minute, and Second.</entry>
      <entry key="incorrectInputsWithValues">Nonnumeric values or heterogeneous datatype vectors must be a cell array.</entry>
      <entry key="tooManyColumnsTable">Number of columns in the table must be less than or equal to 8, or if the first column contains ''Timestamps'' value, the number of columns must be less than or equal to 9.</entry>      
      <entry key="tooManyColumnsTimeTable">Number of columns in the timetable must be less than or equal to 8.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidCellArray">Data must be a 1-D cell array.</entry>
      <entry key="emptyData">Data provided contains only NaN values.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidParamWithBatchValues">''Values'' value must be an array or a table.</entry>      
      <entry key="tooManyColumnsArray">Number of columns in the array must be less than or equal to 8.</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidParamSizeWithBatchValuesFields">Number of columns in ''Values'' must be equal to the number of fields specified.</entry>      
      <entry key="unequalNumTimestamps">Number of elements in ''Timestamps'' value must be equal to the number of rows of ''Values'' value.</entry> 
      <entry key="tooManyColsTimeStamps">''TimeStamps'' value should contain a single column.</entry>      
      <entry key="missingArrayBatchTimestamps">Timestamps for data values being written must be specified as datetime values. Use ''Timestamps'' to specify datetime values.</entry>       
      <entry key="missingTableBatchTimestamps">Missing timestamps. Either specify timestamps in the first column, or specify datetime values using ''Timestamps''.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidParamWithBatchLocation">''Locations'' value must be specified as [latitude, longitude, altitude]. Specify latitude and longitude in degrees between [-90, 90] and altitude in meters.</entry>
      <entry key="multipleTimeBatchLocation">Timestamps have been provided through two arguments. Use either ''Location'' or ''Timestamps'' to specify timestamps.</entry>
      <entry key="badSizeBatchLocation">''Locations'' value must have a maximum of three columns and the same number of rows as that of ''Values'' or ''Timestamps''.</entry>
      <entry key="incompleteBatchLocation">''Locations'' value must have at least two columns specified as [latitude, longitude].</entry>      
      <entry key="invalidServerResponse">Server returned an invalid response.</entry>      
      <entry key="updateErrorResponse">Server returned an error. Check Channel ID, write API key and wait for 15 seconds between updates.</entry>
      <entry key="urlReadFailed">Unable to fulfill request. Make sure the ChannelID and the corresponding Write API Key are correct. If you just successfully wrote data to your channel, wait for 15 seconds before writing data again.</entry>
      <entry key="incorrectAPIKey">Incorrect write API key. Make sure the Channel ID and the corresponding write API key are correct.</entry>
      <entry key="toomanyRequests">Requests are too frequent. For further information, see &lt;a href=\"matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot, 'matlab', 'helptargets.map'), 'THINGSPEAK_TSWRITE_LIMITATIONS')\"&gt;Limitations&lt;/a&gt; in the documentation.</entry>
      <entry key="resourceNotFound">Unable to find resource. Check the URL, channel ID and write API key.</entry>
      <entry key="unsupportedURL">URL is incorrectly formed, or the requested feature is not supported in this version of ThingSpeak.</entry>
      
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  addons supportpackage
-->
