<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2023 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Slvnv">
    <message>
        <entry key="InputMustBeCellOfStrings">Input must be a cell array of strings or character vectors.</entry>
        <entry key="NewSysAlreadyExists">Block named ''{0}'' already exists.</entry>
        <entry key="ErrorOccurredOnSpecBlockCreation">Unable to create new block named ''{0}''.</entry>
        <entry key="NoDefaultRowInAssumptionTable">The Assumptions Table does not support default rows.</entry>
        <entry key="NoActionOnMultiLineLogicRow">Setting actions in multiple line logic rows is not supported. This change attempt has been ignored.</entry>
        <entry key="SetPostconditionNotAllowed">Setting postconditions in multiple line logic rows is not supported. This change attempt has been ignored.</entry>
        <entry key="SetActionsNotAllowed">Setting actions on row ''{0}'' is not supported. This change attempt has been ignored.</entry>
        <entry key="SetPreconditionNotAllowed">Setting preconditions on row ''{0}'' is not supported. This change attempt has been ignored.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidComplexityEnum">'Complexity' can be set to 'On', 'Off' or 'Inherited' only.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidScopeEnum">'Scope' must be 'Local', 'Input', 'Output', 'Constant', or 'Parameter'.</entry>
        <entry key="HasDefaultRow">Appending a row after a default row at this hierarchy is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotAddRowToDependentHierarchy">Appending a child row to a dependent hierarchy is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotAddDefaultRowToAssumptionTable">Adding a default row to an Assumptions Table is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotDeleteLastRow">Unable to delete row. The table must contain at least one row.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidRow">Row must be a valid RequirementRow or AssumptionRow object.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidInputToFind">Invalid input. Input must be a handle or path of a model or subsystem.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidInputToCreate">Invalid optional input. Input can be a char vector or a scalar string.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidNumberOfPreconditionsOrPostconditions">Assumptions have only one precondition and postcondition column.</entry>
        <entry key="SaveToPreviousVersion">Requirements Table block ''{0}'' is not supported in versions prior to R2022a and will be deleted.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidDesignOutputProperty">'isDesignOutput' is invalid for this data type. Use 'isDesignOutput' only when the 'Scope' property is 'Input'.</entry>
        <entry key="ReqTablenewArgs">Too many input or output arguments.</entry>
        <entry key="InputsToRTnew">Input argument for slreq.modeling.create must be a string scalar or character vector.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotAddDefaultRowToMLLHierarchy">Adding a default requirement to a semantic requirement is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotChangeMLLEvaluation">Changing the child evaluation of a semantic requirement is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotChangeMLLChildEvaluation">Changing the child evaluation of a child requirement of a semantic requirement is not supported.</entry>


    </message>
</rsccat>
