<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="MATFileNotFound">MAT 파일 {0}을(를) 읽을 수 없습니다.\n파일 경로를 확인하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileCorruptMatFile">Unable to read MAT-file {0}.\nFile may be corrupt.</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileGeneralFileNameErr">Diagnostic reported while reading file ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileInvTimeVectorIncr">Time values must be monotonically non-decreasing</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileInvTimeseries">Invalid timeseries object. The most common cause for this is empty timeseries objects. To correct this problem, add at least 1 sample to this timeseries.</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileNonInt32EnumDataError">From File 블록을 사용하여 불러온 열거형 데이터는 기본 유형이 int32 또는 Simulink.IntEnumType이어야 합니다</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileNonFiniteDataErr">파일 ''{0}''에서 읽어오는 중 non-finite 데이터, Nan, Inf 또는 -Inf가 발견되었습니다</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileReadingErr">Simulink does not support loading the input data in file ''{0}''. Simulink can only load two-dimensional arrays or timeseries objects. The array must consist of one-dimensional, double, noncomplex samples. To load data having a different type, complexity, or dimension, use a timeseries object. For either an array or a timeseries object, at least one sample point is necessary.</entry>
    <entry key="FromFileReadingPre73Err">Simulink does not support loading the input data in file ''{0}''. For data saved using MAT file versions prior to 7.3, Simulink can only load two-dimensional arrays consisting of one-dimensional, double, noncomplex samples. To load data of any other type, complexity or dimension, use a timeseries object and save the file using MAT file version 7.3 or later. For example, use: ''save file_name -v7.3 timeseries_object''.</entry>
    <entry key="RTWFromFileInconsistentComplexity">MAT 파일 ''{0}''에서 신호의 실수/복소수 여부({1})가 신호에 대한 예상 실수/복소수 여부({2})와 다릅니다.</entry>
    <entry key="RTWFromFileInconsistentDatatypesEnum">MAT 파일 ''{1}''의 데이터형 ''{0}''이(가) MATLAB에서 지정된 열거형 데이터형과 호환되지 않습니다. MAT 파일 데이터에 현재 클래스 정의에 존재하지 않는 열거형 이름이 포함되어 있거나 적어도 하나의 열거형 값이 현재 클래스 정의에 있는 대응값과 일치하지 않습니다. load(''{2}'') 명령을 사용하고, 데이터를 현재 클래스 정의와 일치하도록 업데이트한 후 MAT 파일을 다시 저장하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="RTWFromFileInconsistentDatatypesFi">MAT 파일 ''{0}''의 고정소수점 데이터형이 필요한 고정소수점 데이터형과 다릅니다.</entry>
    <entry key="RTWFromFileInconsistentDatatypesGeneral">MAT 파일 ''{0}''의 신호 데이터형 ''{1}''이(가) 필요한 신호 데이터형 ''{2}''과(와) 다릅니다.</entry>
    <entry key="RTWFromFileInconsistentDims">MAT 파일 ''{0}''의 신호 차원 {1}이(가) 필요한 신호 차원 {2}과(와) 다릅니다.</entry>
    <entry key="ToFromFileOpenCloseErr">Error opening or closing file ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="ToFileWasTouchedWhileOnPause">Unable to continue logging into file ''{0}'' because it was modified or removed while simulation was on pause.</entry>
    <entry key="ToFileFileNameIsTooLong">File name is too long. Specify a shorter file name.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyFilesError">Too many files are being accessed by the system. Consider the following approaches: reduce the number of To File blocks in your model or close other applications that may access files.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidIndexForMATFileRecord">Invalid read range for the given record within the MAT file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileDirDoesNotExist">The file ''{0}'' is no longer accessible for reading.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
