<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="look1MaxAndMin">Maximum x value must be larger than minimum x value (including quantization).</entry>
    <entry key="look1NotFixPt">The input is not a fixed point data type so the power of two spacing restriction will be ignored.</entry>
    <entry key="look1InvalidLimits">Both upper limits were invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="look1ScaleNotEven">ASSERT: Scaling not even.</entry>
    <entry key="look1DTNotSupport">이 데이터형의 클래스는 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="look1EvenSpacingConversionInputOutOfBounds">Input data is outside the range of its data type. Consider using the Lookup Table Optimizer to convert unevenly spaced lookup tables to use even spacing. </entry>
    <entry key="numInputArg">적어도 2개의 입력 인수를 지정해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="num2fixptNonDoubleVal">num2fixpt requires the first parameter to be double.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTNoArg">첫 번째 입력 인수를 지정해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTInputArg">This model has not been loaded, or the provided handle or model name is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTLibrary">모델 {0}은(는) 라이브러리입니다. </entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTResolve">블록 {3}에서 데이터형 {2}의 {0} 또는 {1}을(를) 확인할 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose0">slDataTypeAndScale() 호출을 찾을 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose1u">다음과 같은 불필요한 slDataTypeAndScale() 호출이 대체되었습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose1">다음과 같은 slDataTypeAndScale() 호출은 불필요하므로 자동으로 대체될 수 있습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slRmDTVerbose2">사용자가 다음과 같은 slDataTypeAndScale() 호출을 검사하여 불필요한지 여부를 판단해야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleNumDTWithAliasOn">slDataTypeAndScale()의 첫 번째 인수 ''{0}''이(가) IsAlias가 true로 설정된 상태에서 완전히 지정된 Simulink.NumericType 객체로 평가됩니다. slDataTypeAndScale()을 이런 방식으로 사용하는 것은 더 이상 지원되지 않습니다. 이 호출을 해당 호출의 첫 번째 인수로 안전하게 대체할 수 있습니다. {1}</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleAliasDT">The first argument ''{0}'' of slDataTypeAndScale() evaluates to a Simulink.AliasType object with a fully specified base type. Such usage of slDataTypeAndScale() is no longer supported. You can safely replace this call with its first argument. {1}</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleUpgrade">이 문제를 포함해 다른 알려진 업그레이드 문제를 위해 모델을 자동으로 업데이트하려면 &lt;a href="matlab:modeladvisor ''{0}''"&gt;이 링크&lt;/a&gt;를 클릭하여 모델 어드바이저를 실행하고 다음 태스크를 실행하십시오: ''{1}''. 또는 스크립트 &lt;a href="matlab:slRemoveDataTypeAndScale(''{2}'')"&gt;slRemoveDataTypeAndScale&lt;/a&gt;을 실행하여 이 문제를 해결할 수도 있습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="slDTnScaleBusDT">The first argument ''{0}'' of slDataTypeAndScale() evaluates to a Simulink.Bus object. Such usage of slDataTypeAndScale() is not valid.</entry>
    <entry key="InvWordLength">Invalid WordLength ''{0}'' specified; the WordLength must be a scalar numeric value that is greater than 0.</entry>
    <entry key="InvFractionLength">유효하지 않은 FractionLength ''{0}''이(가) 지정되었습니다. FractionLength는 정수 스칼라 값이어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="FxDLicenseRequired">Fixed-Point Designer license is required to run the example. Ensure that the product is installed and a license is available.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveDTOModel">Data type override is active on the model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;. This enables you to simulate floating-point behavior regardless of the data types specified on the blocks. To learn how to control this setting, refer to the &lt;a href="matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot,'fixedpoint','fixedpoint.map'), 'dtOverride')"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveMMOModel">Min, max and overflow logging is active on the model &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;. To learn how to control this setting and view collected simulation data, refer to the &lt;a href="matlab:helpview(fullfile(docroot,'fixedpoint','fixedpoint.map'), 'minMaxOverflow')"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveDTOModelNoLinks">Data type override is active on the model ''{0}''. This enables you to simulate floating-point behavior regardless of the data types specified on the blocks. To change this setting, open Fixed-Point Tool. To learn more, refer to the Fixed-Point Designer documentation.</entry>
    <entry key="ActiveMMOModelNoLinks">Min, max and overflow logging is active on the model ''{0}''. To learn how to control this setting and view collected simulation data, refer to the Fixed-Point Designer documentation.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzTopModelSetInNormalMode">모델 &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;은(는) FTZ(0으로 플러시) 동작을 시뮬레이션하도록 구성되었지만, 표준 모드 시뮬레이션을 사용하고 있습니다. FTZ 동작을 관측하려면 가속화된 모드를 사용하여 모델을 시뮬레이션하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzRefModelSetInNormalMode">모델 &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;은(는) FTZ(0으로 플러시) 동작을 시뮬레이션하도록 구성되었지만, 모델의 인스턴스가 표준 모드 시뮬레이션을 사용하고 있습니다. FTZ 동작을 관측하려면 가속화된 모드를 사용하여 시뮬레이션하도록 필요한 모델 인스턴스를 다시 구성하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="ftzLicenseCheckout">모델 &lt;a href="matlab:open_system(''{0}'')"&gt;{0}&lt;/a&gt;은(는) FTZ(0으로 플러시) 동작을 시뮬레이션하도록 구성되었습니다. 이 경우 &lt;a href="matlab:web('https://www.mathworks.com/products/fixed-point-designer.html')"&gt;Fixed-Point Designer&lt;/a&gt;가 필요하지만 라이선스 체크아웃에 실패했습니다.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
