<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="Simulink" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="FunctionToImportMismatch">Functions ''{0}'' do not exist, are undefined, or are not compatible with Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="TypeToImportMismatch">유형 ''{0}''이(가) 존재하지 않거나 Simulink와 호환되지 않습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindOutputFolder">Unable to find the specified output folder ''{0}''. Check your output folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotFindPackageFolder">Unable to find the specified package folder ''{0}''. Check your package folder against current working directory if it is specified with relative path. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableOutputFolder">Output folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify an output folder that is not write-protected. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseUnsuccessful">사용자 지정 코드를 구문 분석하지 못했습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptyParseResult">Python Importer parser returned empty result. </entry>
    <entry key="NoCodeToImport">가져올 코드를 찾을 수 없습니다. 적어도 하나의 소스 파일 또는 include 파일을 지정하십시오. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotLoadFile">지정된 파일 ''{0}''을(를) 불러올 수 없습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="EmptySourceFile">가져올 소스 파일을 한 개 이상 지정하십시오. </entry>
    <entry key="CannotReadFunctionSettings">Failed to read Python Importer settings. The specified file ''{0}'' is not a Python Importer settings file, or is corrupted. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsFilePath">Unable to load the file ''{0}'' because it does not exist on the computed file path ''{1}''. Check your full path specification ''{2}'' against output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAbsPath">Unable to find the directory ''{0}''. Check your directory folder specification against the output folder. Output folder is current working directory if it is not specified. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonPackageName">''{0}''은(는) 유효하지 않은 Python 패키지 이름입니다. Simulink에서는 밑줄 문자로 시작하는 Python 패키지 이름이 지원되지 않습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonModuleName">Python 모듈 이름 ''{0}''이(가) 유효하지 않습니다. Simulink에서는 밑줄 문자로 시작하는 Python 모듈 이름이 지원되지 않습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonClassName">Python 파일 ''{1}''의 Python 클래스 이름 ''{0}''이(가) 유효하지 않습니다. Simulink에서는 밑줄 문자로 시작하는 Python 클래스 이름이 지원되지 않습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPythonFunctionName">Invalid python function name ''{0}'' in python file ''{1}''. Python function name starting with an underscore character is not supported in Simulink. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPackageNameWithRelativePath">''{0}''은(는) 유효하지 않은 Python 패키지 이름입니다. Python 패키지를 지정하려면 절대 경로를 사용하십시오. </entry>
    <entry key="NonexistentProjectFile">Unable to load project file. Specified project file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="ImportRequiredBeforeAddToProject">Cannot add files to the project. Perform an import before adding to project.</entry>
    <entry key="ProjectWithinIncludeDir">Unable to add file or folder ''{0}'' to the project. File or folder must be inside of specified project root folder ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="SaveTheNewLibraryModel">Python Importer tool requires that you save the library model first.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSaveFile">Failed to save Python Importer settings. </entry>
    <entry key="FilePathNotExist">지정된 폴더 또는 파일 ''{0}''이(가) 존재하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotOverwrite">File ''{0}'' already exists. Specify a different file name, or to overwrite, set 'Overwrite' to 'on'. </entry>
    <entry key="SaveFileIsNotWritable">File ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a file that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="NoFileToLoad">불러올 파일을 한 개 지정합니다. </entry>
    <entry key="NonwritableFolder">Folder ''{0}'' is write-protected. Specify a folder that is not write-protected. </entry>
    <entry key="UnableToOpenSLBlocksFile">디렉터리 ''{0}''에 ''slblocks.m''을 생성할 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLibraryFileName">''{0}'' is not a valid library file name. Specify a valid Simulink model file name.</entry>
    <entry key="NothingToImport">가져올 Simulink 호환 함수 또는 유형이 없습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="MissingPythonInitFile"> Python 패키지는 a __init__.py 파일을 포함해야 합니다. 지정된 폴더 ''{0}''에 __init__.py 파일이 누락되었습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="StaticAnalysisFailedIOTypes"> 정적 분석에서 Python 모듈 ''{0}''의 Python 함수 입력값과 출력값을 식별하지 못했습니다. Simulink가 ''{0}''을(를) 가져올 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecificationDataType"> Simulink Python Import port specification data type must be one of ''double'', ''uint8'', ''int64'', ''boolean'', ''string'' or a Simulink bus. </entry>
    <entry key="NoAvailableFunctionsToImport"> 가져올 수 있는 Python 함수가 없습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecificationLabel"> 밑줄 문자로 시작하는 Simulink Python 가져오기의 포트 레이블은 Simulink에서 지원되지 않습니다. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPortSpecification"> Simulink Python Importer does not support python functions with no inputs and outputs. </entry>
    <entry key="ParseErrors">{0}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
