<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="nav" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="MinPathPoints">Path argument must contain minimum of 3 path points for optimization.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPathInput">Invalid value for path argument. Value must be a double matrix of size N-by-2 or N-by-3.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidArgument">Invalid argument at position 2. The second argument of optimizePath function must be binaryOccupancyMap, occupancyMap, vehicleCostmap, or optimizePathOptions class.</entry>
    <entry key="CutoffLessThanInclusion">ObstacleCutOffDistance must be greater than ObstacleInclusionDistance.</entry>
    <entry key="DelTVelGreaterThanMap">ReferenceDeltaTime*MaxVelocity가 맵의 대각선보다 큽니다. 맵 크기를 늘리거나 ReferenceDeltaTime을 줄이거나 MaxVelocity를 줄이십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="InputPathOutsideMap">Some or all poses in the path are out of map bounds. Path must be in world frame. Choose a different path or map.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStart">Start state of the path is not obstacle-free. Choose a different start state or map.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidGoal">Goal state of the path is not obstacle-free. Choose a different goal state or map.</entry>
    <entry key="DelTVelGreaterThanSafetyMargin">ReferenceDeltaTime * MaxVelocity is greater than 2*ObstacleSafetyMargin, this can lead to path skipping over obstacles. Either increase ObstacleSafetyMargin, reduce ReferenceDeltaTime, or reduce MaxVelocity.</entry>
    <entry key="SafetyMarginGreaterThanMap">2*ObstacleSafetyMargin is greater than the diagonal of the map. Increase map size or reduce ObstacleSafetyMargin.</entry>
    <entry key="TrajectoryParameters">궤적 파라미터</entry>
    <entry key="ObstacleParameters">장애물 파라미터</entry>
    <entry key="SolverParameters">솔버 파라미터</entry>
    <entry key="Weights">가중치</entry>
    <entry key="PoseMoreThanMaxPathStates">경로에 있는 자세 수를 MaxPathStates 값보다 작은 값으로 줄일 수 없습니다. MaxPathStates 값 또는 ReferenceDeltaTime 값을 늘리십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="NumPoseTooLarge">경로에 있는 자세 수가 큽니다. 경로에 있는 자세 수를 줄이거나 ReferenceDeltaTime 값을 늘리십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="InputPathOrthogonality">The input path must contain at least one pose where the travel direction is non-orthogonal to the orientation vector. The travel direction is distance vector connecting the consecutive poses of the input path.</entry>
    <entry key="AngleBetweenPosesLarge">입력 경로에서 연속된 자세 간의 각도 차이가 90도를 초과합니다. 각도 차이를 줄이려면 입력 경로를 보간하여 출력값을 향상시키십시오.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
