<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="UnsupportedVersion">The rosbag parser only supports versions 1.1 and 2.0 of the ROS bagfile format. The given file uses version {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="FileOpenError">An error occurred when opening the bagfile {0}. Make sure the file is readable.</entry>
    <entry key="FileReadingError">An error occurred when reading from the file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileCorruptError">An error occurred while parsing the bagfile {0}. Most likely, the file is corrupt. Try using the "rosbag fix" utility in the standard ROS environment to repair the file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileHeaderEmpty">The file record header was empty. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileHeaderInvalid">Expected file record header not found. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ConnectionHeaderEmpty">The connection record header is empty. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ConnectionHeaderInvalid">Expected connection record header not found. Unable to parse the file.</entry>    
    <entry key="ConnectionInfoHeaderEmpty">The connection information header for topic {0} was empty. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ExpectedMsgDefNotFoundInConnectionHeader">Unable to parse the file. The expected message definition for {0} in connection header does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="ChunkHeaderEmpty">The chunk information record header was empty. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ChunkHeaderInvalid">Expected chunk information record header not found. Unable to parse the file.</entry>        
    <entry key="ChunkInfoVersionInvalid">Expected chunk information in format version {0}, but found {1} instead. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ConnIndexHeaderEmpty">Unable to parse the file. The connection index data record header is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="ConnIndexHeaderInvalid">Unable to parse the file. The expected connection index data record header does not exist.</entry>        
    <entry key="ConnIndexVersionInvalid">Index data format version {0} not supported. Unable to parse the file.</entry>
    <entry key="ConnectionIDInvalid">Invalid connection ID {0}.</entry>    
    <entry key="CellStringInvalid" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Invalid value of argument {0}. Expected value is a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="EvenTimeVector">Invalid value of "Time" argument. Expected value is a vector with an even number of elements, such as [0, 5, 6.5, 7].</entry>
    <entry key="TimeSeriesSingleTopic">Current selection of the message subset in the timeseries function contains {0} topics. Select the message subset so that it contains one topic. For example: select(b, 'Topic', '/topic1')</entry>
    <entry key="MsgIndicesInvalid">The specified message indices are not within the valid range of [{0},{1}].</entry>
    <entry key="MsgPropertyInvalid">The {0} property does not exist for message type {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="MsgPropertyNotScalar">The timeseries function only supports numeric and scalar message properties. However, the {0} property is not scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MsgPropertyNotNumeric">The timeseries function only supports numeric and scalar message properties. However, the {0} property is not numeric.</entry>
    <entry key="FileOpeningError">Unable to open the rosbag file because it is already open or read permission is not available.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedMode">Unsupported mode. 'rosbagwriter' supports only 'Write mode'.</entry>
    <entry key="BagFileOpeningError">Unable to open the rosbag file. Check for the validity of the file path and the read-write permission.</entry>
    <entry key="BagFileAlreadyOpenError"> Unable to open the rosbag file {0} because it is already open or read-write permission is not available.</entry>
    <entry key="PathHasASCII">The file path {0} only contains non ASCII characters. The file path and file name must only contain ASCII characters.</entry>
	<entry key="RosbagWriterError">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MsgTypeNotRegistered">Message type: {0} is not registered with this 'rosbagwriter'. First register it using 'registerMessageType()' and then write to bag file.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedCompression">Compression type not supported. 'rosbagwriter' supports only 'Uncompressed', 'BZ2' and 'LZ4' compression formats.</entry>
    <entry key="RosbagWriteError">An error occurred while writing message with topic: {0} and message type: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="TimeStampListError">Length of input timestamp list does not match the length of input messages. While writing multiple messages using 'write', the length of input timestamp list and the length of input messages must be same.</entry>
    <entry key="TopicListError">Length of input topic list does not match the length of input messages. While writing multiple messages using 'write' the length of input topic list and length of input messages must be same. If all messages belong to same topic, a single topic can be given as input.</entry>
    <entry key="RosbagWriterCreationError">Unable to create the 'rosbagwriter'.</entry>
    <entry key="RosbagWriterInvalidFileError">File must have the extension '.bag'.</entry>
    <entry key="ReadFromDataSourceError">Specify a valid data source path.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMoreMessageAvailable">No more messages are available in current selection.</entry>
    <entry key="FileReadError3P">{0}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
    
