<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014-2020 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="CreateError">Failed to create message of type {0}. This message type might not be available. See help for custom messages.</entry>
    <entry key="NotValidJava">Not a valid Java message object.</entry>
    <entry key="DefinitionNotFound">Unable to find definition of message type {0}. Check the spelling of the message type or use "rosmsg list" to retrieve a list of available message types.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTypeMatch">The type of the input message is {1}. However, this object requires a message of type {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTypeMatchArray">All messages in the input array need to be of type {0}. However, at least one message has a different type.</entry>
    <entry key="NoClassGenerator">The MatlabClassGenerator infrastructure was not found.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotCreateJava">Unable to create Java message with type {0}. The Java implementation for this message type does not yet exist. See the help on custom messages.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMatlabClass">Unable to find a MATLAB message class for type {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="ParsingError">An error occurred while parsing the message definition for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="NotValidFolder">The {0} folder does not exist. Specify an existing folder.</entry>
    <entry key="FolderCreationError">Cannot create folder {0}, or the folder already exists, but is not writable.</entry>
    <entry key="GenerateError">An error occurred while generating MATLAB code for message type {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstantScalar" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Make the constant value of the {0} property a scalar number or a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="NoClassFolders">Do not use class folders, which begin with @, as targets for message generation.</entry>
    <entry key="NoSpaceAllowed">Because it contains a space, the generated namespace, {0}, is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyNamespace">The {0} namespace contains empty components, which is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNamespace">MATLAB software cannot use the {0} namespace because it is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="ExactlyOneSlash">The given message type ({0}) contains {1,number,integer} .The message type must contain exactly one forward slash.</entry>
    <entry key="MessageArraySizeError">The message object expects a scalar or a vector of messages as an input. Try constructing the message object with a valid input.</entry>
    <entry key="CellArrayStringError" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Expected all elements of the cell array {0} to be character vectors, but some had a different data type. Modify your cell array input to only contain character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayDataTypeNotValid">MATLAB cannot print the {0} data type.</entry>
    <entry key="ArrayOutputTruncated">(output truncated at {0} array elements)</entry>
    <entry key="FromStructArrayInputSize">The structure array needs to have {0} elements, but currently has {1}. Try adding or removing elements from the structure array.</entry>
    <entry key="SetJavaMessageTypeMismatch">Expected input to be of type {0}. Instead its type was {1}.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
