<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014-2016 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="FrameNameNotFound">Invalid frame name ''{0}'' in the transformation tree. Use the ''AvailableFrames'' property to see all valid frame names.</entry>
    <entry key="FrameNameLeadingSlashes">The ''{0}'' frame name is invalid. Remove the leading forward slashes.</entry>
    <entry key="BothFrameNamesNotFound">Invalid frame names ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' in the transformation tree. Use the ''AvailableFrames'' property to see all valid frame names.</entry>
    <entry key="SourceTimeOutsideBuffer">Unable to find the transformation between ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' at source time {2}. The given time is outside of the buffered time window. Increase the ''BufferTime'' of the transformation tree or use the timeout in ''getTransform'' to wait for a source time in the future.</entry>
    <entry key="FramesNotConnected">The ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' frames are not connected in the transformation tree. Try waiting for the transformation to be available on the ROS network or check that the frame names are correct.</entry>
    <entry key="WaitTimeout">The transformation did not become available within {0} seconds. Try using a larger timeout value.</entry>
    <entry key="NoValidTransformation">No valid transformation was found between ''{0}'' and ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="MessageTypeNotSupported">The {0} message type is not supported for transformation. Try one of the supported types: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="TfTypeNotValid"> Invalid message type {0} on the /tf topic. Valid message types are: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidQuaternion">The rotation quaternion between the ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' coordinate frames is invalid. It has been replaced by the unit quaternion in the tf transformation tree.</entry>
    <entry key="ShutdownError">An error occurred while shutting down the transformation tree.</entry>
    <entry key="GetTransformBehaviorChange">The behavior of getTransform will change in a future release. If only TARGETFRAME and SOURCEFRAME are specified and the transformation is not available, getTransform will display an error and not return an empty TF.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
