<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--Copyright 2020-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="ros">
  <message>
    <entry key="invalidFileType">Expected {0} file to have extension "{1}". Instead, it has extension "{2}".</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCurrentTime">Expected current time to be in the range [{0}, {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="fileDoesNotExist">File {0} does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="fileOpenFailed">Unable to open {0} file {1}.\n\n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCalibrationFileIncorrectEnabledLaserCountForDeviceModel">Invalid Velodyne calibration XML File. Number of enabled lasers for device model {0} is expected to be {1, number, integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCalibrationFileTagNotFound">Invalid Velodyne calibration XML File. &lt;{0}&gt; tag not found in file.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCalibrationFileIncorrectEnabledLaserCount">Invalid velodyne calibration XML File. Enabled lasers count should be 16, or 32, or 64.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCalibrationFileMissingCalibrationValues">Invalid Velodyne calibration XML File. Calibration values missing for some enabled lasers.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidCalibrationFileNonnumericTagValue">Invalid Velodyne calibration XML File. Expected numeric value for &lt;{0}&gt; tag.</entry>
    <entry key="calibrationFileReadError">Error reading calibration XML file.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputArg">Invalid input argument. Input should be a frame number of numeric type or a time offset in seconds of type duration.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidTimeDuration">Expected time duration to be in the range [{0}, {1}].</entry>
    <entry key="laserCalibDataNotSet">Velodyne laser calibration data not initialized.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidArgTypeForLaserCalibrationData">Invalid data type. The LaserCalibrations field of calibration data structure must be a float array.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidArgValueForLaserCalibrationData">Invalid argument value. LaserCalibrations data should be Mx9 float array.</entry>
    <entry key="errorReadingFrame">Error reading Velodyne frame. Make sure the deviceModel matches with the device that records this ROS message.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidArgTypeForROSMessage">Data type not supported. The input message must be velodyne_msgs/VelodyneScan ROS messages.</entry>
    <entry key="emptyROSMessage">Empty Velodyne message. velodyneROSMessageReader cannot interpret an empty message.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDeviceModel">Invalid device model data type. Input should be a string or character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="endOfMessage">End of message reached. Unable to access next frame.</entry>
    <entry key="missingMessageField">No {0} field found in the message. The input message must be velodyne_msgs/VelodyneScan ROS messages.</entry>

  </message>
</rsccat>
