<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="fixed" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="angleOutOfDomainOfConvergence">{0}에서 입력 각도 {1}이(가) 수렴 영역을 벗어났습니다. 입력값은 최대 시프트 값 {4}의 범위 [{2}, {3}] 내에 있어야 하고 {5}(으)로 양자화되어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="cart2pol_YXDataTypesMustMatch">The Y and X arguments must be of the same data type.</entry>
    <entry key="cart2pol_YXMustBeReal">The Y and X arguments must be real-valued.</entry>
    <entry key="cart2pol_invalidDataValue">The input argument values must be numeric, finite, and non-empty.</entry>
    <entry key="cart2pol_invalidDims">The Y and X arguments must be the same size (or either can be scalar).</entry>
    <entry key="cart2pol_invalidMixedDataTypes">The Y and X arguments must be of the same data type class (mixing floating-point and non-floating point types or double and single types is not supported).</entry>
    <entry key="invalidDataType">The datatype ''{0}'' is unsupported for the function {1}</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputDataTypeAcos">The input ''cosVal'' must be a single, double, or fi object with the property ''DataTypeMode'' equal to ''Fixed-point: binary point scaling'', ''Scaled double: binary point scaling'', ''double'', or ''single''.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidInputDataTypeAsin">The input ''sinVal'' must be a single, double, or fi object with the property ''DataTypeMode'' equal to ''Fixed-point: binary point scaling'', ''Scaled double: binary point scaling'', ''double'', or ''single''.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNiters">The number of iterations (niters) argument of function {0} must be a positive integer-valued scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidNitersCodeGen">반복 횟수 인수는 양의 정수 값 스칼라여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidParameter">인수가 구문 분석기의 유효한 파라미터와 일치하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidScaleOutputArg">인수 ''ScaleOutput''의 유효성 검사에 실패했습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSinCosInput">The input value of function {0} must be a real, finite value in the range [-1, 1].</entry>
    <entry key="invalidThetaValue">The angle (theta) argument values of function {0} must be real, numeric, non-empty, and in the range [-2*pi, 2*pi).</entry>
    <entry key="inputWordLengthNotGTOne">CORDIC input arguments must have word lengths greater than one.</entry>
    <entry key="nitersConstCodeGen">CORDIC 커널의 반복 횟수를 나타내는 입력값은 상수여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="pol2cart_invalidR">The magnitude (r) argument values must be real (consider using CORDICROTATE for complex vector rotation).</entry>
    <entry key="rotate_invalidDims">The u and theta arguments must be the same size (or either can be scalar).</entry>
    <entry key="rotate_invalidMixedDataTypes">The u and theta arguments must be of the same data type class (mixing floating-point and non-floating point types or double and single types is not supported).</entry>
    <entry key="rotate_invalidU">The u argument values must be numeric and non-empty.</entry>
    <entry key="thetaValueOutOfRange">함수 {0}의 각도(theta) 인수 값은 범위 [-2*pi, 2*pi) 내에 있어야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidHyperbolicArgument">The angle (theta) argument value of function {0} must be real, numeric, non-empty and finite.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidHyperbolicArgumentHDL">The angle (theta) argument value of function {0} must be real, numeric, scalar and finite.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
