<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--Copyright 2013-2020 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale ="en_US" product="SimulinkBlocks" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
<message>

  <entry key="EmptyTransferFunction">
    Either the numerator or the denominator of the transfer function as
    specified by the block parameters is empty.
  </entry>

  <entry key="DenominatorMatrixParameter"> 
    Denominator of the transfer function cannot be a matrix. Change it to a row
    vector.
  </entry>

  <entry key="ImproperTransferFunction"> 
    The given transfer function is an improper transfer function. The order of
    the transfer function numerator must be less than or equal to the order of
    the denominator.
  </entry>

  <entry key="ImproperTransferFunctionInGeneralRealization"> 
    The given transfer function is an improper transfer function because all
    coefficients of the numerator and the denominator are considered tunable at
    run time. The order of the transfer function numerator must be less than or
    equal to the order of the denominator.
  </entry>

  <entry key="StateSpaceTransformFailed">
    A time domain realization of the given transfer function for block ''{0}''
    failed. Check values of ''{1}'' and ''{2}'' parameters.
  </entry>

  <entry key="InvalidRuntimeChangeInTransferFunction">
    A change in parameters ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' for the transfer function block
    ''{2}'' causes a structural change in the time domain realization of the
    transfer function. This is not allowed when the simulation is running.
  </entry>

  <entry key="RuntimeChangeInOrderOfDenominator">
    A change in the order of the denominator results in a change in the number
    of states in the time domain realization of the transfer function.
  </entry>

  <entry key="InvalidRuntimeChangeInOrderOfNumerator">
    A change in numerator introduces a direct dependency of the output on the
    block input in the time domain realization of the transfer
    function. However, the simulation was started with no such dependency.
  </entry>
  
  <entry key="DenominatorHasLeadingZerosInTunableRealization">
      The denominator of the transfer function block ''{0}'' has leading zeros 
      which can lead to a mismatch in results between different simulation modes 
      and/or code generation targets.
  </entry>
    
  <entry key="DenominatorHasLeadingZerosInTunableCodeGeneration">
      The denominator of the transfer function block ''{0}'' has leading zeros 
      which will cause the state-space realization to have non-finite values and 
      cause the simulation to fail.
  </entry>
  
</message>
</rsccat>
