<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="insframework" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="expectedCellstr">Expected a cell array of character vectors for the {0} property.</entry>
        <entry key="OptsDatatype">Valid choices for the {0} property are 'double' or 'single'.</entry>
        <entry key="OneOpts">Specify only one insOptions input. The insOptions should be the last argument.</entry>
        <entry key="MotionLast">A motion model should be the final argument before an optional insOptions argument.</entry>
        <entry key="OtherInputs">All inputs must be either a sensor, a motion model, or an insOptions.</entry>
        <entry key="NeedUniqueNames">The sensor names must be unique.</entry>
        <entry key="SensorNotFound">The sensor was not used to design this filter.</entry>
        <entry key="NumSensorAndNamesNotEqual">Number of sensors and sensor names must be equal.</entry>
        <entry key="StateInfoSensorArg2">Expected the second argument to be the handle to a sensor used to design this filter.</entry>
        <entry key="StateInfoStringInput">Expected a string or character vector for the final argument.</entry>
        <entry key="MotionModelRequired">A motion model is required as input when custom sensors are used.</entry>
        <entry key="SetSameStateNumel">Expected a {0} element array when setting this state.</entry>
        <entry key="StatePartsOutOnGet">The stateparts function does not return a value when used to set part of the State vector.</entry>
        <entry key="StateCovPartsOutOnGet">The statecovparts function does not return a value when used to set part of the StateCovariance matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="StateInfoChoice">When {0} is called with a handle to a sensor class, valid choices are : {1}. If access to a motion model state is required, call {0} with two arguments : the filter handle and state name.</entry>
        <entry key="SensorTwice">This sensor has already been added to this filter or another filter.</entry>
        <entry key="SetStateCovNumel">Set the covariance associated with this state with either a scalar, an {0}-element vector, or a {0}-by-{0} matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="InstanceRequired">A filter instance is required.</entry>
        <entry key="MeasSizeExpected">Expected a measurement that was {0} elements but the supplied measurement was {1} elements</entry>
        <entry key="MeasJacobianSizeExpected">The measurement Jacobian for class {0} was {1}-by-{2} but expected {3}-by-{4}. The Jacobian should be a NUMEL(measurement)-by-NUMEL(states) matrix.</entry>
        <entry key="GPSMeasSize">The measurement input for FUSE or RESIDUAL with a GPS sensor can be either 3 or 6 elements long. However, if Velocity is not tracked in the filter State property, then the measurement can only be 3 elements long.</entry>
        <entry key="MeasSize3">Expected a 3-element measurement for the {0} sensor.</entry>
        <entry key="EstimateTimeTable">Expected the second input to be a timetable of sensor data.</entry>
        <entry key="EstimateMnoiseStruct">Expected the third input to be a struct of measurement noises.</entry>
        <entry key="EstimateVarNames">The variable names of the sensor data timetable should match the filter's SensorNames property. The table variable {0} is not one of {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="EstimateMnoiseNames">The field name {0} of the third input, the measurement noise, must be one of: {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="CopyPrivateProtected">The object {0} has private or protected properties which cannot be copied. To copy these, implement a {0}/copy method.</entry>
        <entry key="ExpectedValidClassName">Expected the input to be a string or character vector which can be a valid class name.</entry>
        <entry key="ExpectedInputToBeSensor">Expected the input to be an INS sensor object.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
