<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="EventTableInput">Creating an event filter from an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then create the event filter from the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="EventFilterOnEventTable">Using an event filter as a subscript on an event table is not supported. Attach the event table to a timetable by assigning it to the timetable's Events property, then subscript into the timetable using the event filter.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsAttached">Creating an event filter for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To create an event filter from this timetable, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventsForSubscripting">Using an event filter as a subscript for a timetable with no attached events is not supported. To subscript this timetable with an event filter, first attach an event table to the timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="NoEventLabelsForSubscripting">To subscript into a timetable using an event filter created using an event label value, the event table attached to the timetable must have the EventLabelsVariable property set.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEventFilterInput">eventfilter에 대한 입력값이 유효하지 않습니다. 입력값은 다음 중 하나여야 합니다:\n - string형 벡터, 문자형 벡터 또는 문자형 벡터로 구성된 셀형 배열\n - 타임테이블\n - 스칼라 누락값.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">eventfilter에 유효하지 않은 이항 연산자 입력값입니다. 두 피연산자 모두 eventfilter 객체여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="EventTimeTypeFilterError">이벤트 필터를 사용하는 ''{0}'' 행 시간값과 ''{1}'' 이벤트 시간값을 갖는 타임테이블에 첨자를 사용하는 것은 지원되지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelFilterError">Comparison between the event labels variable ''{0}'' and the event filter value failed.</entry>
    <entry key="EventLabelTypeMismatch">이벤트 변수 ''{0}''의 유형은 ''{1}''이고 이벤트 필터 값의 유형은 ''{2}''입니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTime">이벤트 레이블 변수는 datetime형, duration형 또는 calendarDuration형 변수일 수 없습니다. 연결된 이벤트 테이블의 rowtimes를 기준으로 타임테이블 이벤트를 필터링하려면 먼저 eventfilter에 대한 입력값으로 타임테이블을 사용하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableChar">문자열 행렬에서 이벤트 필터를 만드는 것은 지원되지 않습니다. 대신 string형 배열을 사용하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableSize">여러 이벤트 레이블 값에 대해 하나의 이벤트 필터를 생성하려면 값은 비어 있지 않은 열 벡터여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLabelsVariableTabular">이벤트 레이블 변수는 테이블 변수일 수 없습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="NegationUnsupported">이벤트 필터는 논리 부정 연산자(~)를 지원하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">이벤트 필터를 사용한 첨자는 이벤트 테이블이 연결된 타임테이블의 행을 선택할 때만 지원됩니다.</entry>
    <entry key="UIStringDispEventLabelsVariable">&lt;이벤트 레이블 변수&gt;</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
