<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="InputType">TIMESERIES2TIMETABLE에 대한 모든 입력값은 timeseries 객체여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="NonscalarInput">TIMESERIES2TIMETABLE에 여러 개의 입력값이 주어진 경우 이들 값은 모두 스칼라 timeseries 객체여야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidUnit">The unit specified in the timeseries DataInfo is not supported in timetable. A timetable variable unit must be scalar text.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTimeUnit">The unit specified in the timeseries TimeInfo is not valid for constructing a duration. The allowed units are: 'weeks', 'days', 'hours', 'minutes', 'seconds', 'milliseconds', 'microseconds', and 'nanoseconds'.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTime">The time vector or start value specified in the timeseries TimeInfo are not valid for constructing a timetable. Both values are expected to be numeric.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInterpMethod">The interpolation method specified in the timeseries DataInfo is not valid for a timetable. The allowed methods are: '', 'linear', and 'zoh'. </entry>
    <entry key="IgnoringEvents">이 입력값에 시작 날짜 또는 시간 단위가 유효하지 않은 이벤트가 포함되어 있으므로 이벤트가 무시되었습니다: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="IgnoringQuality">timeseries의 Quality는 타임테이블에서 지원되지 않습니다. 타임테이블을 생성할 때 무시됩니다.</entry>
    <entry key="TimeVectorMismatch">모든 입력값은 동일한 시간 벡터, TimeInfo Units 및 TimeInfo StartDate를 가져야 합니다. 개별적으로 각 timeseries를 타임테이블로 변환한 다음, SYNCHRONIZE 함수를 사용하여 타임테이블을 결합하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="NumberOfRowsMismatch">timeseries의 시간 벡터는 모두 길이가 같아야 합니다. 개별적으로 각 timeseries를 타임테이블로 변환한 다음, SYNCHRONIZE 함수를 사용하여 타임테이블을 결합하십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyTimeVector">모든 입력값은 비어 있지 않은 시간 벡터를 가져야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyTimeseriesArray">timeseries array input must be non-empty.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStartDate">이벤트는 유효한 시작 날짜를 가져야 합니다.</entry>
    <entry key="TimeInfoNotUniform">시계열 이벤트는 모든 이벤트에 대해 등간격 시간 정보를 가져야 합니다.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
