<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2020 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
      <!-- Errors from MATLAB code -->
      <entry key="noLastConnection">Bluetooth Classic device connection has not been made before.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidIdentifierType">Invalid device identifier. Device name or address must be specified as a string or character vector.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidIdentifierValue">Unable to find paired device with specified name or address "{0}". Run bluetoothlist to check device status and channel number.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidChannel">Invalid device channel. Device channel must be specified as an integer between 0 and 255.</entry>
      <entry key="invalidTimeout">Invalid timeout value. Timeout must be specified as an integer greater than or equal to {0}.</entry>
      <entry key="connectionExists">Connection to this device already exists in the workspace.</entry>
      <entry key="failedGetPairedDevices">Unexpected error - Failed to get paired devices. Contact Technical Support if issue persists.</entry>
      <entry key="nosave">Saving bluetooth object to a MAT-file is not supported.</entry>
      
      <!-- Errors from C++ AsyncIO plugins -->
      <entry key="failedConnect">Unable to connect to device. Run bluetoothlist to check device status and channel number.</entry>  
      <entry key="failedConnectAddressInUse">Unable to connect to device because device is already in use.</entry>
      <entry key="failedConnectConnectionRefused">Unable to connect to device because device refused the connection.</entry>
      <entry key="failedConnectConnectionTimedOut">Unable to connect to device because connection has timed out.</entry>
      <entry key="failedConnectWithArgs">Unable to connect to device due to the following error: "{0}". Run bluetoothlist to check device status and channel number.</entry>
      <entry key="failedDisconnect">Something went wrong while disconnecting from device. You might need to repower the device before reconnecting.</entry>
      <entry key="failedDisconnectWithArgs">An error occurred while disconnecting from device - "{0}". You might need to repower the device before reconnecting.</entry>
      <entry key="failedWrite">Failed to write to device. Check device status.</entry>
      <entry key="failedWriteConnectionAbort">Failed to write to device because device connection was lost.</entry>
      <entry key="failedWriteOperationAbort">Failed to write to device because the operation was aborted. Check system Bluetooth status and device status.</entry>
      <entry key="failedWriteWithArgs">Failed to write to device due to the following error: "{0}". Check device status.</entry>
      <entry key="failedLoadConnectionLost">Unable to receive data from device because device connection was lost.</entry>
      <entry key="failedLoadWithArgs">Unable to receive data from device due to "{0}". Check device status.</entry>
      <entry key="connectionLost">Device connection is lost.</entry>
      <entry key="pluginError">Unexpected error - "{0}". Contact Technical Support if issue persists.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>