<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
    <message>
        <entry key="AlternativeGestureSupport">"{0}" gesture does not support objects of class "{1}". Use "{2}" instead.</entry>
        <entry key="AmbiguousOptionMatch">Specified option is not unique. Use indices to disambiguate.</entry>
        <entry key="AmbiguousSelectionType">Specifying the SelectionType and Button-Modifier name-value arguments is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="CanNotBeDeselected">Unable to deselect objects of {0} class.</entry>
        <entry key="ClientError" note="This is an assertion message intended for internal use only">An internal error occurred in the client:\n{0}</entry>
        <entry key="ComponentNotMultiSelectable">Specified component does not support multiselection.</entry>
        <entry key="ContainerIsLocked">{0} is locked to prevent unintended interactions during testing. To unlock it, use matlab.uitest.unlock.</entry>
        <entry key="ColumnNotSortable">Unable to sort the specified column because the ColumnSortable property is false for the column.</entry>
        <entry key="GestureNotCompleted">Gesture did not complete within {0} second(s).</entry>
        <entry key="GestureNotSupported">"{0}" gesture is not supported on this component.</entry>
        <entry key="GestureNotSupportedForClass">"{0}" gesture does not support objects of class "{1}".</entry>
        <entry key="GestureNotSupportedForDialog">"{0}" gesture does not support a "{1}" dialog box.</entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectCellValues">To select all cells in between two cells, specify the start and stop cell indices as a 2-by-2 array.</entry>
        <entry key="IndexExceedsNumberOfOptions">Index must not exceed the number of options ({0}) in the dialog box</entry>
        <entry key="YYAxisPositionNotSupported">Specifying a position when interacting with the right y-axis is not supported. To perform a gesture on the axes, use 'yyaxis' to make the left y-axis active.</entry>
        <entry key="Invalid3DAxesCoordinate">3-D axes coordinate must be a 1-by-3 numeric array.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidAxesCoordinate">Axes coordinate must be a 1-by-2 or 1-by-3 numeric array.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidContextMenuOption">Invalid context menu item.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidFolderSelection">Value "{0}" is not a valid folder.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTableCell">Specified cell indices are invalid.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTableHeader">Specified column index is invalid.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSelectionDataType">Specify either a valid string, character vector, cellstr, or numeric index.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeEditableAndEnabled">Component must be editable and enabled.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeScalar">Input must be a scalar.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeScalarTextOrIndex">Input must be a character vector, string scalar, or numeric index.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeTextOrIndex">Input must be a character vector, cell array of character vectors, string array, or numeric index.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeTextOrIndices">Input must be a character vector, cell array of character vectors, string array, or numeric indices.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeUIFigure">Input must be a figure handle or array of figure handles created with the uifigure function.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeValidHGHandle">Input must be a valid graphics object.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBeValidHandle">Input must be a valid handle object.</entry>
        <entry key="MustBelongToUIFigure">Component must be the child of a figure created with the uifigure function.</entry>
        <entry key="MustHaveSingularParent">Tree nodes must have the same parent.</entry>
        <entry key="MustNotBeNaT">Specified datetime must not be NaT.</entry>
        <entry key="NeedsToUnblockDialog">Not enough gestures specified to close all the blocking dialog boxes.</entry>
        <entry key="NoAlertDialogsFound">Unable to find any alert dialog boxes in the figure window.</entry>
        <entry key="NoConfirmationDialogsFound">Unable to find any confirmation dialog boxes in the figure window.</entry>
        <entry key="NoDisplay">Gestures on MATLAB Apps require figure display.</entry>
        <entry key="NoValidCoordinateFound">Unable to find any valid coordinates using the function handle passed to the fplot function.</entry>
        <entry key="NoOptionMatch">Unable to find the specified item.</entry>
        <entry key="NoBlankAreaFound">Unable to find a blank area in the table.</entry>
        <entry key="NoHeaderFound">Unable to find the specified row or column headers in the table.</entry>
        <entry key="NotALeafMenu">Gestures are not supported on menus that contain other menus.</entry>
        <entry key="NotAllDialogGesturesPerformed">Skipping some gestures because the number of specified gestures exceeds the number of blocking dialog boxes.</entry>
        <entry key="NotInSameDimension">Start and end coordinates must have the same number of dimensions.</entry>
        <entry key="NotWithinViewableArea">Gesture location must be within the axes viewable area.</entry>
        <entry key="OutOfBounds">Gesture location outside figure bounds.</entry>
        <entry key="OutOfViewport">Unable to perform the gesture because the gesture location is outside the viewable area of the application and the framework could not bring the component into view. Make sure that the component is supported by the scroll function and that its ancestors have their Scrollable property set to true, or update the gesture location if these conditions are met.</entry>
        <entry key="ParentTabUnselected">Component's parent tab must be selected before performing the gesture.</entry>
        <entry key="RootDescendant">The component must be a descendant of the root.</entry>
        <entry key="StaleElement">Unable to perform the gesture using the specified component.</entry>
        <entry key="UnEditableTableCell">Specified table cell is uneditable.</entry>
        <entry key="UnitsMustBePixels">Performing a gesture at an explicitly specified location is not supported for nonpixel units.</entry>
        <entry key="UnknownGesture">Unknown gesture "{0}".</entry>
        <entry key="UnknownPopupOptionSupplied">Popup option supplied is not valid.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedSelectionModeForSingleCellStrategy">Contiguous selection of a single cell is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedTableCellColumnFormat">Unable to perform the specified gesture on the table cell.</entry>
        <entry key="UntypableTableCell">Specified table cell does not support type gestures.</entry>
        <entry key="VisibleHierarchy">Component must belong to a visible hierarchy.</entry>
        <entry key="ValueOutsideLimits">Specified value must be within component limits.</entry>
        <entry key="WarnInHGCallbacks">MATLAB UI Test gesture invoked within a graphics object callback.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  rsccat multiselection uitest yyaxis DAxes ALeaf Viewport Scrollable uneditable
     LocalWords:  nonpixel Untypable
-->
