<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Block mask description for sensors -->
<!-- Copyright 2022 The MathWorks, Inc.-->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="matlab_sensors" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="spfBlockDesc"> \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time: \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time</entry>
        <entry key="spf">Samples per frame:</entry>
        <entry key="timeStampDesc">The Timestamp output represents the time since the block execution started.</entry>
        <entry key="lsm6dsMaskDescription"> Measure linear acceleration and angular velocity along X, Y, and Z axis and temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration and angular rate as [1X3] vectors of type double, and temperature as a scalar value of type double.
            \n\nThe Status output is a [1X3] vector of int8 values which represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements. The status value is -1 if the corresponding output is not selected, 0 if the data read is new, and 1 if data read is not new.</entry>
        <entry key="icm20948MaskDescription"> Measure linear acceleration, angular velocity, magnetic field along X, Y and Z axis, and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration, angular rate, and magnetic field values as [1X3] vectors and temperature as a scalar value.
            \n\nThe Status output is a [1X2] vector of uint8 values whose first element represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements and second element represents status of magnetometer measurements.The status value is 0 if the data read is new,
            and 1 if data read is not new for the corresponding measurement.</entry>
        <entry key="adxl34xMaskDescription">Measure linear acceleration along X, Y, and Z axis from ADXL34x family of accelerometers.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration values as [1X3] vector in units of m/s^2.</entry>
        <entry key="lsm303cMaskDescription">Measure linear acceleration, magnetic field along X, Y and Z axis and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration as a [1X3] vector of double values in m/s^2, magnetic field values as a [1X3] vector of double values in microtesla, temperature value in degree Celsius, Acceleration status of the values [Z, Y, X] as a [1x3] vector and Magnetic Field status
            of the values [Z, Y, X] as a [1x3] vector where 0 indicates that the data read is new and 1 indicates that data read is not new.</entry>
        <entry key="lsm6dsMaskTimeStampSPFDescription"> Measure linear acceleration and angular velocity along X, Y, and Z axis and temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration and angular rate as [1X3] vectors of type double, and temperature as a scalar value of type double.
            \n\nThe Status output is a [1X3] vector of int8 values which represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements. The status value is -1 if the corresponding output is not selected, 0 if the data read is new, and 1 if data read is not new.
            \n\nThe Timestamp output is a double value that represents the time since the block execution started.
            \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time:
            \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time </entry>
        <entry key="icm20948MaskTimeStampSPFDescription"> Measure linear acceleration, angular velocity, magnetic field along X, Y and Z axis, and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration, angular rate, and magnetic field values as [1X3] vectors and temperature as a scalar value.
            \n\nThe Status output is a [1X2] vector of uint8 values whose first element represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements and second element represents status of magnetometer measurements. The status value is 0 if the data read is new,
            and 1 if data read is not new for the corresponding measurement.
            \n\nThe Timestamp output is a scalar value that represents the time since the block execution started.
            \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time:
            \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time </entry>
        <entry key="adxl34xMaskTimeStampSPFDescription">Measure linear acceleration along X, Y, and Z axis from ADXL34x family of accelerometers.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration values as [1X3] vector in units of m/s^2. The Timestamp output is a scalar value that represents the time since the block execution started.
            \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time:
            \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time </entry>
        <entry key="lsm303cMaskTimeStampSPFDescription">Measure linear acceleration, magnetic field along X, Y and Z axis and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration as a [1X3] vector of double values in m/s^2, magnetic field values as a [1X3] vector of double values in microtesla, temperature value in degree Celsius, Acceleration status of the values [Z, Y, X] as a [1x3] vector and Magnetic Field status
            of the values [Z, Y, X] as a [1x3] vector where 0 indicates that the data read is new and 1 indicates that data read is not new.
            \n\nThe Timestamp output is a double value that represents the time since the block execution started.
            \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time:
            \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time </entry>
        <entry key="bme680MaskDescription">Measure barometric air pressure, relative humidity, ambient temperature, index for air quality (IAQ) , equivalent carbon dioxide concentration (eCO2) and breath volatile organic compound concentration (bVOC) from BME68x family of sensors.
            \n\nThe block outputs barometric air pressure in Pascal (Pa), relative humidity in %, ambient temperature in {0}C, index for air quality, eCO2 and bVOC values in units of ppm (parts per million) respectively, along with the status of the IAQ values. Status is 0 if IAQ data read is new and 1 if IAQ data read is not new. All outputs are of single data type, except for IAQ Status, which is uint8.</entry>
        <entry key="bme680I2CAddress">I2C address:</entry>
        <entry key="bme680Mode">Mode:</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActivePressure">Pressure (Pa)</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActiveHumidity">Humidity (%)</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActiveIAQ">IAQ</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActiveeCO2">eCO2</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActivebVOC">bVOC</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActiveIAQStatus">IAQStatus</entry>
        <entry key="bme680IsActiveTemperature">Temperature ({0}C)</entry>
        <entry key="bme680SampleTime">Sample time</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160AnymotionAmplitudeMessage">Any motion amplitude</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160SingletapAmplitudeMessage">Single tap amplitude</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160HighGTimeMessage">High g time</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160FlatThetaMessage">Flat theta</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160HighGAmplitudeMessage">High g amplitude</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160SlowmotionAmplitudeMessage">Slow motion amplitude</entry>
        <entry key="bmi160MaskDescription">Measure linear acceleration and angular rate along X, Y, and Z axis and measure temperature from BMI160 sensor. Measure magnetic field along X, Y, and Z axis by connecting BMM150 as a secondary sensor to BMI160.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration, angular rate, and magnetic field values as separate [1X3] vectors in units of m/s^2, rad/s, and {0}T respectively. The block also outputs status of the measured values in polling mode, interrupt source, tap interrupt source, high g interrupt source and any motion interrupt source. Status is 0 if data read is new and 1 if data read is not new. The block also outputs temperature value in {1}C. Connect BMM150 as a secondary magnetometer through ASDA and ASCL pins of BMI160.
            \n\nInterrupt source output is a [1X7] vector with elements corresponding to the source of single tap, double tap, high g detection, any motion, slow motion, flat detection, and data ready interrupts respectively. 1 indicates that it is the source, 0 indicates that it is not a source, and -1 indicates that the interrupt is not active.
            \n\nTap source output is a [1X4] vector, with the first three elements indicating whether the tap/double tap occurred in X, Y and Z axis, and the fourth element indicating whether it is on positive or negative direction of the axis. High g source output is a [1X4] vector, with the first three elements indicating whether the High g interrupt occurred in X,Y and Z axis and the fourth element indicating whether it is on positive or negative direction of the axis. Any motion source output is a [1X4] vector which shows on which of the X,Y and Z axis did Any motion interrupt occur and whether it is on positive or negative direction of the axis. First byte denotes whether the event occurred on X axis, second byte denotes whether the event occurred on Y axis, third byte denotes whether the event occurred on Z axis and fourth byte denotes the direction. For direction byte 0 denotes negative side and 1 denotes positive and for other bytes 1 denotes that axis is the source and 0 denotes that axis is not the source.
            \n\nWhen interrupts are enabled use external interrupt block and develop respective function call subsystem.</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhMaskDescription">
            Measure analog and digital values of linear acceleration, voltages at ADC inputs, and temperature from LIS3DH sensor. Recognize application features like single/double click, inertial wake-up, free-fall, 4D position, 4D movement, 6D position, and 6D movement. Only two of the application features can be configured at a time from inertial wake-up, free-fall, 4D position, 4D movement, 6D position and 6D movement.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration along X,Y, and Z axis as a [nX3] vector, where n is Number of FIFO samples that you specify. If Enable FIFO is not selected, n = 1. The status output value is 0 if the data read is new, 1 if data read is not new, and 2 if an overflow occurs. If HPF is enabled, the block uses the Normal mode for filtering acceleration values. Accelerometer output data rate (ODR) depends on accelerometer resolution and HPF cutoff frequency depends on ODR.
            \n\nIf Generate data ready interrupt is selected, an interrupt is generated on the INT1 pin depending on the FIFO settings - Either when a new data is available (when FIFO is disabled) or when FIFO buffer has the number of samples specified (when FIFO is enabled).
            \n\nThe block also outputs voltage in the range 0.8V to 1.6V by sensing the voltage on the dedicated ADC pins.
            \n\nThe block outputs single/double click axis as a [1x3] vector. The click axis provides information of the axis in which click is detected. The axis value is 1 if click is detected and 0 if no click is detected.
            \n\nThe block supports inertial wake-up, free-fall, 6D position, 6D movement, 4D position and 4D movement recognition.  The block outputs inertial wake-up axis as a [1x3] vector. The inertial wake-up axis provides information of the axis in which inertial wake-up is detected. The block outputs freefall. The 6D position axis and 6D movement axis are of size 1x6. The 4D position and 4D movement axis are of size 1x4. The status contains the information about the axis, on which the detection is recognized. If the configured detection is recognized on the selected axis, the axis value is displayed as 1 otherwise it is displayed 0. </entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhI2CAddress">I2C address:</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhEnableFIFO">Enable FIFO</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhFIFOSamples">Number of samples to read from FIFO (1 - 32)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhAcceleration">Acceleration (m/s^2)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhADC1">Voltage (external input at ADC1)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhADC2">Voltage (external input at ADC2)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhADC3">ADC3 output</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhStatus">Acceleration data ready status</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhHPF">Enable high pass filter</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhCutoff">HPF cutoff frequency (Hz)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhRange">Accelerometer range</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhResolution">Accelerometer resolution</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhODR">Accelerometer output data rate (Hz)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhDataType">Data type</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhSampleTime">Sample time</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhInterruptPin">Interrupt pin</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhDataInterrupt">Generate data ready interrupt on INT1 pin </entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhEnableClick">Enable click detection</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickInterrupt">Generate click interrupt</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhThreshold">Threshold (m/s^2)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhTimeLimit">Time limit (s)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhTimeLatency">Time latency (s)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhTimeWindow">Time window (s)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickThresholdValidation">acceleration value limit for click detection</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickTimelimitValidation">time limit value for click detection</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickTimeLatencyValidation">time latency value for click detection</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickTimeWindowValidation">time window value for click detection</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickProp">Click status</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhClickType">Type</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhFIFOOverrunInterrupt">Generate FIFO overrun interrupt on INT1 pin</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableConfigurableDetections1Interrupt">Configurable detection 1</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableConfigurableDetections2Interrupt">Configurable detection 2</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhDuration">Duration (s)</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhPositiveXDirection">X axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhPositiveYDirection">Y axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhPositiveZDirection">Z axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhNegativeXDirection">-X axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhNegativeYDirection">-Y axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhNegativeZDirection">-Z axis</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhEnableConfigurableDetections">Configurable detections</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections1Prop">Configurable detections 1 status</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections2Prop">Configurable detections 2 status</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhSameConfigurableDetections">Configuration detections 1 and configuration detections 2 must be different</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhFIFOSamplesValidation">Number of samples to read from FIFO</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections1Interrupt">Generate configurable detection 1 interrupt</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections2Interrupt">Generate configurable detection 2 interrupt</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections1DurationValidation">duration value for configurable detections 1</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections1ThresholdValidation">acceleration value limit for configurable detections 1</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections2DurationValidation">duration value for configurable detections 2</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhConfigurableDetections2ThresholdValidation">acceleration value limit for configurable detections 2</entry>
        <entry key="lis3dhADCPinValidation">Invalid pin name. Valid pin names are ADC1, ADC2, ADC3.</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505MaskDescription"> Measure acceleration, angular velocity along X, Y and Z axis, and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration and angular rate values as [1X3] vectors and temperature as a scalar value.
            \n\nThe Status output is a scalar of uint8 values which represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements. The status value is 0 if the data read is new, and 1 if data read is not new.
        </entry>
        <entry key="adis16505ChipSelectPin">SPI chip select pin</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505InterruptType">Interrupt type</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Accel">Acceleration (m/s^2)</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Gyro">Angular velocity (rad/s)</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Temp">Temperature ({0}C)</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Status">Status</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505DesiredODR">Desired output data rate (1 Hz - 2000 Hz)</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505AcheivedODR">Achieved output data rate (Hz)</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505bartlettFilter">No of taps for Bartlett window filter</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Datatype">Data type</entry>
        <entry key="adis16505Sampletime">Sample time</entry>
        <entry key="SSPinInvalidValue">ADIS16505 sensor block parameter SPI chip select pin must be {0}.</entry> 
        <entry key="adis16505MaskTimeStampSPFDescription"> Measure linear acceleration and angular velocity along X, Y and Z axis, and measure temperature.
            \n\nThe block outputs acceleration and angular rate values as [1X3] vectors and temperature as a scalar value.
            \n\nThe Status output is a scalar of uint8 values which represents status of acceleration, angular rate, and temperature measurements. The status value is 0 if the data read is new, and 1 if data read is not new. The Timestamp output is a scalar value that represents the time since the block execution started.
            \n\nThe Samples per frame value that you specify is the number of samples that block outputs, and it is also used to compute the output sample time: 
            \n   Output sample time = Samples per frame * Sample time
            \n\nBefore reading data, configure the SPI Properties in the Configuration Parameters window. Go to Hardware Implementation pane > SPI Properties and set SPI clock out frequency (in MHz) to 2000000, SPI mode to 3, and Bit order to 'MSB first'.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
