<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2022 The MathWorks, Inc.
-->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="matlab_sensors" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="sensorNotResponding">Sensor is not responding. Reconnect the sensor and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="licMissing">''{0}'' property is not supported. Download Navigation Toolbox or Sensor Fusion and Tracking Toolbox to use the property.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidDeviceID">Incorrect device ID read from the connected sensor. Expected device ID (value stored in WHO_AM_I register) for {0} is ''{1}''. Make sure that the correct device is connected.</entry>
        <entry key="GPSBuffersFlushed">Flushing internal buffers. You will receive new GPS data in 1/(Update Rate) seconds.</entry>
        <entry key="enableStreaming">''{0}'' property is not supported when 'Streaming' is false. Clear the object and recreate the object with 'Streaming' property set to true to use this property.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidHwObjSensor">Incorrect hardware object. Use a valid hardware object for instantiating sensor devices.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedFunctionSensor">Function ''{0}'' is not supported for sensor objects.</entry>
        <entry key="incorrectI2CAddressSensor">Incorrect I2C address for the sensor. Specify the correct I2C address. Here are the list of possible I2C addresses {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="multipleSameI2CAddress">Multiple sensors of the same type connected. Please specify different I2C address for each sensor during instantiation. Refer to the sensor data sheet on how to specify different I2C addresses for the same sensor.</entry>
        <entry key="expectedI2CDeviceNotFound">Expected sensor not detected. Connect the right sensor to the hardware and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="streamingInProgress">Unable to stream data for the sensor as data streaming for the other sensors are in progress. To stream data from sensor object, release the other sensor objects, and call sensor read.</entry>
        <entry key="streamingNotSupportedOnHardware">Function ''{0}'' is not supported on sensor objects on ''{1}'' hardware. </entry>
        <entry key="streamingPropertiesNotSupportedOnHardware">Property ''{0}'' is not supported on sensor objects on ''{1}'' hardware. </entry>
        <entry key="unSupportedOnDemandFunction">Function ''{0}'' is not supported. To use the function, download Navigation Toolbox or Sensor Fusion and Tracking Toolbox. </entry>
        <entry key="unSupportedCommandLogs">Command logs are not supported for {0}. Create the hardware Object with property 'TraceOn' disabled.</entry>
        <entry key="dataNotReceivedOnDemand">Unable to read data from the sensor. Check if the device is properly connected,clear all hardware objects and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="incorrectNumI2CAddresses">Incorrect number of I2C addresses. Expected {0} I2C addresses.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidSampleRateRange">Maximum permitted sample rate is less than the minimum sample rate. Check the sample rate limits.</entry>
        <entry key="wrongChecksum">Dropping data due to incorrect Checksum in ''{0}'' sentence.</entry>
        <entry key="configureGPSwhileLocked">Cannot configure once the object is locked. Release the GPS object and then try configuration.</entry>
        <entry key="validateGPS">Obtaining the required NMEA sentences (RMC,GGA,GSA) is taking longer than expected. Verify the physical connection of the GPS device to the specified serial port and the configuration of the GPS device.</entry>
        <entry key="differentReadModeProperty">All the sensor objects should have same 'ReadMode' property. Set the same 'ReadMode' property for the sensor objects and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="hostBuffersFlushed">MATLAB buffers are flushed to get latest values.</entry>
        <entry key="unSupportedOnDemandProperty">Property 'Streaming' is not supported. Download Navigation Toolbox or Sensor Fusion and Tracking Toolbox to use the property.</entry>
        <entry key="streamingNotEnabledGPS">Property 'Streaming' is not enabled for GPS where other sensor objects are created with 'Streaming' property as true. Delete all objects and recreate all sensor and GPS objects with 'Streaming' property set as true.</entry>
        <entry key="unSupportedPropertiesNoLic">Property {0} not supported. To use the properties {1}, download Navigation Toolbox or Sensor Fusion and Tracking Toolbox.</entry>
        <entry key="unSupportedPropertiesNoStreaming">Property {0} not supported with 'Streaming' set as false. Create the object with 'Streaming' property set as true to use {0}.</entry>
        <entry key="sensorSampleRateLimitation">To read data from both GPS and IMU together, keep the sample rate of IMU greater than ''{0}''. Change the sample rate of IMU and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidIntTypeRanged">Invalid parameter type. The {0} value must be a scalar integer.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidI2CAddressValue">Invalid value for I2C address. The address may either be a string representation of a hex value, a binary or hex representation of an uint8 scalar, or a positive scalar integer.</entry>
        <entry key="scanI2CBusFailure">Device not detected on I2C Bus {0}. Make sure the I2C device is properly connected.</entry>
        <entry key="functionMissing">Implement ''{0}'' method in hardware class.</entry>
        <entry key="mandatoryNVPairSPIChipSelect">Not enough input arguments for connecting to an SPI device. Specify 'SPIChipSelectPin' parameter followed by a corresponding value</entry>
        <!-- Adding sensor codegen messages -->
        <entry key="ParameterNotSupported">''{0}'' parameter is not supported in code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="propertyValueFixedCodegen">Setting ''{0}'' property is not supported in code generation. The value of ''{0}'' is always fixed to ''{1}''.</entry>
        <entry key="ParamNotNumeric">Value of {0} supported on the hardware must be numeric.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBusType">Invalid type for {0} bus number, the {0} bus must be a positive scalar double. Valid bus numbers are {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBusValue">Invalid {0} bus number. Valid bus numbers are {1}.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidI2CAddressType">For code generation 'I2CAddress' parameter must be passed as a numeric scalar or vector.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedFunctionSensorCodegen">Function ''{0}'' is not supported for sensor objects during code generation.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedFunctionCodegen">Function ''{0}'' is not supported for code generation.</entry>

        <!-- BNO055 Sensor -->
        <entry key="uncalibratedSensor">{0} is uncalibrated. Calibrate BNO055 sensor to ensure sensor returns correct data. See &lt;a href=&quot;matlab:helpview('matlab', ''calibratebno055'')&quot;&gt;Calibrate BNO055 Sensors&lt;/a&gt; for the steps.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedSampleRate">Failed to set 'SampleRate' in 'ndof' operating mode. Sample rate is fixed at 100 samples/s in 'ndof' operating mode.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedFunctionBNO055">Function ''{0}'' is not supported when the 'OperatingMode' property of BNO055 is set to ''{1}''. To use this function, clear and recreate the object with 'OperatingMode' set to ''{2}''.</entry>
        
        <!-- LIS3DH Sensor -->
        <entry key="unsupportedDataReadyInterruptFeature">Data ready interrupt cannot be enabled in external mode. Data ready interrupt is applicable only in build and deploy.</entry>
        <entry key="unsupportedFunctionCallWhileStreaming">Function read{0} is not supported after using the read function that read data continuously at the specified rate from the sensor. To use the function read{0} stop the data collection from sensor object using the function stop and then use the function read{0}.</entry>

        <!--Simulink sensor block errors -->
        <entry key="I2CAddressNotFound">Device not detected on I2C Bus. Make sure the I2C device is properly connected.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidHwObjSensorSimulink">Incorrect hardware object. Ensure correct steps are followed for adding sensor for a target.</entry>
        <entry key="FunctionNotAvailableSimulinkSensors">Function {0} not found. Ensure correct steps are followed for adding sensor for a target.</entry>
        <entry key="SensorsNoOutputs"> No outputs selected. Select at least one output to continue.</entry>
        <entry key="outOfRangeI2CAddress">Invalid I2C address. Specify value as hex or scalar integer in the range (8, 119).</entry>


        <!-- Sample time validation errors -->
        <entry key="SampleTimeNonTunable">Sample time is a nontunable property. You cannot change the sample time value while the model is running.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTimeNeedScalar">Invalid sample time. Sample time must be a real scalar value.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTimeNeedPositive">Invalid sample time. Sample time must be non-negative or -1 (for inherited).</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTimeNeedSmallerOffset">Invalid sample time. Sample time offset must be smaller than the sample time period.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTimeNeedZeroOffset">Invalid sample time. When the period is -1, offset must be 0.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTimeNeedOffsetOne">Invalid sample time. When the period is 0, offset must be 1.</entry>

        <!-- Sensor block with frame outputs error -->
        <entry key="ExpectedSystemObjectBlockH">Function createSensorBlockWithFrameOutput expects the handle of MATLAB System block without mask on mask.</entry>
        <entry key="OutportsExceeded">Number of outports exceeds the number of frame blocks available.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSampleTime">Sample time values 0, inf or -1 are invalid if Samples per frame value is greater than 1. Either specify a discrete block sample time or specify Samples per frame as 1.</entry>

        <entry key="InvalidSPIChipSelect">Parameter name 'SPIChipSelectPin' must be specified followed by a corresponding value, which is the pin number to which ADIS16505 sensor is connected. To see the possible values, enter 'SPIChipSelectPin' in ADIS16505 object creation syntax and then press Tab</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidSensorObject">Unrecognized parameter name ''{0}''. Use 'SPIChipSelectPin' instead.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidArguments">Invalid Sensor object. Sensor object creation supports either specifying the I2CAddress or the SPIChipSelectPin.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidTapValue">Invalid 'NumTapsBartlettFilter' value. Press tab to identify the valid values for 'NumTapsBartlettFilter'.</entry>
        <entry key="DeviceNotConnected">ADIS16505 sensor not detected. Ensure that sensor is properly connected to hardware board.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
