<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021-2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLABTest">
    <message>
        <entry key="FileNotFound">Unable to find the specified MATLAB Function "{0}".</entry>
        <entry key="BuiltInFunctionsNotAllowed">Specified function is a built-in MATLAB function. These functions are not allowed. You need to provide a different function name.</entry>
        <entry key="EmbeddedCoderNotPresent">Embedded Coder is required for DLL or LIB verification.</entry>
        <entry key="UnexpectedCoderConfiguration">The specified coder configuration is "{1}". The expected coder configuration is "{0}".</entry>
        <entry key="GenerateCode">### Generating code for "{0}" ({1} configuration)</entry>
        <entry key="BuildSuccess">Code generation successful.</entry>
        <entry key="EntryPointNotSpecified">A valid function name is required to call a single entry-point function from a multiple entry-point MEX. To do that, use the "{0}" name-value argument on the execute method.</entry>
        <entry key="IncorrectEntryPoint">Specified entry-point "{0}" is not a recognized entry-point function.</entry>
        <entry key="ExecuteMEXFcn">### Executing "{0}" with specified run-time inputs</entry>
        <entry key="ExecutionSuccess">Execution successful.</entry>
        <entry key="ConfigOptionNotAllowed">Use the "Configuration" name-value argument to specify different build configuration instead of '-config'.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedOption">Code generation argument "{0}" is not supported in a MATLAB Coder equivalence test.</entry>
        <entry key="LaunchReportWithoutFolder">Launching the code generation report requires the build artifacts to be present. Use the "PreserveInFolder" name-value argument in the build() method to preserve artifacts.</entry>
        <entry key="CodegenWarningLocation">Warning in ==> {0}</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedConfigParameter">Code generation configuration parameter "{0}" is not supported in a MATLAB Coder equivalence test.</entry>
        <entry key="CodeGenerationDirArgumentNotAllowed">Using "-d" as a code generation argument in a MATLAB Coder equivalence test is not allowed. Use the "PreserveInFolder" option in the build() method instead to preserve the build artifacts.</entry>
        <entry key="UnsupportedTarget">Unable to generate code because the specified code generation target is not supported. You must specify one of these code generation targets: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="NoCoderServices">Unable to equivalence test the MATLAB code because a required toolbox is not installed. To generate and test MEX functions, ensure that MATLAB Coder is installed. To generate and test static or dynamically linked C/C++ libraries, ensure that Embedded Coder is installed. Use the ver function to check which products are installed.</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  rsccat
-->