<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="comparisons" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>
        <entry key="MergeActionFailed">Merge action failed because one or more objects were unable to be inserted. Verify that there is space in the target model for the inserted object.</entry>
        <entry key="ParentNotExist">Merge action failed because Stateflow node should always be parented.</entry>
        <entry key="CannotInsertGraphObjectsInGroupState">Inserting graphical objects is not supported in a grouped state.</entry>
        <entry key="CopyOrPasteFailed">Merge action failed because one or more objects to be inserted violate clipboard rules during copy or paste.</entry>
        <entry key="LastTransition">The last transition of a {0} is unable to be removed.</entry>
        <entry key="ChangeDecompositionCondition">To allow adding the condition, change the decomposition of {0} to exclusive (OR).</entry>
        <entry key="OneChildStateRow">{0} can be inserted from the choice model into the target model if the parent state in the target model has at least one child state row.</entry>
        <entry key="AllDestinationsExist">{0} can be inserted from the choice model into the target model if all destinations already exist in the target model.</entry>
        <entry key="ChangeDecompositionDefaultTransition">To allow adding the default transition, change the decomposition of {0} to exclusive (OR).</entry>
        <entry key="DefaultTransitionExists">Unable to add a default transition to state {0} because a default transition path row exists in its parent hierarchy.</entry>
        <entry key="ChangeDecompositionHistory">To allow adding a history junction, change the decomposition of {0} to exclusive (OR).</entry>
        <entry key="ChildStateRowForHistoryJunction">To insert a history junction, {0} must have at least one child state row.</entry>
        <entry key="AddParentRow">Add parent row before adding this row.</entry>
        <entry key="RemoveDefaultTransitionForParallelDecomposition">To set the decomposition to parallel, remove the default transition path row.</entry>
        <entry key="RemoveInnerTransitionForParallelDecomposition">To set the decomposition to parallel, remove the inner transition path row.</entry>
        <entry key="RemoveHistoryJunctionForParallelDecomposition">To set the decomposition to parallel, remove the history junction.</entry>
        <entry key="RemoveConditionTextForParallelDecomposition">To set the decomposition to parallel, remove text from all conditions in the children.</entry>
        <entry key="MergeUserChanges">Currently merging user changes is not implemented (mergeable objects without edits)</entry>
        <entry key="MergeTextNodeDoesNotExist">Unable to merge text if node does not exist</entry>
        <entry key="UnknownRowType">Unknown row type.</entry>
        <entry key="InsertConditionDestinationPREV">Unable to insert condition with destination state set to $PREV.</entry>
        <entry key="InsertConditionDestinationNEXT">Unable to insert condition with destination state set to $NEXT.</entry>
        <entry key="InsertConditionDestinationDoesNotExist">Unable to insert condition if the destination state does not exist.</entry>
        <entry key="OneDefaultTransition">Unable to add more than one default transition path row.</entry>
        <entry key="InvalidMLFBHandle">The handle is not a valid MATLAB Function block handle.</entry>
        <entry key="ChangeDecompositionITPR">To allow adding an inner transition path row, change the decomposition of {0} to exclusive (OR).</entry>
        <entry key="ChangeDecompositionDTPR">To allow adding a default transition path row, change the decomposition of {0} to exclusive (OR).</entry>
        <entry key="CannotSetDestinationEndpointForSuperTransition">Setting DestinationEndpoint for supertransitions is not supported.</entry>

    </message>
</rsccat>

