<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="imagesui">
    <message>

        <!-- Viewer Validation -->
        <entry key="interactionsString" note="">'Interactions' value must be 'all', 'none', or a string array of these values: \n \n'rotate', 'zoom', 'pan', 'clip', 'slice', 'axes'</entry>
        <entry key="clippingPlaneMax" note="">Set at most 6 clipping planes.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidViewer" note="">Specify parent as a valid Viewer object.</entry>
        <entry key="noReparent" note="">Reparenting object is not supported.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidPlane" note="">Specify planes as a 1-by-4 vector where the first 3 elements are a unit vector.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidChild" note="">Viewer children must be objects of the following type: \n \nimages.ui.graphics.Image\nimages.ui.graphics.Volume\nimages.ui.graphics.BlockedVolume\nimages.ui.graphics.Surface</entry>
        <entry key="invalidCurrentObject" note="">'CurrentObject' must be a child of the Viewer object.</entry>
        <entry key="emptyViewer" note="">Interactive drawing requires at least one visible object in the Viewer.</entry>
        <entry key="clippingInteractions" note="">'ClippingInteractions' must be 'all', 'none', or a string array of these values: \n \n'add', 'remove', 'rotate', 'translate'</entry>
		<entry key="sliceInteractions" note="">'SliceInteractions' must be 'all', 'none', or a string array of these values: \n \n'add', 'remove', 'rotate', 'translate'</entry>
        <entry key="cropInteractions" note="">'CropInteractions' must be 'all', 'none', or a string array of these values: \n \n'add', 'remove', 'move'</entry>
        <entry key="javaGraphics" note="">3-D rendering is not supported in figures created with the figure function. Use uifigure to create a supported figure for 3-D rendering.</entry>
        <entry key="orthoCameraRequired" note="">An orthographic camera is required to view the scale bar.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidCameraPosition" note="">'CameraPosition' must not match the values of 'CameraTarget'.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidModeObject" note="">'CurrentMode' must be a valid object in the Mode property.</entry>
        <entry key="lightMax" note="">Set at most 10 lights.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidBox" note="">Specify box as a 2-by-3 matrix where the first and second rows correspond to minimum and maximum values of the box, respectively.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidSphere" note="">Specify sphere as a 1-by-4 matrix where the first three elements correspond to the center and the fourth element corresponds to a non-negative radius respectively.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidCylinder" note="">Specify cylinder as a 1-by-5 matrix the first three elements correspond to the center, the fourth element corresponds to a non-negative radius and the fifth element corresponds to a non-negative height respectively.</entry>
        <entry key="repeatedViewer" note="">Specified 'Parent' already contains a Viewer object. To render additional objects in the same scene, specify 'Parent' as a handle to the existing Viewer object.</entry>
        <entry key="cropRegionDimension" note="">CropRegion must be specified as an empty array or an array with dimensions (2,3), (1,4) or (1,5).</entry>
        <entry key="licenseError" note="">Viewer requires a valid Image Processing Toolbox license.</entry>
        <entry key="installError" note="">In order to use the Viewer, you must have Image Processing Toolbox installed.</entry>

        <!-- WebGL Management -->
        <entry key="contextLost" note="">The graphics card on this machine encountered an issue during rendering. Consider freeing up graphics resources on this machine, downsampling your data, or creating multilevel blockedImages to display large data.</entry>
        <entry key="webGL2NotSupported" note="">The graphics card on this machine does not meet the minimum requirements for visualization.</entry>
        <entry key="errorEncountered" note="">Viewer encountered an error during rendering: {0}</entry>
        <entry key="outOfMemory" note="">Insufficient memory for visualization. Viewer will attempt to render a downsampled version of the scene. Consider creating multilevel blockedImages to display large data.</entry>
        <entry key="contextLostFinal" note="">The graphics card on this machine encountered an issue during rendering and the rendering could not be recovered.</entry>
        <entry key="hardwareRequired" note="">Hardware accelerated graphics support is required for this 3-D visualization.</entry>

        <!-- Surface Validation -->
        <entry key="invalidInput" note="">Surface must be a 3-D triangulation object or a 3-D logical array.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidTriangulation" note="">Triangulation object must contain 3-D data.</entry>
        <entry key="invalidMask" note="">Mask must be a 3-D logical array with no singleton dimensions.</entry>

        <!-- Points Validation -->
        <entry key="invalidPoints" note="">Points must be an M-by-3 array of (x, y, z) locations.</entry>

        <!-- Wide Line Validation -->
        <entry key="invalidNaNSeparator" note="">Line segments must be separated by a complete row of NaN values.</entry>

        <!-- Annotation Validation -->
        <entry key="invalidTextPosition" note="">Text position must be specified as a 1-by-3 array for world coordinates or as a 1-by-2 array for normalized screen coordinates.</entry>
        <entry key="caliperDistance" note="">Caliper distances must not exceed the distance between the endpoints specified by the Position property.</entry>
        <entry key="mustSpecifyImage" note="">Viewer contains more than one image. Specify the image handle as an input to resolve ambiguity.</entry>
        <entry key="noImage" note="">Viewer does not contain a valid image.</entry>
        <entry key="noValidImage" note="">Image object must be valid.</entry>

        <!-- Object Info -->
        <entry key="overlay" note="">Overlay</entry>
        <entry key="intensity" note="">Intensity</entry>
        <entry key="row" note="">Row</entry>
        <entry key="column" note="">Column</entry>
        <entry key="color" note="">Color</entry>

        <!-- Compatibility -->
        <entry key="parentProperty" note="">The property {0} is not supported on the Volume object. Set the {1} property on the Volume object's parent Viewer.</entry>
        <entry key="removedProperty" note="">The property {0} is no longer supported with volume rendering.</entry>
        <entry key="renamedProperty" note="">The property {0} is no longer supported. Use the {1} property.</entry>
        <entry key="removedMethod" note="">The function setVolume is no longer supported. Use the 'Data' property to update the volume.</entry>
        <entry key="removedFunction" note="">{0} has been removed. With appropriate code changes, use 'volshow' instead.</entry>

    </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe context of message-->