<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MCR" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="MCLMCRMCC_CANNOT_FIND_MCR_ROOT">Cannot find MATLAB Runtime root directory in environment variable MATLABROOT.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRMCC_ERROR_INTIALIZING_MCR">Error initializing MATLAB Runtime.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRMCC_ERROR_SETTING_COM_DIR">Error setting compilation directory to: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRMCC_ERROR_SETTING_COM_DIR_NULL">Error setting compilation directory: directory was NULL!</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRMCC_FULL_PATH">fullpath = {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRSIMULINK_INVALID_OUTPUT">Error in S-function. Evaluation of expression resulted in an invalid output. Only finite double outputs are supported</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCRSIMULINK_INVALID_OUTPUT_WIDTH">Error in S-function while computing the output. The width of the result was {0,number,integer}, and was expected to be {1,number,integer}"</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ARCHIVE_REMOVAL_FAILED">Failed to remove out-of-date CTF archive: \n   ''{0}''. \n Re-extraction of archive may fail.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ASSERTPCTIDENTITY_USAGE">USAGE: assertPCTIdentity(private_key,decrypt_func_name)</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_AUTH_FILE_EMPTY">Authentication file ''{0}'' is empty \n Cannot load mex file</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_AUTH_FILE_READ_FAILED">MEX Authentication file read Failed!</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_BAD_FILE_FOR_PATH">The file\n   ''{0}''\n exists, but is cannot be added to the MATLAB Runtime path because it is not a directory.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_BAD_MCR_USER_DATA" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Incorrect format for -mcruserdata key:value argument.\n Both the key and value must be character vectors.\n Found   : ''{0}''\n \n The -mcruserdata switch will be removed from the argument list, but the \n key:value argument will be passed to your main program. This may cause\n an error in your main program if this input is unexpected.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CACHE_ACCESS_ERROR">Could not access the MATLAB Runtime component cache. Details: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CACHE_DIR_NOT_ABSOLUTE">The MATLAB Runtime component cache directory (''{0}'') must be an absolute path. Check the value of the MCR_CACHE_ROOT and/or HOME environment variable.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CACHE_DIR_NOT_FOUND">An error occurred while trying to access the MATLAB Runtime component cache: directory\n not found: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CANNOT_CALL_FCN_IN_MATLAB">Cannot call function ''{0}''. MATLAB Compiler-generated software components cannot be used from within MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CANNOT_FIND_AUTH_FILE">Cannot find authentication file ''{0}''. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CANNOT_FIND_COMPONENT_DIR">Cannot find the directory containing the ''{0}'' component, \n which is required by this application. Make sure the directory containing \n ''{1}.ctf'' is on your dynamic load library path \n (PATH on Windows, or LD_LIBRARY_PATH on Linux, for example), or your\n application search path (PATH on both Windows and Linux).</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CANNOT_FIND_CTF_ARCHIVE">Cannot find CTF archive ''{0}''. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CLASS_IN_USE_AT_EXIT">Warning: Class\n    ''{0}''\nin use at MATLAB Runtime termination.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CLEAR_CLASSES_ERROR">Error trying to clear classes.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CLEAR_FUNCTIONS_ERROR">Error trying to clear functions.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_CACHE_ROOT">Component cache root: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_NAME">Component name: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_MAY_TAKE_TIME_TO_EXTRACT">Extracting CTF archive. This may take a few seconds, depending on the\n size of your application. Please wait...</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_ROOT_DOESNT_EXIST">Extracting CTF archive. This may take a few seconds, depending on the\n size of your application. Please wait...</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_ROOT_EXIST">Component Root Exists.  Skipping CTF extraction...</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COULD_NOT_ACCESS_PREF_DIR">Could not access preferences directory: ''{0}''. System error: ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR">Could not create directory: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_COMPONENT_MISMATCH">The ''{0}'' ctf file \n and the corresponding ''{1}'' target (standalone application/shared library) \n created using MATLAB Compiler do not match. Please make sure that the \n ctf and the target are created as output of the same MCC command. You \n can also verify the time stamp of these files to make sure that they were \n created at the same time. Please do not combine the ctf file and the \n target application created during execution of different MCC commands. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_EXTRACT_DONE">...CTF archive extraction complete.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_EXTRACT_NOT_EXCLUSIVE">Unable to obtain exclusive lock on CTF directory. If you are running multiple simultaneous instances of this application, initialization errors may occur.  (To disable this message set the environment variable MCR_INHIBIT_CTF_LOCK.)</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_EXTRACT_NOT_EXCLUSIVE_FIO_ERR">Unable to obtain exclusive lock on CTF directory because of a file access error. If you are running multiple simultaneous instances of this application, initialization errors may occur.  (To disable this message set the environment variable MCR_INHIBIT_CTF_LOCK.  Additional diagnostic information may be available by setting the environment variables DSERVICES_FSLOCK_VERBOSE and DSERVICES_FSLOCK_WARNING.)</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_IN_METHOD_DIR">The path to the CTF archive file for this application contains one \n or more subdirectories whose name begins with ''@''.  Please move the CTF and \n application file to a directory with no ''@'' characters in the path. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_IN_PRIVATE_DIR">The directory containing the CTF archive for this application is named \n ''private''.  Please move the CTF and application file to a directory with \n a different name.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_LOCK_WAIT_TIMED_OUT">Timed out while waiting to acquire an exclusive lock on the CTF directory. If you are running multiple simultaneous instances of this application, initialization errors may occur.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTF_MISSING_PRODUCTS">Unable to access required products file. The CTF archive file may be corrupt. Please recompile the application.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_DELETE_RERUN">Please delete the extraction directory and re-run the application.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_DEMO_LICENSE">Checking DEMO license: Invalid MATLAB Runtime handle</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_EMPTY_MCR_USER_DATA">-mcruserdata appears to have been specified with no argument.\n \n The -mcruserdata switch must be followed by an argument of the form key:value. For example: -mcruserdata "StartUpType:Command Line". \n The -mcruserdata switch will be removed from the argument list.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR">Error Occurred</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_ADDING_TO_MCR_PATH">Error adding to MATLAB Runtime path</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_COMMAND_ARGUMENTS">Error: Incorrect format for command line arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_CONSTRUCTING_CLASS_PATH"><![CDATA[Could not initialize the dynamic Java classpath needed for toolboxes and\n custom java classes. The Java calls may not work in the deployed mode. If\n you are using certain MathWorks toolbox that uses jar files, you can\n extract the CTF archive by either running the application once or using the\n extractCTF utility and then copy the toolbox jar file from \n <component>_mcr/java/jar/toolbox directory to the <mcrroot>/java/jar/toolbox\n directory. For your custom Java class and jar files, you can copy these to\n any directory on your target machine and add this directory and/or the jar\n files with fully qualified path to the classpath.txt in your MATLAB Runtime installation.]]></entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_CONSTRUCTING_PATH">Error constructing MATLAB Runtime Path</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INITIALIZING_CTF">Error initializing CTF archive: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INITIALIZING_MCR">Error initializing MATLAB Runtime</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INITIALIZING_PREFS">Error initializing preferences required to run the application</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INITIALIZING_READER">Error initializing {0} reader</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INITIALIZING_SECURITY">Error initializing Security Context</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INVALID_KEY">Invalid key for initializing MATLAB Runtime</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INVALID_MESSAGE">Invalid message received by the worker</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_INVALID_PCT_LICENSE">Error: This MATLAB compiled application requires Parallel Computing Toolbox.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_READING_FROM_MANIFET">An error occurred while trying to read from the manifest. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_REMOVING_DIR_FROM_MCR_PATH">Error removing directory from MATLAB Runtime path: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_SETTING_MCR_CWD">Error setting MATLAB Runtime current directory to: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_SETTING_UP_READER">Error setting up {0} reader</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_ERROR_VERSION_MISMATCH">Error: This application requires MATLAB Runtime version {0}.{1} to run. The current MATLAB Runtime is v{2}.{3} .</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FILE_EMPTY">File is empty</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FILE_NOT_IN_CTF">The file\n   ''{0}''\n   is not in the application''s expanded CTF archive at\n    ''{1}''.\nThis is typically caused by calls to ADDPATH in your startup.m or matlabrc.m files. Please see the compiler documentation and use the ISDEPLOYED function to ensure ADDPATH commands are not executed by deployed applications.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FILE_READ_FAILED">File read Failed!</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FUNCTION_NOT_FOUND">Function ''{0}'' not found.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_GETMCRAPPKEYS_USAGE">USAGE: [session_key, public_key] = getmcrappkeys</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INSTANCE_CWD">Getting Instance CWD: Invalid MATLAB Runtime handle</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INSTANCE_PATH">Getting Instance Path: Invalid MATLAB Runtime handle</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INVALID_MCR_HANDLE">Terminating MATLAB Runtime: Invalid MATLAB Runtime handle</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INVALID_WARNING_STATE">Could not set warning ''{0}'' to state ''{1}''. Valid states are: ''on'' and ''off''.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INVISIBLE_FIGURE">Name: {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_INVISIBLE_FIGURES_AT_EXIT">Warning: {0,number,integer} invisible figure(s) at MATLAB Runtime termination.\n Figure ID(s):\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MALFORMED_WARNING_STATUS_STRING"><![CDATA[The warning status string ''{0}'' is incorrectly formatted. Warning status\n strings have this format: \n\n     on|off[:all|<warning id>]\n\n For example:\n\n     off:MCR:Extract\n\n     off\n\n     on:all]]></entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MCC_FLAG_MISUSE">''{0}'' may have been excluded from the MATLAB search path at compilation due to misuse of the path related mcc flags (-N, -p, -I).\nHave the application owner verify that these flags were correctly used.\nContact the application owner for more details.\n\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MCR_INITIALIZATION_FAILED">Failed to initialize MATLAB Runtime Instance ''{0}''. \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_COMPONENT_EXPIRED">Failed to initialize MATLAB Runtime Instance: The specified component has expired.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MEC_FILE_READER_CREATION_ERROR">Error creating encrypted M file reader.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MEC_FILE_READER_SETUP_ERROR">Error setting up encrypted M file reader.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MEX_AUTH_FILE_READER_CREATION_ERROR">Error creating MEX auth file reader.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_MEX_AUTH_FILE_READER_SETUP_ERROR">Error setting up MEX auth file reader.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_MATLAB_LOAD">Warning: MATLAB Compiler-generated software components will load, but will not function, in MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_MCR_USER_DATA">Unable to locate a valid MATLAB Runtime instance. Access to MATLAB Runtime user data is not available.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_MEX_TARGET">The MATLAB Runtime does not support the execution of MEX files generated by the\n MATLAB Compiler. (You should never see this message, since the Compiler\n cannot generate MEX files as of MATLAB Release 14.)\n Component name: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_SFUN_TARGET">The MATLAB Runtime does not support the execution of Simulink S-function files\n generated by the MATLAB Compiler. (You should never see this message,\n since the Compiler cannot generate Simulink S-functions as of MATLAB\n Release 14.)\n Component name: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_SIGNATURE_INFO">Could not get the signature information for ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_SIGNATURE_ON_MATLAB_PATH">''{0}'' not found on the MATLAB path</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NO_UNKNOWN_FILE_ON_PATH">The type (directory, plain file, etc.) of file \n   ''{0}''\n cannot be determined. It will not be added to the MATLAB Runtime path.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_NULL_MCRINST">MATLAB Runtime Instance has not been set.  \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_PLATFORM_UNSUPPORTED">Application not supported on {0} due to platform dependencies. Intended platforms include: {1}. For more information, please contact the application author.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_PREF_DIR_NEEDS_WRITE_PERMISSION">MATLAB user preference directory: ''{0}'' requires owner write permission.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_READDIR_ERROR">Could not read directory ''{0}''. Reason: ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_RUNTIME_STAGE_REGRESSION">The installed MATLAB Runtime ({0}) is outdated and not compatible with the application ({1}). Uninstall the existing {0} runtime and install a {1} runtime to run this application.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_SECURITY_CONTEXT_INIT_ERROR">Error initializing security context for the given keys.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_SETMCRAPPKEYS_UNAUTHORIZED_CALLER">The caller is not authorized to use setmcrappkeys.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_SETMCRAPPKEYS_USAGE">USAGE: setmcrappkeys(session_key, public_key)</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_SET_DISPATCHER_CWD">Unable to set dispatcher current directory to: \n{0}\n{1}\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_SFUN">Error in S-function. Evaluation of expression resulted in an invalid output. Only finite double outputs are supported</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_TBX_ROOT_NOT_SET">Unable to determine root directory for MATLAB toolbox. \n Check the values of the environment variables MCRROOT and TOOLBOXMATLABDIR.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNDEPLOYABLE_COMPONENT">''{0}'' was excluded from packaging for the MATLAB Runtime environment according to the MATLAB Compiler license.\nHave the application owner either resolve the file or function from the code, or use the MATLAB function "isdeployed" to ensure the function is not invoked in the deployed component.\nContact the application owner for more details.\n\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNEXPECTED_ERROR">Unexpected error thrown</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_ERROR_CODE">Unknown error code</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_ERROR_IN">An unknown error has occurred in ''{0}'', on line {1,number,integer}.  \n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_ERROR_INITIALIZING_MCR">Error initializing MATLAB Runtime: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_ERROR_IN_IS">An unknown error has occurred in ''{0}'', on line {1,number,integer}.  \n The internal error is: ''{2}''.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_INTERNAL_ERROR">An unknown internal error has occurred in ''{0}''.  \n The internal error is: ''{1}''.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNKNOWN_TARGET">Internal error: the component ''{0}'' has a "Target Type" which the MATLAB Runtime\n cannot recognize. Try recompiling your application, or contacting the\n vendor from whom you obtained the application.\n Component name: ''{1}''</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_VISIBLE_FIGURES_AT_EXIT">Warning: {0,number,integer} visible figure(s) exist at MATLAB Runtime termination.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_WAIT_FOR_FIGURES_STANDALONE">See the documentation on how Standalone applications terminate \n for more information.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_WAIT_FOR_MSG_AT_EXIT">If your application has terminated unexpectedly, please note that \n applications generated by the MATLAB Compiler terminate when there are no \n visible figure windows.\n</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_WRONG_USER_DATA_KEY_TYPE" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Wrong type of data used as MATLAB Runtime user data key. Keys must be character vectors. \n Actual key type: ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNABLE_TO_LOCK_DOWN">Unable to lock mclmcr shared library down- may be unloaded by dispatcher.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_UNABLE_TO_RETRIEVE_CTF_COMPONENT_DATA">Unable to retrieve component data. There was a failure during initialization.</entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FUNCTION_HANDLE_WRONG_MCR">
Component boundary error: function handles may only be used by the component that created them.
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CLASS_INSTANCE_WRONG_MCR">
Component boundary error: MATLAB class instances may only be used by the component that created them.
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_BEGIN_ITER_ARRAY_NOT_CONTAINER">
Internal error: Cannot begin iteration on non-container array. 
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_END_ITER_ARRAY_NOT_CONTAINER">
Internal error: Cannot end iteration on non-container array. 
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CONTAINER_ITERATOR_MISSING_DEREF">
Internal error: operator*() not defined for container iterator type.
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_FORBIDDEN_NON_CONST_CONTAINER_DEREF">
Internal error: Non-const operator*() forbidden for container iterator type.
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_Invalid_MATLAB_Runtime">
The installed MATLAB Runtime is not compatible with the application. Reinstall the MATLAB Runtime or the application using the application installer generated using deploytool.
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CORRUPTED_COMPONENT_CACHE">
    The component cache extracted by the application is corrupt. Contact MathWorks Support for assistance.\n
    Details: ''{0}'' \n
    Original component cache dir is copied to ''{1}'' .\n
    
    </entry>
    <entry key="MCLMCR_CTFPREFDIR_NOT_FOLDER">"''{0}'' is not a folder."</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
