<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2021 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="badIterateFunction">Specified ITER_FUNC handle does not reference a valid function.</entry>
    <entry key="badtype">''{0}'' is not a supported datatype for H5ML.SIZEOF.</entry>
    <entry key="copy_prop_unsupported">The HDF5 function ''H5Pcopy_prop'' implementation is currently disabled.</entry>
    <entry key="getCacheDeprecated">H5P.get_cache is deprecated.  Please use H5P.get_mdc_config instead.</entry>
    <entry key="getPreserveNoLongerUseful">H5P.get_preserve no longer has any effect since compound datatype field preservation is now core functionality in the HDF5 Library.  Please consult the HDF5 User''s Guide and Reference Manual.</entry>
    <entry key="HDF5libDeprecated">This function is deprecated and may be removed in a future version of MATLAB.</entry>
    <entry key="hoffsetDeprecated">This function is deprecated.  Offsets should be computed directly from the size of the datatypes using H5T.get_size.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidIterationFunctionSignature">The iteration function must take three input arguments and provide two output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidFunctionSignatureForIterateScales">The iteration function must take four input arguments and provide two output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidID">An invalid HDF5 identifier was returned from the HDF5 library.</entry>
    <entry key="notFunctionHandle">Specified ITER_FUNC argument must be a function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="notRelativeLinkName">The relative link name should not have a leading slash.</entry>
    <entry key="saveLoad">Saved HDF5 identifiers cannot be reloaded in a valid state.</entry>
    <entry key="setCacheDeprecated">H5P.set_cache is deprecated.  Please use H5P.set_mdc_config instead.</entry>
    <entry key="setPreserveNoLongerUseful">H5P.set_preserve no longer has any effect since compound datatype field preservation is now core functionality in the HDF5 Library.  Please consult the HDF5 User''s Guide and Reference Manual.</entry>
    <entry key="sizeofDeprecated">This function is deprecated.  The size of a compound datatype should be computed from the size of the field datatypes using H5T.get_size.</entry>
    <entry key="unrecognizedObjectType">Unrecognized object type: {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="invalidSizeHint">Size in bytes must be a non-negative value.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
