<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2021 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="shared_gps" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="UnsupportedFunction">Function ''{0}'' is not supported for gpsdev object.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidGPSData">Obtaining the required NMEA sentences (RMC, GGA and GSA) is taking longer than expected. Verify the physical connection of the GPS device to the specified serial port and the configuration of the GPS device.</entry>
    <entry key="UnableToConfigure">Unable to call writeBytes function because the gpsdev object is in use. Release the object first and then try again.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidPort">Unable to connect to the device. Verify that the device is connected to the port, the port is not in use, and all input arguments and Name-Value pairs are supported by the device.</entry>
    <entry key="WrongChecksum">Dropping data due to incorrect checksum in ''{0}'' sentence.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageID">Invalid message ID. Ensure all the steps for adding a new message are followed.</entry>
    <entry key="NoLicense">This feature requires a license for the Navigation Toolbox.</entry>  
    <entry key="InvalidCustomSentenceValue">'CustomSentence' value must be a cell array. Each element of the cell array must be a string array or cell array of character vectors of message ID and function name.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCustomSentenceMessageID">MessageID for the 'CustomSentence' value must be a string or a character array.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCustomSentenceFunctionType">Function specified for 'CustomSentence' value must be a string or character array of the custom function name or passed as a function handle.</entry>    
    <entry key="InvalidCustomSentenceFunction">Function specified for 'CustomSentence' value is not a valid MATLAB function.</entry>          
    <entry key="DuplicateMessageID">">{0} is specified for both 'MessageIDs' property and 'CustomSentence' value. Either use the supported property value to parse {0} or specify {0} as custom message ID to override the built-in support.</entry>                
</message>
</rsccat>
