<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ko_KR" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="OperatorNotSupported">Operator is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTraverseFcn">Not enough arguments. The "traverse" method must have one or more input arguments and one or more output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidVariableName">Variable name "{0}" is not a selected variable. Filter constraints can only be applied on selected variables:\n\n    {1}\n\n</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterInput">Input argument must be a table or timetable.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterOperand">Data type of operand not supported for filtering. Supported operand data types are: numeric, string, logical, datetime, duration scalars, or character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperationOperand">Relational operators (&gt;, &lt;, &gt;=, &lt;=, ==, ~=) with multiple rowfilter or eventfilter inputs are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRelationalOperatorInputs">Relational operator must have a rowfilter or eventfilter object as input.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBinaryOperatorInputs">Invalid binary operator input. Both operands must be rowfilter or eventfilter objects.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForRelationalOperator">Unsupported relational operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterForBinaryOperator">Unsupported binary operator syntax. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="MissingNotSupported">Missing values are not supported as operands to RowFilter.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRowFilterInput">"rowfilter" 함수에 대한 입력값이 유효하지 않습니다. 입력값은 다음 중 하나여야 합니다:\n - string형 벡터, 문자형 벡터, 또는 문자형 벡터로 구성된 셀형 배열\n - ParquetInfo 객체\n - ParquetDatastore 객체\n - DatabaseDatastore 객체\n - 테이블 또는 타임테이블.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidIndexingOperation">Unsupported filtering operation. Use dot indexing to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingInput">Unsupported dot indexing input for filtering. Use a string scalar or a character vector to select a variable for filtering.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidDotIndexingVariableNames">Unrecognized variable name for filtering. Select a variable for filtering using one of the following variable names: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedDotAssignment">Unsupported filtering operation. rowfilter and eventfilter variables cannot be set using dot assignment.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedClassVersion">버전이 호환되지 않으므로 matlab.io.RowFilter를 불러올 수 없습니다.\nRowFilter를 재생성해 보십시오.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidFilterClass">RowFilter 디스패처에 대한 "{0}" 클래스가 유효하지 않습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidSubscripter">Unable to use a row filter to subscript into the variables of a table, timetable, or event table. Specify rows using the syntax T(rf,vars), where rf specifies a row filter and vars specifies variables of T.</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperationFailed">제약 조건을 적용할 수 없음: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedType">Unexpected type returned from relational operator in the "{0}" expression. A logical vector was expected but the expression returned a value of "{1}" type.</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedDimensions">"{0}" 표현식의 관계 연산자에서 예기치 않은 차원의 논리형 행렬이 반환되었습니다. 결과는 빈 논리형 배열이거나 논리형 열 벡터여야 합니다. 그러나 표현식이 {1} 크기의 논리형 행렬을 반환했습니다.</entry>
    <entry key="RelationalOperatorUnexpectedHeight">"{0}" 표현식의 관계 연산자에서 예기치 않은 개수의 행이 반환되었습니다. {1}개 행이 필요하지만, 표현식이 {2}개 행을 갖는 논리형 벡터를 반환했습니다.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
