<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2015 The MathWorks, Inc.
Messages related to Support Package Installer support package root
-->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="supportpkgservices" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/msgcat.xsd">
    <message>            
        <entry key="CannotCreate">There was an error creating the support package root directory "{0}":\n{1}</entry>
        <entry key="NoWritePermissions">MATLAB cannot record the change to support package root: {0}\nChanges to the support package root need to be recorded under MATLABROOT. You may not have permissions to modify files under MATLABROOT. Please restart MATLAB as administrator and try again.</entry>
        <entry key="InstallerOpen">Support package installer is open. Please close support package installer before attempting to change the support package root directory</entry>
		<entry key="InvalidRoot">The specified directory “{0}” contains a corrupt installation of support packages. Please use a different directory.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableToSetSPRoot">Unable to set the support package root directory</entry>
        <entry key="RelativePath">The specified directory "{0}" is a relative path, please provide an absolute path instead.</entry>
        <entry key="UnableToReadSPRoot">Unable to read the support package root directory value from MATLABROOT</entry>
        <entry key="CorruptSettingFile">The support package root setting file "{0}" is corrupt. Please delete the file and try again. If you do not have permissions to modify the file, contact your System Administrator</entry>
        <entry key="NoSettingFile">No setting for the support package root directory was found for this MATLAB installation. Please use "matlabshared.supportpkg.setSupportPackageRoot" to set the value of support package root directory</entry>
        <entry key="DirInUse">The requested support package root directory "{0}" is being used by the following MATLAB installation: "{1}". Please choose a different directory</entry>
        <entry key="FailedInfoFile">Unable to write to the specified support package root directory "{0}": {1}\nPlease ensure the directory is writable.</entry>
        <entry key="DefaultsMaxed">Unable to create a default support package root directory. Please use "matlabshared.supportpkg.setSupportPackageRoot" to explicitly set a support package root directory of your choice.</entry>
        <entry key="NonExistentRoot">The support package root is currently set to a directory that does not exist. The directory may have been deleted. Please use "matlabshared.supportpkg.setSupportPackageRoot" to set the value of support package root</entry>
        <entry key="SpsForDiffMatlab">No support packages were loaded as the specified support package root "{0}" directory contains support packages installed for a different MATLAB installation. It is recommended that a different directory is used before installing any support packages to avoid any unexpected behavior</entry>
        <entry key="UncPathError">The specified support package root cannot be a UNC path.\nUse a mapped network drive instead.</entry>
        <entry key="FolderContainsSpecialChar">The specified support package root contains invalid characters.\nFolder names can only contain alphanumeric characters, dashes and underscores.</entry>
        <entry key="FolderNotWritable">The specified support package root directory is not writable. Choose a folder with write permissions.</entry>
        <entry key="SpacesInFolder">The specified support package root folder name contains a space character.\nCreate or use a folder name that does not contain any space characters.</entry>
        <entry key="ExpectedCharInput">Expected a single char array input</entry>
        <entry key="CannotCanonicalize">Could not canonicalize the specified directory "{0}" - The path does not exist</entry>
    </message>
</rsccat>
