<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018-2022 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="shared_adlib">
  <message>
    <entry key="FirstArgNotFcnHdl" note="" context="error">First input must be a function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="OutputSizeNotNumeric" note="" context="error">OutputSize must be numeric.</entry>
    <entry key="OutputSizeNotCellOfSizeVectors" note="" context="error">OutputSize must be a cell array of size vectors.</entry>    
    <entry key="ReuseEvaluationNotBoolean" note="" context="error">ReuseEvaluation must be true or false.</entry>
    <entry key="AnalysisNotScalarString" note="" context="error">Analyze must be ''on'' or ''off''.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayNotScalarString" note="" context="error">Display must be ''on'' or ''off''.</entry>
    <entry key="ParamNameAmbiguity" note="" context="warning">Created an optimization expression with no optional arguments. You may have intended {0} as an optional argument name, but some inputs that follow it do not match any admissible name-value pair arguments. Refer to the fcn2optimexpr documentation for supported syntaxes.</entry> 
    <entry key="TooManyFcnInputs" note="" context="error">Incorrect number of input arguments to supplied function. Expected {0} but given {1}.</entry>    
    <entry key="FcnError" note="" context="error">Function evaluation failed while attempting to determine output size. The function might contain an error, or might not be well-defined at the automatically-chosen point. To specify output size without function evaluation, use 'OutputSize'.</entry>    
    <entry key="OutputSizeCellTooManyElts" note="" context="error">There are more sizes specified than number of function outputs.</entry>            
    <entry key="OutputSizeCellTooFewElts" note="" context="error">There are fewer sizes specified than number of function outputs.</entry>    
    <entry key="OutputSizeEmptyCell" note="" context="error">OutputSize must be a cell array of size vectors.</entry>   
    <entry key="IgnoreOutputSize" note="" context="warning">Specified OutputSize differs from the calculated output size. Used the calculated output size.</entry> 
    <!--Resource entries for non-error/warning strings-->
	<entry key="AnalysisSuccess" note="" context="diagnostic">The function uses only supported operators. The returned expressions use the operators on the problem variables.</entry>
	<entry key="AnalysisFail" note="" context="diagnostic">The function contains an unsupported operator. The returned expressions are nonlinear black boxes.</entry>
    <entry key="PossibleAssignmentIntoDouble" note="Holes are html tags" context="diagnostic">For ways to avoid creating black boxes, see {0}this doc section{1}.</entry> 
  </message>
</rsccat>

<!--Please use note attribute to describe note="" context of message-->
