<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="ros" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="NoPackage">''.msg'' ファイル、''.srv'' ファイル、または ''.action'' ファイルを含むパッケージが {0} 内に見つかりません。各メッセージ パッケージには、''msg'' という名前のディレクトリに入った ''.msg'' ファイル、''srv'' という名前のディレクトリに入った ''.srv'' ファイル、''action'' という名前のディレクトリに入った ''.action'' ファイル、またはこれら任意のディレクトリの組み合わせが含まれていなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMessageName">メッセージ名 ''{0}'' が無効です。メッセージ名は大文字で始まり、英数字が続かなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCustomMessagesError">検証中に無効なメッセージ形式、パッケージ、または構造体が見つかりました。</entry>
    <entry key="CreateColconIgnore">''{0}'' の作成中にエラーが発生しました: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="CreateCatkinIgnore">''{0}'' の作成中にエラーが発生しました: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="MsgFieldNameError">Invalid message field names in message definition {0}. Message field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the message definition file: {1}}</entry>
    <entry key="SrvFieldNameError">Invalid service field names in service definition {0}. Service field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the service definition file: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="ActionFieldNameError">Invalid action field names in action definition {0}. Action field names must not be a C++ keyword. Change the following field names in the action definition file: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="NoZipFileExists">The input folder is empty. The folder must contain a zip file named {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="FolderExists">The input folder contains {0} folder. To avoid overwriting existing generated messages, copy the zip file to a different location and then execute the registration.</entry>
    <entry key="PlatformNotSupported">Registering these custom messages is not supported for {0}. Sharing custom messages is only supported between systems using the same architecture. You can &lt;a href="matlab:{1}(''{2}'')"&gt;regenerate your custom messages here&lt;/a&gt;</entry>
    <entry key="ReleaseNotSupported">Registering these custom messages is not supported for {0}. This zip file was created on a {1} release. Sharing custom messages is only supported between systems using the same release. You can &lt;a href="matlab:{2}(''{3}'')"&gt;regenerate your custom messages here&lt;/a&gt;</entry>
    <entry key="ParserValidationError">{0}</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
