<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Copyright 2024 The MathWorks, Inc.-->

<rsccat xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0" locale="ja_JP" product="MATLAB" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="AccessForbidden">An Access Token or API Key with the appropriate read/write permissions is required for read or write operations with Google Sheets. Ensure the correct permissions are set.</entry>
    <entry key="BadSheetIndex">指定された 'Sheet' 値は有効なシート インデックスではありません。有効なシート インデックスは、指定したワークブックのシート数以下の正の整数でなければなりません。</entry>
    <entry key="FeatureFlag">Resource not found.</entry>
    <entry key="FilenameCannotBeEmpty">[内部]: Google スプレッドシートの場合、''matlab.io.spreadsheet.internal.createWorkbook'' への 2 番目の入力 ''filename'' は空にできません。</entry>
    <entry key="InternalError">An internal error has occurred while communicating with the Google Sheets server. Cause: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRange">The range must be a character vector or string of the form ''A1:B2'' or ''A1''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidGSheetNamedRangeOrOutOfBounds">Unable to determine range. Range must be a named range in the sheet, or a single cell that cannot exceed 18278 as the column index and cannot exceed 10 million cells.</entry>
    <entry key="MustHaveOneSheet">Cannot delete all the sheets from a Google Spreadsheet. A Google Spreadsheet must contain at least one sheet.</entry>
    <entry key="MergingRulesNotSupported">''MergedCellColumnRule'' and ''MergedCellRowRule'' are not supported for Google Sheets.</entry>
    <entry key="NotFound">Google Sheet with spreadsheetId ''{0}'' not found.</entry>
    <entry key="OperationNotSupported">[INTERNAL]: Loading an entire Google spreadsheet or pre-selecting the date and number formats for the entire workbook are not supported operations.</entry>
    <entry key="RangeTooLarge">The input data exceeds the range for Google Sheets. A Google Spreadsheet cannot exceed 10 million cells or 18278 columns.</entry>
    <entry key="RequestTimedOut">Request to the Google Sheets server timed out. Check the URL of the Google Sheet, the bandwidth of the internet connection, and the firewall settings.</entry>
    <entry key="ServiceUnavailable">The Google Sheets service is currently unavailable. Cause: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="SheetTitlesMustBeUnique">Google スプレッドシートには、同じタイトルの複数のシートを含めることはできません。名前と値の引数 ''SheetTitles'' を使用して、シート タイトルの一意のセットを提供してください。</entry>
    <entry key="SpreadsheetNameTooLong">Google Spreadsheet title cannot exceed 10000 characters.</entry>
    <entry key="SpreadsheetIdNotSupplied">The supplied URL ''{0}'' does not contain a valid Google spreadsheetId.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyRequests">The Google Sheets server is currently limiting the number of requests that can be submitted per minute. Try again in a few minutes.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManySheets">Google スプレッドシートのセルの上限数である 1,000 万個を超えてしまうため、Google スプレッドシートに 384 を超えるシートを含めることはできません。</entry>
    <entry key="TypeNotSupported">A Google sheet must contain only tabular data. Google Sheets consisting of objects such as charts and images are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownMimeType">Input with spreadsheetId ''{0}'' is not a Google spreadsheet. Microsoft Excel spreadsheets have to be converted to Google Sheets for reading or writing.</entry>
    <entry key="UseExcelNotAllowed">''UseExcel'' cannot be used when reading or writing from Google sheets.</entry>
    <entry key="OutofBoundRange">The range violates Google Sheets limits. Start and end boundaries must be positive, with a maximum of 18278 columns and a total area not exceeding 10 million cells.</entry>
    <entry key="WriteSizeLimitReached">The input data exceeds ~2MB size limit that Google Sheets allows for a single write operation. To resolve this issue, consider calling write in a loop on data that is split into smaller chunks using ''WriteMode=append''.</entry>
    <entry key="ReadSizeLimitReached">The range exceeds size limit supported for a single read operation. To resolve this issue, consider calling read in a loop with ''Range''.</entry>
    <entry key="PublishToTheWebGsheetNotSupported">The supplied URL ''{0}'' is an unsupported Google Sheet URL generated via "Publish To The Web".</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
